I'm sorry
I broke your expensive bachelor vase.
Aw.
That's all right. I've learned
that when you're in a loving family
there's nothing wrong
with a little horsing around.
Cut!
That's the show, folks.
Now, let's hear it for our amazing cast.
Joelle. Bradley.
Little Sarah Lynn.
And our star, bojack horseman!
Aw. Thanks for coming out.
Thank you very much.
- Wow.
- Great pilot.
We got the biggest laugh I ever heard
with that "gag me with a spoon" joke.
And then we topped it
with the "get a room" joke.
This was so fun.
Do we get to make more?
I think we got a real shot.
And as long as the ratings don't dip
below a dismal 15 million a night,
we could be on the air for many years.
- No way!
- All right!
- Your squirt, sir.
- Thank you.
And if that happens,
take care of each other.
No matter what,
we're going to stick together.
Thank you, Tina,
for those touching grunts and growls.
I'm Henry winkler.
You probably remember me
from my 2002 guest role
on law & order: Special victims unit.
- Whoo!
- Thank you.
But perhaps the greatest role
I've ever played is friend.
Herb was a dear friend
and I am honored to be dedicating
this bench in his memory.
In his last days, herb's cancer
had gone into remission.
He was full of hope.
But on the drive home from the hospital,
his brakes gave out,
he crashed into a truck full of peanuts.
He survived the crash,
but he was allergic to peanuts.
He died instantly.
Let us now read his final tweets.
"I'm gonna live forever!
Hashtag 'cancer free.'
hashtag 'invincible.'
hashtag 'tweeting while driving.'
oh, no, I think I'm gonna hit that truck.
Hashtag 'hopefully it isn't full
of peanuts.'
hashtag 'oh, no. It was full of peanuts.
I was wondering
where you wandered off to.
- Oh, shn.Hey.
- Hey.
I'm no good with funerals.
When I cry, it messes up my makeup
and then I get really bummed out.
Yeah, same for me.
Herb told me you came
by the house last summer.
Yeah?
Did he tell you anything else?
No, we talked about cancer,
how hard it is living with cancer,
about the la. Kings,
and then back to cancer.
- Probably...
- Then I read that chapter in your book
about how he never forgave you
and he tried to kick you out of the house
and you ended up wrestling on the floor
over a telescope.
- Oh, you did read that part?
- Yeah. Heh.
I just wish
there was something I could do.
Okay, I gotta go.
Wait, I haven't seen you in 30 years.
You wanna go grab a cup of vodka?
I... I'm sorry, the funeral.
I mean, a bottle of vodka?
No. You should stick around.
Hey, maybe you'll find
that something you're looking for.
But if you're ever in new Mexico,
drop me a line.
New Mexico?
I thought you lived in Maine.
I always pictured you there.
A little house by a lake?
Heh. I was just there for, like, a month,
30 years ago.
I live outside Santa fe now.
- Do you think everyone here read my book?
- Well, I didn't.
Of course you didn't.
Here's the cliffsnotes version:
Shut up, Todd!
Okay, you're clearly in one of your moods.
I'm gonna go play astronaut in the trunk
of your car for the next few hours.
Have fun being sad.
Do you know what you're supposed to do
with our date pits?
Why serve dates
and not have a place to put the pits?
You know, some people just have no class.
What are you doing here?
You didn't know herb.
No, but I do know a hot ticket,
and this funeral's a real whom's-whom.
Henry winkler,
Jake and maggot Gyllenhaal,
that Pakistani girl
who keeps winning nobel prizes.
I'm gonna go rub me some elbows.
There's so much to hate
about what you just said.
Good news. You know when someone dies,
everyone wants to buy their shit?
You're lucky you have a piece
of horsin' around,
because this is where money
starts rolling in.
I don't want that money.
That's blood money.
Well, what do you want me to do with it?
It's coming.
I don't know. Give it to some orphans.
- I can't deal with this.
- Oh, come on!
You don't think Elton John
was raking it in when Diana died?
More like "candle in the windfall."
Cha-ching! Hmm.
You have to live with the shitty
thing you did for the rest of your life.
Huh.
Hello, love.
Hey, joelle,
I actually came here to be alone.
I'm at my wit's end, I truly am.
I just flew in across the pond
and I don't know which end is up.
This might be a stupid question,
but were you always so British?
Oh, let's get some light in here,
it's so dreadfully dreary.
Because I'm, like, 70 percent sure
you used to be American.
That's better.
Hey, this one's having a freak-out.
She needs to lie down.
I'm not freaking out.
I just don't understand
why that lady was being all judgy.
You were touching her face
and telling her she was gonna die next.
I'm eccentric. I do weird shit.
How is that my problem?
Hey, when was the last time
all four of us were in the same room?
Probably not since the show ended.
Yeah, I left California
pretty much right after.
Now I got the biggest hardware store
in Seattle.
That's a lie. We're actually in Olympia.
And I'm on the west end
playing Juliet's nurse.
- And how are your kids?
- I don't have any kids.
Oh, I just assumed
you had a bunch of kids,
because, you know, your body.
Come on, Sarah Lynn.
I assumed
you weren't still a massive cunt.
- Jesus Christ, joelle.
- That's an okay thing to say in england.
Shove it up your ass
with a spoonful of sugar,
you supercalifragilisticexpiali-bitch!
- Guys, hey, hey, come on.
- Let go of me!
- I'm gonna hulk out!
- Guys, can we just be civil for one day?
- Oh, you're one to talk.
- What's that supposed to mean?
Were you being civil
when you had sex with my mom?
What? I never... why would...? Wait, which
one was your mom? Blond hair? Glasses?
- No.
- This sucks. You guys suck.
I don't even know
why I came to this party.
It's not a party, it's herb's funeral.
Herb died?
You know, maybe it's for the best
we don't get together that often.
We'd most likely drive each other mad.
Well, no one knows how to get
under your skin like family.
We're not a family, bojack.
We probably won't even see
each other again, until the next funeral.
- Why are you all looking at me?
- You are the oldest.
You are a severe alcoholic.
I'm honestly so high right now,
I don't even know where I'm looking.
Anyway, so long, thanks for the memories,
and don't forget to suck a dick, dumbshi...
Pardon me. Is one of you Sarah Lynn?
I am. Of course. God, are you blind?
Well, forgive me.
I'm herb kazzaz's blind executor.
Per the instructions of his last will
and testament, I am to give you this disk.
Am I close?
Just take the disk from the guy.
It contains directions to herb's gold.
Herb's gold?
There were no further details.
He was a peculiar client.
I told him, I'm not actually an attorney,
I'm just a blind man.
Still, herb thought me wise
for some reason.
Perhaps it is
my overly formal manner of speech.
I bid you good day.
Oh, pardon me. Ow.
Right at shin level.
What are we supposed to do
with a floppy disk?
So, what's up, kiddo?
Bojack and my mom
are becoming, like, friends
and they're acting real weird.
Oof. Uh...
Hey, guys, guys, come on!
There's somebody beneath you!
Jeez, all day with the...
Listen, kiddo, forget about them.
You wanna check out
this cool new game I got?
You have solitaire?
On your computer?
Yep. It only took 12 disks to install it.
Wow.
Herb's computer had a floppy disk drive.
I bet it's still in his old office.
Unless somebody else moved in.
Nobody wanted herb's office, remember?
Because it was under tap dancing star
savion glover's office. Let's go.
- What? Right now?
- Yeah. Don't you get it?
Herb's giving us a reunion special.
Remember how he always wanted to do
a treasure hunt episode of horsin' around
but the network said it was too edgy?
This is that episode.
- I just don't know.
- Yeah, I don't want to do that.
Wait, so you would rather just stay
at this funeral and be sad,
instead of going on a crazy adventure
to find our dead friend's secret treasure?
Do you have any idea
how insane you all sound?
Oh, I get it.
You just don't wanna be here.
No, that's not it.
Herb clearly wanted us to do this,
as a family.
Who cares what he wanted?
He doesn't, because he's dead.
And we all know he hated your guts.
Yeah. He was my best friend
and he died hating me
and nothing I do is gonna change that,
but herb left you that disk
because he wanted us to find his gold.
If we can honor herb's last wish,
then that's something.
I don't know what, but it's something.
- Okay. For herb.
- Fine.
- Shotgun!
- Everyone knows you can't call shotgun
- before you see the car!
- My turn! Get out of the way!
Brad, hang on one second.
Your mom wasn't redheaded twins, right?
Hi, Henry winkler.
I loved you in that one episode
of law & order: Svu.
Oh, thank you.
How would you like
to narrate a documentary for...
Hey, listen, I am so flattered,
but today is about herb,
so let's respect that.
Oh, god, I... I'm so sorry.
I'll let you get back to your business.
Hey, winkly! Oh, such a shame, isn't it?
About our friend herb?
It really burns my brisket
that some people would turn a funeral
into some kind of schmoozefest.
Yeah. I know.
Those other people are the worst.
I bet that woman barely knew herb.
Anyway, hi, I'm Henry.
I used to volunteer with herb
at habitat for humanity.
Or as we like to call it,
herbitat for henranity. Ha-ha-ha.
We spent most of the day working
on that name,
and only part of the day building
but, still, we helped some people.
- How did you know herb?
- We also volunteered at a, uh,
soup plantation... kitchen! Soup kitchen!
Uh, whichever one is the good one.
What? I never knew you did that.
Princess Carolyn, please elaborate.
Oh, hey, Mr. Peanutbutter, why don't you
talk about how you knew herb?
Oh, I never met the guy.
I'm just here to schmooze.
Tell us about your thing, though,
it sounds fascinating.
Ooh. Everyone, gather round
and listen to Princess Carolyn's story.
Okay.
Wow, herb kept all this old stuff.
He sure did.
Look, one of those answering machines
with tapes.
Mr. Kazzaz,
this is Manny from pep boys.
We fixed the brakes on your car,
you can pick it up tomorrow.
Just to reiterate,
your brakes are in great shape
and shouldn't give you any more trouble.
Unless, of course,
someone intentionally cut them,
but why would anyone do that?
I'm sorry, I'm rambling.
Probably because I'm such a big fan.
Horsin' around was a goddamn riot!
I especially loved those kids.
You know, wasn't so crazy
about the horse, though...
Message deleted.
Hmm. How curious.
How could you like
horsin' around but not like the horse?
That's like watching castle
but hating castles.
I mean, I've never seen it.
I assume it's about castles.
Wow! Look at all these
old 20th century relics.
- How did you get here?
- I was in your trunk.
Now I'm in outer space.
Todd, cut it out
with your childish high jinks.
Yeah, get out of here, dweeb.
Whoa, whoa, can't I help?
Here's 10 bucks. There's a squirt machine
by the garage. Get us five cans.
You got it. I won't let you down.
Ooh-hee-ooh-ha! Oh, no!
Your mom, was her name Karen?
- Can we drop it?
- Something with a k?
Her name is Nora. You know,
my parents got a divorce because of you.
Nora? I don't know.
I banged so many chicks in the '805.
Okay, Todd, you can do this.
Five squirts.
You just need to take this money
and put it in that machine.
This... wait, what?
What happened to the $10?
No! Wind! Be cool!
Hey! That's mine!
Why does this always happen to me?
Looks like herb set up a password.
Oh, this is easy. Try "bojack."
- No. Didn't work.
- "Bojack-bff"?
"Bojack-i-forgive-you"?
Well, I'm out of ideas.
Hmm.
I'm just, like, so mad.
Well, you should be.
You're on the show that fired herb kazzaz.
Tell me, what are the writers doing
to my baby? Are they killing it?
Are they putting my baby into a car,
then driving the car into a lake?
Topical! I still got it!
They keep giving the best story lines
to Sarah Lynn.
I haven't gotten
a single very special episode.
When am I gonna learn
about drunk driving?
Don't worry so much.
It's my legacy they're crapping all over.
You're gonna come out of this
smelling like a Daisy.
You're too good
for this TV stuff, anyway.
You're a real actress,
you should be doing theater.
Hold on.
Hey, joelle.
Wanna go to the mall this weekend?
Don't you have any friends
your own age from school?
No. My mom's boyfriend home-schools me.
He's a photographer.
I'm going to the Lilith fair this weekend
to support female solidarity.
- So scram!
- Oh.
Hey, be nicer to Sarah Lynn, will you?
She didn't choose this life.
Remember this word: Family.
Okay? You two are family,
whether you like it or not,
and that's the most important thing. You
listening? What's the most important thing?
Family. It's family. I get it.
I've got it! The password is
"password."
It worked!
Good thinking, joelle.
So in that memory,
were you British or American?
The disk just has just one file on it,
it's, uh...
It's the address of a storage locker
in Van nuys.
A storage locker? Ugh.
This treasure hunt sucks.
At long last, can you keep down the noise,
keep down the funk?
If tap dancing was gonna be a cool thing,
it would have caught on by now!
And when the mayor gave us
the key to the city,
herb said, "volunteering isn't about keys.
It's about people."
- How touching.
- Good story.
- Who are you again?
- Wow, that was touching.
A story that could never be topped.
Or could it?
Princess Carolyn, sing us another song
in the key of kazzaz.
You clearly knew the man so well.
Please tell us another story
but with even more details.
Yes. That's a great idea, Mr. Dog-man.
Tell us another story, pink cat lady.
Story, story!
Come on, everybody.
What is this, a funeral?
Story, story, story!
Well, you blew it again.
You really are a dweeb.
Don't say that.
Whoa, who are you?
Some kind of magical trash troll?
No. I'm a janitor.
But I was clearing out
some of the old stages,
and I found this transformation chamber.
Looks like a bunch of old junk.
Let me tell you a story.
Back in the '905, the biggest dweeb
of them all was Steve urkel.
Oh, yeah.
It was so funny how he never knew
whether or not he did that.
Right.
Well, nerdy Steve urkel invented a machine
that transformed him
into the debonair Stefan urquelle.
Mr. Janitor, you're standing next
to machine right now.
Yes. That's why I brought it up.
Now, this is just a prop.
But it represents a very powerful idea.
So if I go through that magic machine,
I'll become cool and confident?
No, it's a... it's a prop. I just said...
- I feel different.
- Now, son...
Todd? Who's Todd?
My name's toad. Toad chavay.
And I gotta get my bubble on.
Machine? Squirt me. Hiyah!
That'll do, machine.
Hmm.
Look at all this
horsin' around fan correspondence
herb received in the post. Capital!
Guys.
Someone already got
to herb's gold.
Oh, shit.
There's a bunch of fur in here.
It's bear fur.
I can tell. My stepdad was a bear.
Herb's nurse is a bear.
You think she knew about this gold?
Hey, listen to this letter.
I think it might be a clue.
Ahem. "Dear herb,
just finished reading your novel.
It's phenomenal.
I'm jealous. I wish I wrote it.
Sincerely, Henry winkler,
the guy from that one episode
of law & order: Svu."
Herb wrote a novel?
You look thin. Did you get into crossfit?
No, Sarah Lynn, I'm dying.
Whatever it is, it is super slimming.
I am for totes jeal over here.
It's rectal cancer.
Ew! Some of us are eating.
Look, ahem, the reason I called you
is because I need a favor.
Want me to leak a nude pic for charity?
I want you to sober up.
First of all, rude. Second, gross.
And third, why?
I have a very important job for you,
but if you're zonked out all the time,
I'm not sure I can trust you
with the responsibility.
No! I can do it! I'll get clean tomorrow.
I said tomorrow, right?
I've been working on this novel.
I wanna be remembered for something.
All I ever did was that stupid sitcom
that got ripped away from me.
But now, with this book,
I have something good.
I'm telling you, this book is gold.
- It's my kazzaz-terpiece.
- Whoa.
I want you to make sure
it gets published after I die.
You can count on me.
To life, huh? It'll kill you.
Oh, my god, the gold is his manuscript.
Herb made me promise
to get it published after he died.
And you're just remembering this now?
Yeah, I'm remembering a lot of stuff.
The ketamine's wearing off.
Oh, my god, you were the other kid
on horsin' around.
That's why you've been following us
around all day.
So no one's read this book
except for Henry winkler
- and now the book is missing?
- He must have been waiting for herb to die
so he could steal the book
and publish it himself.
But then when the cancer went
into remission...
Oh, my god.
Guys, I don't think
that car crash was an accident.
I think herb might have been murdered!
What's going on?
Something about a merger?
My name's toad, baby.
Mmm. Mwah. Yeah.
Coolsville, daddy-o.
Oh, iookie here. Unh.
Yeah.
Yo! That's my bike!
Oops. Did I do that?
Damn. I know I should be mad,
but that guy's just so cool.
And when the river finally stopped,
herb went over
to a poor little ottawan boy
and he said, "son, you have water now."
You know, a lot of people go their
whole lives and they never give a damn.
But herb? He gave those beavers a dam.
That was beautiful.
You clearly had a special relationship.
We were gonna sprinkle herb
over the ocean,
but his resting place should be
some place meaningful, don't you think?
Why don't you take this up to Ottawa
and spread his ashes there.
And make sure you take a video,
and I'll e-mail blast it to everyone here.
So we can always remember
your great friendship.
Everybody, stop!
Henry winkler is a stone-cold killer!
What? I'm not a killer.
Unless you mean killer of gloom,
because I bring joy everywhere I go.
Did you mean "killer of gloom
because I bring joy everywhere I go"?
You know that's not what I meant.
You murdered herb so you could
publish his book under your own name.
But we're not gonna let you steal
his legacy, Henry winkler.
I was afraid this would happen.
- Oh, no, he's got a gun!
- Oh, no!
What?
No, I have herb's book.
I didn't kill herb,
but I did steal his manuscript.
- So that I could burn it.
- What?
Because it's terrible.
Well, I'll see for myself.
"The air in 18305 California was fragrant
with the flowers of laughter
and the smoke of adventure.“
- what?
- Huh.
After he died, Tina and I agreed
we couldn't let the book get published.
It would have turned herb
into a laughingstock.
"The carpenter's boy was a hungry boy.
Hungry for crumpets.
But also hungry, dot, dot, dot, for life."
He literally wrote out "dot, dot, dot."
I know there's no accounting for taste,
but come on.
He's right. Herb wanted a legacy,
but he already has one.
People loved horsin' around.
This would only ruin that.
I'm sorry I accused you of murder,
American TV legend Henry winkler.
No need to apologize.
You ascribed a mystery to herb's death
to give it meaning.
But there is no meaning in death.
That's why it's so terrifying.
It was just easier to believe
that you killed him for his book
than believe that he just died
for nothing.
There is no shame in dying for nothing.
That's why most people die.
I just wanted to fix things somehow.
I'm sorry, horse guy, but you can't.
Wow, heady stuff.
But let's not get distracted
from what a true friend
Princess Carolyn is.
Don't forget the ashes, Princess Carolyn.
Fantastic.
Hey. Special delivery.
Courtesy of the toad-man.
Thanks. Hey, why'd you roll up
your sleeves like that? You look weird.
Oh, I, uh...
Well, you know, I was...
I was trying out a new look.
It was... it was a dumb idea.
Yup. Whoa! Oh, no!
Ow. Ow!
- Here's your squirt, sir.
- Thank you.
And if that happens, I want you
to take care of each other.
No matter what,
we're going to stick together.
- Congratulations!
- Hey, good job.
- You've got a goddamn hit on your hands.
- Anyone got coke?
Abc sent us limousines
to take us to the wrap party.
I'm scared. I've never been in a limo.
Don't worry. We'll take care of you.
- Seriously, no one has coke?
- Let's go.
You don't wanna go to the party?
No.
Hey, we never got a chance
to walk around the lot.
Wanna check out that water tank
where they filmed the love boat?
Are you kidding? I've always wanted
to get tanked in a tank.
- Quiet. Be careful. Ow.
- Oh, okay, okay.
You ready?
- Whoa. What?
- What...? The water's only two inches deep.
Well, that's Hollywood for you.
Are you scared at all?
That if the show takes off,
everything's going to change?
Heh, heh. No, I'm not scared, bj.
The future is bright.
Just look at it.
J“ back in the '905 j“
j“ I was in a very famous TV show j“
-j' I'm bojack the horse j“
-j' bojack! J'
j“ bojack the horse
don't act like you don't know j“
j' and I'm trying to hold onto my past j'
j“ it's been so long
I don't think I'm gonna last j“
j“ I guess I was trying
to make you understand j“
j' that I'm a horse and a man j
j' or I'm more man than a horse j'
j” bojack! J'
boxer versus raptor.