- Huh?
- 0h, uh, it's a pet name.
I don't have actual honey.
Diane!
Hey, Mr. Peanutbutter. Mwah.
Bojack horseman!
- Put her there!
- That's all right.
I'm gonna get that handshake.
No, you're not.
Since when am I honey?
Since now.
I made up the nickname
while you were back east.
Yeah, really? You made up
calling someone honey?
Uh, I do believe so. Yes.
Hey, why don't we give
bojack a ride?
That's okay.
Todd's supposed to pick me up.
Where is he?
First day, huh?
Well, stick with me.
You're gonna be just fi...
Probably just forgot,
the lazy bum.
Hey, I'll take the ride
as long as it's not as bumpy
as that pilot's landing.
That was seriously very scary.
- Hey...
- I'm just glad you were there,
because I really would have
freaked out by myself.
Be stiller, my beating heart.
Stiller crazy
after all these years.
Did I miss something funny?
- I love funny somethings.
- No, we were just laughing
about this Ben stiller article
from the plane.
Ooh, he is the best.
- What did it say?
- You wouldn't get it.
Either you read hemisphere's
magazine, or you don't.
Hey, I might be crazy, because
this is such a dumb question,
and I'm embarrassed to even ask,
but do I have anything to worry
about with you and Diane?
What?
Get out of here.
I got to say, bojack,
that is a relief.
Ho-ho! Whoo!
Hey, do you guys
want to grab dinner?
Or at least some road sodas,
so I don't have
to go through the ordeal
of sobering up and then having
to get drunk all over again?
Oh, I actually already made
special plans
for just the two of us.
Oh, come on.
You're the one
who's always saying
you want to hang out
with bojack more,
and how it's weird that bojack
never returns your calls,
and how I should
hang up the phone
because maybe bojack's
trying to call you right now.
Uh, okay.
I guess we can make this work.
Oh.
Oh, man.
Remember that guy in 34-8?
Do I? Can't stop
remembering him.
Uh, hey.
Diane and I have memories too.
This place reminds me
of a Cliffside meal we had
one romantic vacay to cabo.
Boring. I wasn't there.
Can we keep this
general interests?
Well, here's to a meal
we're all here for.
Mmm.
Oh, oh. Ew.
There's something in my food.
Ah, crap.
Someone get the manager.
No, no, no. Wait.
It's supposed to be in there.
Welcome home, honey.
I got you a d pendant,
because I am d-pendant on you.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. Real... real cute.
- A d for dog.
- It's for Diane.
This is the sweetest choking
hazard anyone's ever given me.
Mwah.
Well, how about some champagne
for the happy couple.
Waiter, get me a bottle of dom
to keep with the trend
of sweet d gifts.
You're too kind,
but everyone knows you go off
menu for the good stuff.
Yes, get me your most expensive
bottle from the back.
Perhaps a 1922-ish heidsieck
diamant bleu?
A toast on me
to Diane and Mr. Peanutbutter.
I'd like a round of drinks
for everyone.
Off the menu, of course.
Bojack, folks. What a sport.
And while we're all
in giving moods,
I'd like to buy you all an Xbox,
courtesy of me.
Wow. You guys don't
have to do this.
Look, I could happily
go down this petty road
of raising and re-raising
one another.
Please do!
But I'd instead
like to highlight the fact
that Mr. Peanutbutter's
ripping off my toast
the same way he ripped off
my entire career.
Uh, we prefer gifts
over observations.
Okay. Well, here's something
I didn't rip off.
This brand-new helicopter
I just bought.
Whoo-whoo! Who wants a ride
in the chopper?
Okay, guys. This has been fun,
and also an offensive display
of extravagant wealth,
but maybe we should
call it a night.
What's the rush?
Because I just bought
the restaurant,
and we can stay
as long as we want.
Hey, you. I own you now.
Do a dance.
Oops.
Oh, no. Hey, sorry, bud.
- It's all yours.
- Please, you first.
Apparently we both
like to be clean.
I love being clean.
That's so coincidental.
- I'm Todd.
- Klaus.
Look, I know you're new here,
but we have a lot in common:
Being white, into cleansing.
I think you'd enjoy hanging out
with me and the gang.
When you say "the gang,"
do you mean a gang?
Check this out.
If you want to lift weights,
we got great yard connecfions.
If you like toilet wine,
we spent the past 20 years
perfecting pruno.
The Aryan nation is number one
for a reason.
Never thought I'd say this,
but you put a pretty good
spin on Nazis.
Hey, tell you what.
Drop by our party tomorrow.
Shoot the shit with the guys,
mostly about Jews,
and make up your own mind.
Until then, take my card.
Whoa. Uh, where were you
keeping that card?
45, 46,
guys, can we give this thing
a rest?
Rest? Why rest? I'm not tired.
I'm twice as not tired.
Or d, sex and candy?
Bojack!
Todd, where the hell
have you been?
I had to carpool home
from the airport
like a goddamn environmentalist.
I'm sorry,
but I'm in jail, dude.
Well, you called the right
person, because I need your help
and you're my phone-a-friend.
Marie curie won nobel prizes
in which two sciences?
A, chemistry and physics.
- B, biology and physics...
- Oh, b! The answer's b!
- It's a!
- Damn it, Todd!
This was life or death.
Same with me.
The bail's set at 50 bucks.
I'll be here wa...
Yes! I am the champion
of the games!
Did you see that, Diane?
Diane?
You win, old friend.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to take
my girlfriend to bed.
We're still out?
Night, bojack.
Good night, Diane.
Give me a bottle of something
to help me forget my problems.
Ooh, maybe not that strong.
What is this, breakfast?
Yeah, that's about right.
Well, that worked effectively.
It's a Holly-who-done-it
as police are scrambling
to figure out
who stole the d from
the famed Hollywood sign.
- Holly-what?
- All of tinseltown 's
at defcon 5 until their
diabolically displaced d
is demonstrably displayed
once more.
Can we cool it
with the alliteration?
Who wrote this copy?
Randy, I'm looking at you.
Weird.
Weirder.
Why the hell would I steal
a giant d?
Ding-dong! It's Diane.
D... d... damn!
Meanwhile, local authorities
are already investigating
several suspects.
David duchovny,
dick Van dyke, dmx,
and of course Dane cook,
who we all know is a thief.
Hey, d-voted memoirist.
I can't work on the book today.
Too ill. Cough.
Are you ill, or hung-over?
Because instead of coughing
you just said the word cough.
Plus you left me along,
drunken voicemail last night.
Ooh, was it bad?
It was mostly a lot of wheezing,
as if you were
climbing something,
followed by the sounds
of dismantling metal,
and then grunting like you were
dragging something heavy
at least a few miles.
I didn't say anything
incriminating, did I?
As incriminating
as that question? No.
Good. Well, just as
a general rule,
you probably shouldn't
be listening
to any voicemails
I leave after...
- What time do I start drinking?
- Noon?
- Yup. See you later.
- But we had an appointment.
What's that? An actor flaking
on an obligation?
- Welcome to Hollywood.
- I think you mean hollywoo.
Did you see? Someone stole the d
off the sign.
Cough, cough, cough,
cough, cough.
cough, door slam.
What is it, bojack?
You know, I'm tied up
with all my deans today.
Kane, Norris, winters,
and koontz,
all being questioned by police.
It was me. I stole the d.
- What?
- Now be a good agent
and make this not my problem.
How did you even...?
You know, your scandal-to-work
ratio is, like, five to one.
Look, I need to get rid
of this before Diane sees it.
Why do you
care if dia... oh, fish.
Are you in love
with your biographer?
What?
Get out of here.
You stole the d for Diane.
Unbelievable.
Yeah, I don't know.
The d might be for David,
because apparently
when I was drunk,
I printed out a bunch
of pictures of David boreanaz.
Yeah. You did that.
Look, I'll keep your little
crush busy long enough
for you to get rid
of the contraband,
but the next three weddings
I'm invited to,
you're my date, dummy.
Since when to women your age
get invited to weddings?
I have a lot
of nieces and nephews!
Well, you pulled it off,
you deviant.
Get it? D-viant?
- I got it.
- Tell me,
how are you gonna complete
your giant bracelet?
With the chain-link fence
from dodger's stadium?
No. How'd you figure out
it was me?
Oh, how did I figure it out?
Well, I just followed the clues,
used deduction, puzzle-solving,
a little bit of forensics,
and also, what did I do?
Oh, I listened to the voicemail
you left me
saying you were stealing the d
because of Diane
so I could, and I quote,
"suck your d."
Stop leaving voicemails!
Admit it!
You like my girlfriend.
Oh, come on. I mean,
am I attracted to her? Sure.
Do my days feel better
when I'm around her? Yeah.
Does she get me in ways
no woman ever has? Indubitably.
Do I fantasize about her?
Yes, but only in two positions.
Look, am I the kind of guy
who would try to steal
someone else's girlfriend?
Sure, of course,
but do I like her?
The answer's no.
You have nothing to worry about.
I'll cut you a deal.
I help you get rid of that d,
and you never talk
to Diane again.
Well, I have to talk to her,
because she's writing my book.
Okay, but just don't
pursue her romantically?
- Deal.
- Ha!
- I knew I'd get that handshake.
- I regret this already.
Spread them wide, ladies.
This is a random cavity search.
Whoa! Buy a guy a drink first.
Did we just say that...
- Oh!
- At the same time?
Look, I saw you talking
to Klaus in the shower.
Now, the Aryan's are good guys.
Don't get me wrong.
But I don't know
if you're gonna get
the right attention over there.
Uh, I'd hate to get lost
in a shop that big.
Now we can't
offer you the works,
but in the Latin kings,
you'll be a star.
We're number two,
and that means we try harder.
Am I really being courted
by two gangs?
Oh, I feel like
the belle of the ball.
So, this is the shapeless
biographer
I've heard so much about.
We've met several times.
Did you just call me here
to insult me?
-What is your secret, lady?
I mean, how do you get
two grown men fighting over you
like a foul ball
at a football game?
First of all, football doesn't
have foul balls.
Ugh, sports.
Second of all,
nobody's fighting over me.
Open your eyes.
Bojack's clearly
in love with you.
Wha...?
Get out of here!
Get out of here?
Why would I get out of here?
You get out of here.
This is my office.
I get the army men are police,
but what's the mustard packet
again?
Oh, that's just
a mustard packet.
- It's left over from lunch.
- Oh.
Well, can we move it
off the table?
No. I still might want it later.
Good call.
So how do we get the d from here
all the way up to here?
What with all these cops
and mustards,
- it's gonna be a pickle.
- Oh, no.
The pickle's a SWAT Van,
but I see your point.
Might be easier to just ditch
the evidence. But how?
- I... I don't know.
You think these coffees
would get the juices flowing.
Well, they do have Bailey's
in them.
Is that why I feel drunk?
Because I've had, like,
seven or eight coffees.
I mean, I admit,
it's been bad for ideas,
but it's been great
for camaraderie.
Couldn't agree more.
Ooh, hey. What time is it?
I probably need
to move my helicopter.
It's in a two-hour zone.
You beautiful bastard,
that's it!
We can pick up the d with your
chopper, fly it out of here,
and then dump it
out into the ocean.
Stupendous!
Take that, the ocean.
- What now, Todd?
- Listen.
So, kind of landed myself in a
two-dates-to-the-prom situation.
The dates being prison gangs
and the prom being a jump-in,
so do you remember how you got
out of the same jam
on horsin'around?
Ah, a classic conundrum.
Well, I recall one time
on Mr. Peanutbutter's house...
I think he's talking to me, pal.
You know, the guy whose show
invented the
two-dates-to-the-prom story.
You may have invented it, but
I think our show perfected it.
The only thing
you ever perfected
- was stealing my thunder.
- Stealing your thunder, eh?
Now you're even stealing
the words I'm saying.
You know, it's tough.
I agree with the Latin kings
on social issues,
but fiscally
I'm more of an Aryan.
Well, juggling both
never ends well.
Mr. Peanutbutter,
anything to contribute?
He's just staring blankly now.
Stealing your thunder.
You could also just
bail me out of here, as I said.
- It's only 50 bucks...
- Got to go, pal.
Hope it's a magical night.
All right,
you ready for the plan?
Oh, yeah.
But we are gonna need
a big distraction
to keep the eyes off the skies.
You leave that to me.
Whoa, wait.
You had a lot to drink.
You better have a cup of coffee.
Who loves you, people?
Look this way, news media.
A celebrity is throwing away
his hard-earned cash.
Everyone pay attention to me.
Oh, it's only
one-dollar bills, folks.
Don't bother.
No, it's still free,
spendable money.
This is a huge story.
Dollars are like the new penny.
Yeah. Cash is for poor people.
What is wrong with you bozos?
Just riot over
the damn money already.
Well, nothing to see here,
I guess.
J“ ooh, ooh j“
whoa!
J“ Jesus Christ, my ankle j"
oh, my god.
American singer-songwriter
Beyoncé is hurt.
Somebody help her!
Ring the alarm.
Irreplaceable pop icon
and independent woman
Beyoncé has been injured.
What more can you give us?
Details are sketchy
at this point,
but we do know
Beyoncé is a survivor,
and presumably
she will keep on surviving.
- But what happened?
- Well, Tom,
I'm being told she fell
on all the single dollars.
- All the single dollars?
- All the single dollars.
All the single dollars?
- Bills, bills, bills.
We promise to provide live,
unflinching coverage
of this harrowing ordeal
of a star gone
from dangerously in love
to dangerously in peril.
Don't stop watching.
Mr. Peanutbutter, take her home.
Doctors have confirmed
that Beyoncé will never
perform again.
This just in. A break in
the story of the hollywoo heist.
We now go live to the house
of Mr. Peanutbutter,
star of
Mr. Peanutbutter's house.
Ah, jeez.
What did that idiot do?
Ladies and gentlemen
of the press,
I, and I alone, stole the d
from the hollywoo sign.
Just tell us, why'd you do it?
Oh, I'll tell you why.
I did it all
for my girlfriend, Diane.
Aww.
Son of a bitch.
That literal son of a bitch.
If you're joining us,
Mr. Peanutbutter has confessed
to stealing the d
for his girlfriend Diane
in what many are calling
the most romantic gesture
in the history of romance
and gestures.
We now await
the I.A.P.D.'S move.
The day they make love a crime
is the day I turn in my badge.
And here's our lady
of the hour now, Diane.
Diane! What do you think?
Wow, Mr. Peanutbutter,
uh, it's kind of a lot.
I don't really like
to be on camera.
And?
Do you love anything or anyone?
I got to go.
We 'ii talk about it later.
J'oohj'
on, my Todd.
You look... you look beautiful,
homes.
What? This old thing?
The guards made me wear it.
Yeah, well, it suits you.
You're an Autumn, bro.
Ahh.
It's good, right?
Come meet my boy, sanfiago.
Uh, you know,
I'll... I'll be right back.
I... I left my cot unmade.
Ooh, watch it.
Oh, sorry I'm late.
Hope you didn't think I was
pulling an Anne frank on you.
Good one.
Can you believe it?
I was double-crossed
by the one man
I assumed was too stupid
to even single-cross.
What? I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I do have a life outside of you,
you know.
Mr. Peanutbutter took my d
and gave it to Diane.
Once again, he completely
ripped me off.
Oh, right. That whole thing.
Just a minute, Cate.
Look, you may have come up
with a log line,
but he's the one
who sold the pitch.
This is more on brand for him
than it is for you.
- What do you mean?
- Desecrated a major landmark
in a drunken stupor,
that's a bojack horseman thing.
But stealing it
for your girlfriend
as a grand display of affection?
That's Mr. Peanutbutter.
You're right.
It's Mr. Peanutbutter all over.
It's the kind of bold,
romantic gesture
they base movies on.
Actually, that's not a bad idea.
Laura? Check if anyone's
bought the rights yet.
Can we keep this about me,
please?
Even if he stole
your stealing of the d,
what he made his was telling
Diane how he felt
from his heart.
You could never say it to me,
and you still
can't say it to her.
That's not true.
I can express feelings.
Nothing on the outside.
Nothing on the inside.
Look, I got to bounce.
Quick question, though.
Would you see Cate blanchett
in a movie about Eva braun?
Why are you wasting my time
with this?
Of course I would. Who wouldn't?
And that's why Eva braun
was like the fifth beatle
of the third reich.
Wow. I never knew Neo-Nazis
were so interested in Nazis.
You got some great moves, Todd.
You dance like a white man,
and I love it.
Hey, no disrespect,
but I got a few chess pieces
I forgot need whittling.
Oh, excuse me.
Oh, thank god you're back.
I was getting nervous that
you left me for another gang.
If that happened,
I'd have to kill you.
Thank you for rescheduling
given your recent, uh,
everything.
Yeah. That was really something.
I guess he makes
your heart stand stiller?
Yeah, but for some reason
the jury's stiller out
on how I feel about it.
Well, that's because
it wasn't for you.
That wasn't a Diane thing.
It was a Mr. Peanutbutter thing.
Well, what would be
a Diane thing?
A Diane thing would be
something that shows
he really knows you,
like giving you an iPod loaded
with all your favorite podcasts,
or a practical houseplant,
or surprising you
with a bound album
of photos and emails he saved.
That's... that's what the Diane
I know would want.
What are you saying to me?
Just that you should be
with someone who knows you.
Yeah? Like who?
|...
Whoa, were we... were we taping?
Um, okay.
Uh, you want to hear
my Andy dick story?
It's a doozie.
All we ask for is 10%
of anything pilfered.
Drugs, cigarettes.
I mean, that's the standard
gang rate.
Hey, I got to go, uh,
do a prison thing.
That sounds legitimate.
We are in prison, after all.
Whew. Hey.
White people, right?
Todd? Why in the name
of pat Buchanan
are you dressed
like a Latin king?
- Uh, what...
- What the hell, bro?
- Are you playing both sides?
- Look, guys,
I didn't want to choose between
you because I like you both.
Look, in fact, if you just
took the time
to get to know each other
the way you did me,
I think you'd agree
we don't need gangs anymore
because, deep down,
we're all just people.
What do you say?
This just in.
A standoff at the super Max
has turned into
a full-on race war.
But first, america has fallen
in love with hollywoo it-couple,
Mr. Peanutbutter and Diane...
Diane? Is that you?
Hey. It's, um, me.
Look, uh, things got
a bit weird earlier,
so I... I want to make sure
that we're still on for tomorrow
to talk about the time
I sneezed on Marisa tomei.
I'm really sorry about before.
I know the d was overkill,
so I got you something
more personal.
Aww.
I also wanted to just, um,
let you know
how much I appreciate you
working on this book with me.
I know I sometimes
get carried away,
but it's because
I love you so much.
You're a catch, Diane,
and I think you know
how much I love catch.
And I'm sorry if I've been
difficult in any way
during this process.
You know, it's... it's really hard
to have somebody,
I don't know, know you, I guess.
And you do, uh, know me, Diane.
We're very different,
but I think we bring out
the best in each other.
It's like you're chocolate
and I'm...
- Peanutbutter?
- What? Now see?
That was so much better
than what I was gonna say.
I was gonna say carrots.
And I know I'm not
the perfect guy.
I actually kind of hate myself
a lot of the time.
But when... when I'm with you,
I, uh, don't hate myself.
I like being around you,
and I don't know
if I ever told you that
in so many words,
so I'm telling you.
Diane, I've got an important
question to ask.
No cameras, no big spectacle.
Just me and you.
Call me back.
This was bojack, by the way.
Horseman, obviously.
Will you do me the honor...
Of becoming Mrs. Peanutbutter?
Wow. This is happening so fast.
Yes. I'll marry you.
But I'm keeping my last name.
You hear that? She said yes!
Let's kick it!
Erica, did you hear
she said yes?
Come on in here! All right!
She's not gonna call.
Get out the consolation scotch.
It's her!
Make that celebration scotch.
- What's the diff?
- It's the same scotch!
Diane! Hey, you!
Hey.
So this is weird.
I'm engaged.
Oh, wow.
To Mr. Peanutbutter?
I saw you left me a voicemail...
Delete it. It's just a drunken
recipe for bundt cake.
Not important.
Okay. I got to go.
They're about to move
the d back.
- See you tomorrow?
- Absolutely.
Well, nobody knows me like you.
Time to bring this baby home.
To think I went from flying
missions over kandahar
to this cushy crap.
I spoke too soon!
Black hawk down!
See, you guys
aren't so different.
We're free! We're free!
- Yeah!
- Freedom!
- I am free!
Oh, wow.
What a twist, huh?
And they say there's
no new stories in hollywoo.
J“ hollywoo, hollywoo j“
J“ back in the '903 j”
j“ I was in a very famous TV show j“
- j“ I'm bojack the horse j“
- I bojack j“
j“ bojack the horse,
don't act like you don't know j“
j“ and I'm trying to hold on to my past j“
j“ it's been so long
I don't think I'm gonna last j“
j“ I guess I'll just try
and make you understand j“
j“ that I'm more horse than a man j'
j“ or I'm more man than a horse j“
j“ bojack j“
boxer versus raptor.
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na!