Say when.
When.
[Woman] Yeah, you'll never
guess who's here.
Think '90$.
No, bojack horseman
from horsin'around.
No, I mean,
he got a little fatter,
but it's definitely him.
He looks really sad.
It's hilarious.
[Laughs]
Get over here now.
[Upbeat ringtone]
[Cell phone vibrates]
I told you,
I don't know where it is.
Don't put things in my butt
if you want them back.
[Phone rings]
And hold
for Princess Carolyn, please.
Thanks, Laura.
J“ when you're walking alone j”
j“ because jellicles are
and jellicles do j“
j“ jellicles do and jelli... j'
bojack,
it's your favorite agent.
Yeah, some agent,
you couldn't even get me
in the room for war horse.
There were, like,
ten horses in that movie.
I didn't need
to be the warhorse.
Listen, dummy, I want
to make sure you're all set
for your first day
with Diane tomorrow.
Is she gonna ask me
a bunch of personal questions?
The woman we're paying
to ghostwrite your memoir?
Yeah, probably.
Okay, all right,
there's no need to get...
What, catty?
Are you gonna say catty?
- I was not gonna say catty.
- Oh, what were you gonna say?
I was gonna say catty
because you're a cat.
Goodbye, bojack.
Laura, I know you're
listening. You got it, right?
Laura, do not respond to him.
Goodbye, bojack.
She got it.
[Camera shutter clicks]
[Laughter]
Oh, my god. Take another one.
Take another one.
Excuse me,
I just wanted you to know
that you ruined
someone else's night tonight,
and I hope
you have enough decency
to at least feel
a little bit crappy about it.
Excuse me?
I was actually
already in a bad mood,
but I thought maybe
for one night,
I could go out to a bar
and try to forget about myself,
but now because of you
and your friends,
I feel more self-conscious
than ever.
If we were bothering you
so much,
why didn't you just leave?
Because I didn't think
of that, and now I feel stupid.
Look, I have a right to be here.
Maybe because you're skinny
and maybe 'cause you're pretty,
you're used to getting away
with things,
but I want you to know
that your actions
have an effect on others,
and I hate you,
and you are a horrible person,
and you not understanding
that you're a horrible person
doesn't make you
less of a horrible person.
You think I'm pretty?
[Chuffs]
Well, that was
another in a long series
of regrettable life choices.
What'd you say?
I was tweeting about all
the weird stuff you do in bed.
[Funky electronic music]
- Good morning.
- Ah!
Why are you here?
I slept here.
Yeah, but why
are you still here?
Breakfast.
That better not be
my last toaster strudel.
No, there were three left.
Well, get out of here.
My memoirist is
gonna show up soon,
and I don't need you...
- What's your name?
- Pam.
I don't need you Pam-ing
up the place when she gets here.
- Hey, bojack.
- Ah! Why are you here?
- You told me to come at 9:00.
- That doesn't sound like me.
I have your email right here.
[Clears throat]
"Diane, why don't you come over
Tuesday morning at 9:00?
“Also, you should bring
this email with you
"because I might not remember it
because I just took
“a bunch of horse tranquilizers,
ha ha.
"Also, please don't put
in my book
“that I use horse tranquilizers,
ha ha.
"I just use a small dose
to help me fall asleep at night
"and then
a much, much larger dose
"to get me through the day.
“Also, I'm drunk.
"Also, I'm alone,
so alone, so, so alone.
“Please don't put that
in my book,
“book, book, book 'em, dildo.
Does it taste like magenta
in here?"
Then I think you fell asleep
on the keyboard
because it just says
the letter "b" 27 times.
That does sound like me.
Well, anyway,
this is my businessperson...
Excuse me?
Here to help me
with some business needs.
- All very above board.
- Uh, what'd you say?
No need to mention her
in the book either,
unless it's a business book.
- [Laughs]
- Ha ha, classic bojack.
Why are you here?
Oh, funny story, I'm filming
a reality show later,
so I thought I'd drop by with
the old tennis ball and chain.
That is neither funny
nor a story
nor a reason for you to drop by.
Aw, he just wanted
to come over and brag
about his reality show.
Get this, I am starring
in a pilot presentation
for a celebrity reality show.
It's pretty cutting edge, huh?
Yeah, if it's 2003.
Ha ha. Don't tell vh1 that.
Seriously, though,
please don't tell vh1 that.
We are calling it
peanutbutter and jelly.
Get it?
- Because I'm Mr. Peanutbutter.
- Okay, who's jelly?
No, no, no. It's like a peanut
butter and jelly sandwich.
It's wordplay.
You may have too forgiving
a definition
of the word "wordplay."
Well, it's a working title.
Well, it could be working
harder, and that's wordplay.
How'd you even get in here?
Your roommate let us in.
Mi casa es su casa.
And that is the last
of the toaster strudels,
and now my morning is ruined.
Could you guys
keep it down, okay?
I'm kind of on a date right now.
[Speaking Japanese] In america,
I am actually
considered very handsome.
[Giggling]
Okay, I'm gonna
go get breakfast,
and when I get back,
I want everyone out of my house
except for you and you and...
- Who are you again?
- The girl you had sex with.
Right. You definitely should
have already been gone.
[Tires screech]
I really shouldn't eat chocolate
'cause it can literally kill me.
Oh, I know.
- But I love chocolate.
- Story of my life.
[Laughter]
Hey, excuse me.
Yes, I am bojack horseman,
star of horsin'around.
Yeah, okay, I don't care.
Those are my muffins.
I'm sorry,
I... I don't understand.
Did you bring them
into the store with you?
No, but I was going to buy them.
That's the last box,
and I had dibs on them.
Really? You had dibs?
Yeah, dibs.
I just put them down
for a second
while I went to the bathroom.
Look, I don't even
want the muffins.
I was just looking at them,
but I got to say,
if you put muffins down,
they're not your muffins.
So what, I was supposed
to take them
into the bathroom with me?
You didn't even
put the muffins in a cart.
You just left them out here.
Yeah, in the produce section.
Clearly, muffins aren't supposed
to be in the produce section.
That wasn't a sign to you that
maybe someone else had dibs?
Look, I don't want to get
into a whole thing here.
Then give me the muffins.
No, 'cause maybe now
I want the muffins.
You think that because
you're a pseudo-celebrity,
normal rules don't apply to you?
Pseudo? Would you say that
to Eric mccormack?
Look, I've had a rough morning,
so I don't need...
You've had a rough morning?
I spent the last ten months...
Hey!
Sorry, wasn't listening. See ya.
You're going to regret this,
bojack horseman.
[Laughing] Oh, really?
I'm gonna regret buying muffins?
What, have they got a lot
of saturated fat in them?
Oh, man, they do have
a lot of saturated fat.
Why'd I buy these?
Man, I really regret
buying those muffins
and then eating them all
on the drive home.
Well, my date
with ayako went really well.
Thanks for asking.
I specifically didn't ask,
and I'll thank you to respect
my total lack of interest
in your personal life.
She's hilarious.
I never met a girl
who was so curious
about American bank
routing numbers.
Still not interested.
Should we get started
on the book?
What's your hurry?
What do you guys think
I should get ayako
for our 12-hour anniversary?
She wants a framed picture
of my mother's maiden name.
Okay, let's get to work.
Let's start at the beginning.
What was your childhood like?
- Normal.
- Normal?
Yeah, it was, uh, normal...
Normal childhood stuff.
Here's your omelet.
I'm sorry it's not as good
as the omelets
your secretary makes,
but then you're not married
to your secretary, are you?
Well, maybe if my secretary
also refused to get an abortion,
I would be.
Mommy, can I have an omelet?
You're the birthday boy.
Normal childhood,
and then just get right
into the big, famous part.
Look, if you're not
ready to talk, we can wait.
I am ready to talk.
Why wouldn't I want
to talk about my parents?
They're so normal. That's crazy.
You sound like
a crazy person, not me.
Stop being so crazy, crazy.
[Laughing]
Why are you calling me crazy?
Okay. Was your father...
[Upbeat ringtone]
Hold on, I got to take this.
Hello?
Hey, bojack, I've got
Princess Carolyn for you.
- It's urgent.
- Great, put her on.
Just a sec.
I'll see if she's available.
J“ when you're walking alone j”
j“ because jellicles are
and... j”
bojack, are you
watching msnbsea right now?
Great question.
Well, I didn't fall down
on my remote,
randomly changing the channel
to msnbsea
while simultaneously
crippling myself,
thus physically forcing me
to watch msnbsea, so no.
No, I'm not watching
msnbsea right now.
Yeah, well, Hamlet,
you might want to turn it on.
They're talking about you.
Ooh! Good things, I hope.
[Sighs]
Our guest via satellite
is Neal mcbeal,
a naval officer on leave
from Afghanistan.
Welcome to the program, Neal.
Thank you, Tom.
Hey, I met this guy.
All Neal wanted
when he got home...
And I emphasize,
from Afghanistan...
Was his favorite brand
of breakfast muffins.
When he went to the supermarket
and called dibs
on the last box...
Well, tell us
what happened, Neal.
Bojack horseman, from
the '90s sitcom horsin'around,
refused to respect my dibs.
Have you no shame,
bojack horseman?
Seen here sneezing
at a Christmas party.
Oh, not the sneezing pic...
Why do they always use
the sneezing picture?
In the '90s,
we laughed at your antics.
Oh, how we laughed.
"Ha, ha, ha,"
we chortled in rapturous glee.
But when you deny the dibs
called by our men and women
on the frontlines, that is
a sick joke, sir.
A sick, sick joke, indeed,
and you'll forgive me
if I chortle no longer,
for, to me, there is
nothing the least bit funny
about stealing a meal
from Neal mcbeal, the Navy seal.
[Grunting]
Wait, wait, you stole muffins
from a Navy seal?
I didn't know
he was a Navy seal.
I just thought he was
the regular kind of seal.
This is
classic Hollywood elitism.
Bojack horseman thinks that
because he was on TV,
that makes him better
than everybody.
Well, guess what, bojack,
now I'm on TV,
so now I'm better
than everybody!
That's right, Neal.
You didn't even have dibs,
you stupid sea cow.
You guys think I should call in
and set the record straight?
Bojack, these people
feed off controversy.
If you dignify the story with a
response, it's just gonna fan...
I'm now receiving word
that we've got bojack himself
on the phone.
Sorry, stopped listening.
You were ramping up
to a "yes," right?
Bojack, what you did today
was a slap in the face
of america's heroes.
Will you apologize?
Okay,
enough about america's heroes.
Can we talk about dibs?
Because he didn't
even really have dibs.
If he had legitimate dibs...
Oh, I had dibs on the muffins.
I hid them
in the produce section!
You left them totally out
in the open.
That's hiding?
[Yelling] How did you survive
in Afghanistan?
Those are my muffins!
You give me back my muffins!
[Barks]
Hey, guess what,
I can't give them back
'cause I ate them all, okay?
Dude.
Hold on, just to be clear,
since this morning,
you ate all the muffins?
Yeah, I ate them all
in one sitting
because I have no self-control
and I hate myself.
Is that what you want to hear?
Neal, was it
a small container of muffins,
like two to four muffins?
No, Tom, there were
a good deal more than that.
Can you remember exactly how
many muffins were in the box?
Yeah, there were exactly 12!
I ate 12 muffins,
and I didn't even want one!
There's your goddamn news story,
the mystery of my missing
goddamn self-respect!
[Pants]
How'd I come off?
Well, that went slightly
better than the worst
it could have possibly gone,
so hooray?
It's not even about the muffins.
Everyone is just out to get me
because I'm famous
and so well-adjusted.
Well, at least
you've got some privacy.
My boyfriend's filming
a reality show at our house.
If I want to be alone,
I have to go to the roof
because it's the only place they
don't have insurance to film.
You go on the roof?
Yeah,
just to get some work done.
Is that really weird?
No, it's adorable.
When I was a kid,
I used to climb onto the roof
with my dad
and look at the stars.
What about you?
Were you close with your father?
Happy father's day, daddy.
What is this supposed to be,
a iima bean?
It's a heart.
That's some shoddy
craftsmanship, son.
- I tried my best.
- No, you didn't.
You slacked off
and took the easy way out.
In this world, you can either
do things the easy way
or the right way.
You take a boat
from here to New York,
you gonna go around the horn
like a gentleman
or cut through the Panama canal
like some kind of democrat?
Um, the canal?
You go around the horn
the way god intended!
Uneventful.
- What?
I asked if you were close
with your father,
and you sat here in silence
for five minutes
and then said, "uneventful."
You know what, this is
a really good conversation,
and I definitely want
to keep having it,
but I just keep thinking
about the muffins thing,
so maybe we could put a pin
in this
thorough deconstruction
of my past,
so I can put that other thing
to bed before it spirals
out of con...
I had dibs!
- My dibs were on those muffins!
- Your dibs were void!
I spent a year in Afghanistan
making america safer,
and this is the thanks I get?
Really, you, specifically,
made america safer?
Well, bojack, surely,
even you would agree
that the troops are heroes.
I don't agree to that.
Maybe some of the troops are
heroes but not automatically.
I'm sure a lot
of the troops are jerks.
Most people are jerks already,
and it's not like giving
ajerk a gun and telling him
it's okay to kill people
suddenly turns that jerk
into a hero.
What?
Did you just say you think
the troops are jerks?
Oh, you took that the bad way,
didn't you?
I'm sure a lot
of the troops are jerks.
No, no, no.
- The troops are jerks?
- Oh, god.
Most people are jerks already,
and it's not like giving
a jerk a gun...
[Upbeat ringtone] Hello?
Princess Carolyn needs
to talk to you immediately.
Great, put her on.
She's actually just
getting out of a meeting.
- Can you hold for a sec?
- You called me.
J“ when you're walking alone j”
j“ because jellicles are
and jellicles do j“
j“ jellicles would
and jellicles can j“
- bojack.
- Ah!
I'm gonna level with you, honey.
This whole you hating
the troops thing is not great.
I don't hate the troops.
I just hate one specific troop.
I don't even hate him, really.
I just think that
he's wrong about the muffins.
I know, bojack...
Just like always,
you're right,
and everyone else is wrong.
But if you don't
swallow your pride,
this is never gonna let up.
- I know you're stubborn...
- I'm not stubborn.
- I'm proud.
- That's kind of the same thing.
No,
it's an important distinction.
Okay, fine. You're not stubborn.
But I'm about to tell you
something very important,
so I want you
to listen carefully.
I'm getting another call.
I'm gonna have
to put you on hold.
J“ when you're walking alone j“
j“ because jellicles are
and jellicles do j“
it is now day three
of the great bojack jerk-off...
Really?
That's the name
we came up with for this?
Who came up with that?
Was it Randy?
Did Randy come up with that?
Anyway, the former
television actor
who hates our troops
has not left his home
since his controversial remarks
on Monday
about how he hates the troops.
Bojack horseman makes me sick.
He voiced his opinion,
even though it was unpopular,
and that's the most cowardly
thing a person can do.
After we made love, he covered
himself in sheets like an arab.
At this very moment,
congress is voting
on a major education bill
that could completely
restructure the...
Joan, I'm sorry
to interrupt you,
but we've got some big news
on the bojack horseman front.
It appears that bojack's Lexus
is coming out of the garage.
This is very big news, indeed.
Any comment on bojack's
controversial remarks this week?
Uh, nope. [Tires screech]
So where are we going?
Don't worry, I've got a plan.
[Tires screech] Whoa!
Jeez.
Ayako, hey, I need you to get
me three tickets to Kyoto.
[Speaking Japanese]
You son of a bitch!
You told me you were
an obscenely rich
American entrepreneur.
You had eighty dollars
in your bank account.
Eighty!
Hey, I meant I was rich
because I have friends
like George Bailey.
[Speaking Japanese]
Who the shit is George Bailey?
Do you have any idea how much
work went into scamming you?
George Bailey!
Hello?
Well, I'm out of ideas.
We can hide out at my place
while we make a plan.
Yeah, great, just get me away
from the cameras.
Do we really need
to be filming this?
It's for my reality show.
You never know
when gold's gonna strike.
Yeah, gold doesn't strike.
That's why you never know.
Bojack, be nice.
Just pretend they're not there.
Okay. Well, I...
Could you speak up, please?
- I'd like to...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
That's too loud.
I want to fix this
as quickly as possible.
I don't care who was right
about the muffins anymore,
even though I was
definitely right.
I just want my privacy back,
so I can finish writing
my tell-all memoir, so everyone
will pay attention to me again.
I've already reached out
to the mcbeal camp.
He's willing to publicly forgive
you if you publicly apologize
and present to him
a box of muffins as a symbol
of your great admiration
for the American military
and everything they do.
But I ate the muffins.
I know. We got another box.
It's in the cupboard.
Oh, you were saving those?
I ate those too.
We've been here for ten minutes!
It's okay,
we'll get more muffins.
I'll get the muffins,
and they're on me.
I just found out
I got 80 bucks in the bank.
I'm helping! Hooray!
So where are we gonna do this?
Do I have to go on msnbsea?
No, we should do it somewhere
people will actually see it.
Oh, why don't you do it
on peanutbutter and jelly?
You can't call a show
peanutbutter and jelly
if there's no jelly.
It's a pun.
It's not a pun
if it only works one way.
Is this a necessary conversation
to be having right now?
Look, I know tempers are high,
but let's not take it out
on the great title
for my reality show,
which we all agree
is really clever.
We can edit this to make me
look smart, right?
J“ yeah j“
- j“ peanutbutter j“
- j“ come on j“
how's this look? Looks good?
- Okay.
- Marker, sound, speed.
Well, here I am, hanging out
with my good friend
bojack horseman,
enjoying each other's company,
as we often do.
Yes, this is all
very authentic and natural.
[Doorbell rings]
Oh, someone's at the door!
I will see who it is.
Wow, this is a surprise.
Neal mcbeal.
Hello, sir.
Thank you for inviting me
into your home. It is lovely.
Bojack, is there anything
you'd like to give Neal mcbeal?
Ahem.
Oh, yeah, Todd?
What the hell is this?
I tried to buy the muffins,
but my bank card got declined
for some reason.
But don't worry,
I still saved the day
because I found this bag
of stale hamburger buns.
I'm sorry?
Yeah, they're just giving them
away behind in-n-out.
Why does anybody
pay for anything?
Uh, Neal, as a token
of my admiration,
please accept this bag
of stale hamburger buns.
- What?
- Yes, hamburger buns.
It's a symbol
for how we throw our veterans
in the trash, sadly,
far too often.
I'm listening.
We send our muffins overseas,
and they come back
as stale hamburger buns,
but that doesn't mean
we should love them any less,
because in their own way,
aren't stale hamburger buns
just as good?
Mmm.
American made.
So what you're saying is,
you think I'm a hero.
Well, I don't know if I...
Say it, bojack. Say I'm a hero.
You're a hero.
The troops are all heroes,
every single one.
Great.
And I don't believe
saying that cheapens the word
and actually disrespects
those we mean to honor
by turning real people
into political pawns.
Okay, you can let go
of the bag now.
Also, I am not deeply ambivalent
about a seemingly mandated
celebration of our military
by a nation
that claims to value peace
telling our children that
violence is never the answer
while refusing to hold our own
government to the same standard.
Yeah, me neither.
I think we're in agreement here.
Furthermore, I do not find
it unbelievably appropriate
that this conversation is taking
place on reality television,
a genre which thrives on
chopping the complexities
of our era
into easily digestible chunks
of empty catchphrases.
Okay.
And finally, I don't...
Hey, look, Mr. Peanutbutter
got a bucket stuck on his head.
Guys, guys, where am I?
Can someone tell me where I am?
Hey, where'd he get
that bucket from?
Who gave him a bucket?
[Laughter]
Uh, actually, I had
another point I wanted to make.
Yeah, but who doesn't love
a dog with a bucket on his head?
Come on.
Bucket! Bucket!
[Crowd] Bucket!
Bucket! Bucket! Bucket! Bucket!
Hey, can anyone find a handle?
[Howls] [All cheer]
Oh, thank you, my friend.
You're a real hero.
Unbelievable.
What's your name, young lady?
Well, my real name's Angela,
but my friends call me jelly.
What?
Oh, my god, did we get that?
Please tell me we got that.
[Chuffs]
You want
a day-old hamburger bun?
I'm all right.
How'd it go down there?
You know what the problem is
with everybody?
They all just want to hear
what they already believe.
No one ever wants
to hear the truth.
I want to hear the truth.
I don't know if you want
to tell it, though.
What do you mean?
Mr. Normal childhood,
Mr. Uneventful father?
Look, I can write you
the standard
empty-calorie celebrity
tell-some,
if that's what
you're looking for,
but I thought you
might want more than that.
I do.
Well, then you're going
to have to open up
and give me something real.
What, you think I can't open up?
Well, I don't know
if you can or not.
You certainly haven't.
[Sighs]
Okay, from now on,
full truth, warts and all.
You're not gonna make me look
like an asshole, are you?
I don't know,
are you an asshole?
Okay, full truth, here we go.
You want to know
about my parents?
They drank a lot.
My father was a failed novelist.
My mother was the heiress to the
sugarman sugar cubes fortune,
and my dad resented her for it.
He used to make me cry with him
while listening
to Cole Porter records.
He made me build
my own tree house,
and then he tore it down
while I was at summer camp
because instead of
hearty, Christian nails,
I used screws,
which he called fancy Jew nails.
Like I said, totally normal.
J“ back in the '903 j“
j“ I was in a very famous TV show j“
- j“ I'm bojack the horse j“
- j“ bojack j“
j“ bojack the horse j“
j“ don't act like you don't know j“
j“ and I'm trying to hold on to my past j“
j“ it's been so long j“
j“ I don't think I'm gonna last j“
j“ I guess I'll just try j“
j“ and make you understand j“
j“ that I'm more horse than a man j“
j“ or I'm more man than a horse j“
j“ bojack j“
boxer versus raptor.
Jnanananananananaj'