- We're live in five minutes, folks.
- [Crew member] Make way.
Someone find out the average rainfall
in bora bora.
Thank you so much for doing this.
Hey, there are a lot of advantages to
being the girlfriend of a
big celebrity.
It's more than being an elbow
they couldn't crop out of
a red-carpet shot in us weekly.
- I've been that elbow.
- Hello, what have we here?
So you know
how the game's played, right?
I'm sure I'll pick it up.
How hard could it be?
You didn't read the treatment?
I faxed it to you.
My bad, our fax machine
isn't plugged in.
Bojack, this is our first show
and it is very important that things
run smoothly tonight.
I mean, do you even care
about this at all?
Sweetie, no. I think this is stupid
and a waste of everybody's time.
But you're my girlfriend
and I care about you.
- So I'm here.
- Okay. Break a leg.
[Vocalizing] Me, me, me. My, my, my.
Bow-wow-wow-wow.
Good boy, good boy.
Okay, this is it, everybody.
Moment of truth.
Now it's in the hands of god.
And for the next 30 minutes,
I am that god.
- I got you an iPad, ma'am.
- Oh, no thanks, Mia.
I'm still working my way through
the last 30 years of technology.
Right now I'm on palm pilot.
But you can use our second screen app
to see what viewers say
about the show as it airs.
0h, cool,
I love stupid bullshit like this. Ooh.
Oh, you just touch it.
Hello, I am mustache Todd.
Like regular Todd, but with a mustache.
Listen boo-boo, I didn't graduate first in
my class from a prestigious university,
rise through the ranks at
an elite news organization,
win a well-known award,
never ever be sick at sea
and also my name is Mia mckibben,
so that I could deal with your nonsense.
- [Grunts]
- Todd, stay out of hair and makeup.
But I like it there.
They brush my hair and tell me stories
about their weekends.
Big-nosed Todd wasn't funny,
zombie Todd wasn't funny,
pretty lady Todd wasn't funny,
and this isn't funny.
No more tomfoolery.
When it's me,
we call it "Todd-foolery."
We certainly do not call it that.
Listen up, everyone.
What you are part of tonight
is bigger than you.
It's bigger than any of us.
I expect all of you to work together.
But I also expect that one of you
will tower above the rest.
And that outstanding individual
will receive this pen.
It was through this pen that I bled
raise high the roof beam,
carpenters upon the page.
Also, it has four different colors.
Black, red, blue
and for some reason, green.
By the end of tonight,
this pen will be bestowed upon
the person most deserving.
Because nothing is more
important than television,
and no one more important than
the people who make that television.
- Now, let's get to work.
- [Ad] And five, four,
-three, two...
[J.D.] Showtime.
[Audience cheering]
[Lively music playing over speakers]
[Announcer] Live from the historic
studio 60 on the sunset strip,
jd. Salinger presents:
Hollywoo stars and celebrities,
what do they know?
Do they know things?
Let's find out!
[Howls]
Ah. All right! Here we go.
Listen to that crowd.
If they lose it this much
for Mr. Peanutbutter,
can you imagine what they're going to
do for a real celebrity?
Hey, this is Mr. Peanutbutter's show,
so be nice.
When you say nice, do you mean kind?
Or, like,
delivering a lot of sick burns,
so that people in the audience go,
"nice."
The first one. Obviously the first one.
Tonight we answer the age-old question:
"Hollywoo stars and celebrities,
what do they know?
Do they know things?
Let's find out!"
[Audience cheering]
[Music resumes]
And now our first-ever guest.
You know him from his years on
horsin ' around,
his drunk appearance on the view,
and his bestselling book,
it's bojack horseman.
[Audience cheering, then bojack chuckles]
There you are. How are you doing?
- Bojack, welcome.
- It is great to be here.
Sorry, no time for idle chit chat,
because we've entered
- the small talk round.
- The what now?
[Dramatic music plays over speakers]
Thirty seconds on the clock.
Bojack, how are you?
- Uh, flne?
- Correct.
- Did you see the game last night?
- No, I don't follow...
[Peanutbutter] Oh.
[Buzzer sounds]
Oh, so sorry.
It says here you did see the game.
[Buzzer sounds]
- What game?
- [J.D.] Ready camera one? Camera one.
You tell me.
You're the one who saw it.
- [Audience laughs]
- I don't...
[Woman screams] God, no!
[Bojack gasps]
- What the...?
- That noise means
it's time for your first
general knowledge question.
Audience, does bojack know things?
[Audience] Let's find out!
Bojack, what is the average
annual rainfall in bora bora?
- Uh, this is general knowledge?
- It's just an average we're asking for.
- I don't know, seven?
- Wrong! So wrong.
Wow, when it comes to bora bora,
maybe this celebrity should
have studied more-a more-a.
[J.d.]
Yes, Mr. Peanutbutter. Go for the kill.
- That doesn't really seem...
- [Woman] They're all dead!
I watched them die!
- What is...?
- Oh-ho. That sound means
it's time to pick your category.
"Trigonometry." "advanced physics,"
and "at the movies with Mr. Peanutbutter."
At the movies with
Mr. Peanutbutter.
Good choice. After seeing j.J. Abrams'
Star Trek reboot, did I call it:
A, “a visual feast for the senses,"
b, "a zestful lark through time
and space,"
c, "the best Zachary quinto movie
of all time,"
or d, "all of the above"?
- I'll say d?
- Ouch, the answer was a and b.
Though I would
also agree with c.
So I told Mr. Peanutbutter
I'd drive him here,
and next thing I know,
I'm an associate producer.
Stupid me. I went to Stanford.
Next time I'll just try that
thing where I'm a huge dumb-ass
who happens to be friends
with Mr. Peanutbutter.
- Yup.
- Cool.
Well, have fun watching me
win that pen.
I don't need a pen.
I can walk into any chili's with a child
under 12 and get crayons for free.
You don't get it.
If salinger gives you his pen,
that means you're worth something.
It means you're a serious person
who's going places.
Actually, you know what?
Don't worry about it. It's not for you.
[Groans]
I'm gonna go with nuclear fusion.
- [Buzzer sounds]
- Oh, the answer is Egypt.
Turn up the directional heat lamps.
Oh, yeah.
Let's really make him sweat.
Surprised you didn't get that one,
since you're an expert
when it comes to de-nile.
Quick impression. [Drinks]
"I'm not an alcoholic."
[Laughs] You love it.
Oh, yeah, pretty good one from king mutt
over here. Am I right?
You know, like king tut?
Because we're talking about Egypt?
And Mr. Peanutbutter's a mutt, so...
You suck.
I'm a yellow lab, bojack.
- You could get one thing right tonight.
- [Audience laughs]
Anyway, let's take a moment
to look at the great comments
we've been getting on
our second screen app,
now available for download.
And we're out.
Fifteen seconds, everybody.
- Hey, how am I doing?
- You're kind of being a dick.
Hey, are we at Tony roma's right now?
Because there's a lot
of ribbing going on here.
I'm not ribbing you.
I'm telling you, you're...
- And we're back in three, two...
- [Music plays]
Welcome back.
Will bojack horseman go down in show
history as our worst contestant ever?
So far, yes.
[Audience chuckling]
Wow. J.D., people are loving this show.
Wait until they see this.
Mia, get ready to drop the bomb.
[Woman] Death from above!
[Bojack gasps]
Uh-oh. That sound means it's time
to drop "da" bomb.
And yes folks, I said "da," not "the."
What I'm trying to say is,
it's a positive bomb.
Audience, let's...
[Audience] Drop da bomb!
Did you guys all practice
before the show, because...
Ladies and gentlemen, we've had
some fun with our little celebrity.
But now, let's meet our big celebrity.
- Big celebrity?
- Say hello to
- Daniel Radcliffe!
- Hi, I'm Daniel Radcliffe. Hello.
- Oh, my god! It's Daniel Radcliffe!
- [Audience cheering]
We'll find out what our big celebrity
knows right after this break.
[Bojack groans]
And we're out.
Oh, we're cooking now.
Hey, you, you're doing great.
I'm not 100 percent watching
because I'm so engrossed
in the second screen experience,
but according to
the second screen experience,
other people are loving the show.
You didn't tell me
there would be another celebrity.
Well, I had no idea that was coming
but some guy named dong-slinger-420
loved the surprise.
He said, "two dongs way up."
There was no mention of another bigger
celebrity in the document you faxed?
I couldn't read it. My fax machine
cut it into little strips.
- That sounds like a shredder.
- Well, I guess I shredded it to you.
- [iPad chimes]
- Oh, I gotta deal with this.
If I don't interact with this app
every 80 seconds,
it charges my credit card five dollars.
Love you.
[Mumbling] Ehh. Love you too.
Could you get the base
a little less pale?
- Hey, Daniel, good to see you.
- Always nice to meet a fan.
- No, sorry, I'm not... I'm an actor.
- Oh, good for you.
It's a dreadful business
but hang in there.
No, I already did hang in there.
I'm bojack horseman?
We've actually met before.
At Chris Martin's holiday party?
We stepped outside for a smoke?
- To get away from Chris Martin?
- Huh.
You opened up
about your fear of success?
I gave you some advice?
You said I was a true friend
and you would never forget me?
And you said your name
was Chadwick boseman?
- Bojack horseman.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
When you're as famous as I am,
you meet so many people.
Sorry, we need you guys back on set.
You were the second hairdresser's
assistant on the Ellen show
about five years ago.
Veronica, right?
- Yeah, that's right.
- How was your mother's party in the end?
And we're back in five, four,
three, two...
So you never say one, huh?
- Welcome back, america.
- [Man] We love you, Daniel.
[Laughs] So do I. So let's watch
our celebrities go... audience?
[All] Head to head!
How could they possibly know that?
- This is the first episode, right?
- [J.D. Laughs]
The puppets clap
when the puppetmaster pulls the strings.
Hello. Serious,
going-places Todd at your service.
Hey, look at you, all dressed up
for the dipshit awards.
You know you're not allowed
in hair and makeup.
- Are you wearing roller skates?
- I'm wearing heelys.
They're shoes with wheels,
for efficiency purposes.
- Now I can be serious faster.
- You can also go nowhere faster.
Seeing as I am a professional...
- [Buzzer sounds]
- Oh, bojack.
Another embarrassingly
wrong answer,
bringing your score down
by 80 points and 12 dollars.
Why are we playing
for both points and dollars?
- Oh, tough break, b.J. Novak!
- My name is...
Our next question is to Mr. Radcliffe.
"What color comes from
the combination of blue and yellow?"
I actually know this one.
When I was growing up,
my neighbor was a painter.
I remember visiting his flat
and watching him work.
Sometimes he would mix together
blue paint with yellow paint
and it made an entirely new color.
And that man was banksy.
And that color was green.
- Final answer.
- Correct!
You've earned
the chance to go for a spin
in our kia sportage cash grab booth.
[Audience cheering]
Oh, splendid.
And while Daniel's in the booth,
bojack, you have an essay question.
- What?
- You'll find a blue book on your podium.
"To what extent was feudalism
a cause of the French revolution?"
- Wait, are you ser... oh!
- And go!
While bojack works,
let's check out the action
-on our kia sportage cash grab booth cam.
[Audience cheers]
- Hey, champ.
- What are you doing here?
I'm trying to write an essay.
I came to ask you how you were doing
and then to tell you
you're not doing so well.
Why am I getting
the hard questions,
while boy wizard over there
just has to know colors
and literally grab cash out of thin air?
[Daniel laughs] A five! This is so easy!
I think I might be able to help you out.
Let me tell you a story.
The year was 2003
and for some reason, everyone was
playing poker all of a sudden.
A then-relevant wilmer valderrama
used to host a weekly how-do-you-do
and all the stars
came out to show off their tricks.
There was Lucy lawless, Lucy liu,
Lori laughlin, Lisa loeb,
the dog from frasier,
and at the head of the table?
Big money himself, Mr. Peanutbutter.
Whoops. Woh-oh.
I thought, "here's a rube."
[Laughs]
But lady luck had other plans.
You know what,
I got an essay to write,
so if this isn't about the precipitous
fall of the French ruling class...
But then I saw, the kid had a tell.
I feel like that story had a lot
of unnecessary details in it.
Listen. You have to pay close attention,
it's subtle,
but when he gets excited, his ears ever
so slightly flop up and give him away.
Well, that's no surprise. Guy's been
flopping upwards his whole career.
Mm-hm. Watch the ears.
[Horn blows]
Time's up, Daniel.
Whoa, looks like d to the r
to the ad to the cliffe
just won 54,000 bonus dollars.
And bojack barely got beyond
his thesis statement.
[Audience laughing]
[Clears throat]
"A continent ravaged by war,
coupled with the retreat
of the church from secular life..."
- And then it just stops?
- [Audience laughs]
Oh, that's gonna cost
you some serious pesos.
But first, it's time for
our multiple choice buzz-in round.
A buzz-in round? All right.
In is my favorite direction
in which to buzz.
Tell me, "how many oak trees are needed
to build an 18th century triple-Decker
royal Navy battle ship?
A, 75? B, 1000?
Or c, 3500?"
C! 3500!
- Um, correct.
- Uh, what?
- Uh, wow. That's, uh...
- [Mild applause]
That's actually correct.
How the hell did he know that? What else
does he know? Does he know things?
Let's find out.
Quantum tunneling.
King Magnus the second.
Miss Scarlet in the library
with the lead pipe.
Sassafras. Butterscotch! Argyle.
- Because seven eight nine.
- [Buzzes]
What an amazing run.
It looks like we've got a tied game.
Which is an exciting surprise.
- Goddamn it, throw to commercial.
- We'll be right back.
[Lively music playing over speakers]
- Hey. Horshack. What's going on?
- What's going on is I'm kicking your ass.
Yeah, you know, you're doing great,
but I'm supposed to win.
That was the deal.
Plug my movie, win money for charity.
Well, tell charity she can kiss my ass.
By the way,
your girlfriend has a stripper name.
It's not my girlfriend, it's charity.
Bojack, according to this app,
you're almost tied.
Oh, you are tied, there's a lag.
Congratulations.
Thanks. It was touch and go...
But I'm a little concerned
because it seems like
you might actually win,
but everyone on the app
is really rooting for Daniel.
People love him.
I guess he was in some movie about a
Potter or a pottery barn or something?
- Are you asking me to throw the game?
- You don't care about this game.
The only reason you're here is for me,
so maybe you could help me out?
- [Sighs] Okay.
- You know what?
You're the best, no matter
what everybody on this app says.
They say you're the worst. Especially
queefburglar69. He's their leader.
[Audience cheering]
And we're back. Contestants, I've got
a history question for both of you.
"You may or may not be familiar with a
famous racehorse named secretariat.
In what year did secretariat
win the triple crown?"
- [Buzzer sounds]
- Bojack.
Piece of cake.
Hmm?
[Sighs]
Um, 1492?
- [Audience and Daniel laughing]
- What? No, not even close.
Bojack, aren't you in a movie
about secretariat?
- How could you not know that?
- Let's just move on.
Maybe instead,
he should be in a movie
about a guy who doesn't know
anything about secretariat. [Laughs]
That would not be a good movie.
I mean, more like secre-terrible.
Damn, bojangles, you got served.
Do you know anything about secretariat?
You know he was a horse, right?
Oh, wait, did I just spoil it for you?
No wonder my wife
had to write your book for you.
Hey, yeah, you know, while we're talking
about your wife, I've got a question.
How come your wife flew
all the way to war-torn cordovia
just to get away from you?
[People murmuring]
That's not what happened.
She went to help people.
Or maybe she went to help herself
get away from her awful marriage.
[Audience gasping]
- Oh, was that too far?
- Oh-ho, you want to get into things?
- Well, I mean...
- No, no, no, let's get into things.
Let's get real.
Everybody, bojack wants to get real.
Cancel the bubble round.
Because we're getting real.
[Production assistant sighs]
Should we cut to commercial?
Would homer cut away
from odysseus's journey
just as he was being enticed
by the sirens' song?
Well, there you are.
Things are getting real out here.
Really real.
Really really really real!
[Audience member clears throat]
- Uh, I'm not sure where you're going...
- Oh, no?
You knew
where you were going with my wife
the time you pulled over
by the side of the road.
- You know, a week before we got married?
- Uh...
You want to talk about that, bojack?
You want to talk about the time when you,
my "good friend," kissed my wife?
- No!
- Yes.
Did something
exciting just happen?
Because people on the app are,
and I quote, “losing their tits."
Oh, no, no, I've stumbled on to
a cancer support message board.
Okay, how do I...?
How did you know about that?
Well, there are roadside cameras
all along the pch,
I have a few friends
in the highway patrol,
and she told me of course,
we're married!
Wait, so you've known all this time?
Now this is television. Turn on the rain.
Um, don't you think
you're pushing them too far?
I'll tell you when it's too far.
This is my art, goddamn it.
I'm j. Goddamn d.
Goddamn salinger, and I want rain!
[Thunder rumbling]
All I ever wanted was to be your friend.
And you treat me like a big joke.
You think I don't notice?
Why don't you like me?
- Mr. Peanutbutter...
- No, tell me.
- Because I'm jealous.
- Oh.
- Of what? Diane?
- No.
Of everything.
Everything comes so easy for you.
Oh, and it doesn't for you?
You're a millionaire movie star
with a girlfriend who loves you,
acting in your dream movie.
What more do you want?
What else could
the universe possibly owe you?
I want to feel good about myself.
The way you do.
And I don't know how.
I don't know if I can.
Whoa, guys, this is getting
a little heavy, don't we think?
I'm sorry, Mr. Peanutbutter.
I can't tell you how sorry I am.
Wow, um, I don't know
if I can forgive you.
But I guess we'll find out
right after this break.
[Audience cheering]
- Damn.
- Shut up.
[All cheering]
I knew it. I knew this show would
bring us to the heights of human drama
more powerfully than literature
ever dreamed.
Now somebody go out and get me
a red bull and a banana fish sandwich.
On it. It's a perfect day for a red bull.
Whoo-oh!
- Mr. Peanutbutter!
- Oh, hey Wanda.
I'm only half paying attention to
whatever you two are arguing about
but it's killer.
Now all we need is a happy ending.
I don't think we can just resolve
everything cleanly in a half-hour.
Uh, this is network television.
So resolving everything cleanly in
a half-hour is kind of what we do.
You want to host a game show where
everyone feels bad at the end?
You can get in your little car, drive to
Santa Monica and pitch it to amc.
But these people want resolution, okay?
So you get your little butt back
on that stage and you resolve.
- Uh...
- [Audience applauding]
And we're back.
You know, I did some thinking
over the break. Bojack...
[Electricity powers down]
[Audience gasps]
- What's going on?
- Oh, my god.
No! No! What's happening?
- [All chattering]
- Oh.
[Electricity powers up]
Someone unplugged the main power line
and plugged in a George foreman grill.
Panini time. Hey, who unplugged...
Todd! Goddamnit, step aside!
Mia, good work.
You saved the show.
You earned my respect and this pen.
- Oh, thank you.
- [All cheering]
Aww.
Oh, are we back? We're back!
Live television, folks.
You know, during the break,
my producers told me
I had to forgive bojack
live on the air.
[Audience booing]
But I'm my own dog.
And as my own dog, I decided
to forgive bojack live on the air!
Bring it in, buddy!
- What?
- Really?
Mr. Peanutbutter,
I applaud your forgiving nature,
but this guy kissed your wife.
Wait, bojack kissed Diane?
The only way to even the score is
if you get to kiss him.
- Wait, what?
- You're right, it makes perfect sense.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- No, it doesn't.
That way Diane and I will have
had the same experience.
It's the only way we can move past this.
[Sighs]
Well, if it helps us move past this,
I guess...
[Daniel and audience] Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
[J.d.] Cue the kiss cam.
[Love song playing over speakers]
Oh, if only I'd had a kiss cam
for catcher in the rye.
Well, just one more regret
on a long list of many.
Todd, there you are. You're missing
a pretty big moment out there.
I don't care. You said it yourself.
Without that pen, I'm totally worthless.
Not for nothing, but you were worthless
before you didn't get the pen.
I really tried this time. I guess
I'll never really amount to anything.
Well, maybe you just need
someone to believe in you.
Wow, no one's ever
fallen for that!
- What?
- You're so stupid!
You had the pen
and you just gave it to me?
Oh, I can't believe that worked.
Oh, my god, look at your stupid face.
The pen is just a symbol.
It doesn't...
Yeah, said the girl
who doesn't have a pen right now.
Unbelievable. You are the most annoying,
immature, aggravating,
irritating, crazy-making...
Oh, she was mad, all right. But kids?
That's the story of
how I met this pen.
[Laughs]
Hey, get out of hair and makeup
and give me back my pen!
I got your pen.
That means you respect me.
- No it does not.
- Viva toddfoolery!
Suck a dick, dumbshits.
- Hey! Hey, hey!
- [Blows raspberry]
[Lively music playing over speakers]
[Audience cheering]
Well, that stern but supple kiss
puts you over the top.
Bojack horseman is tonight's winner.
[Dog howls]
- Well played, jock-jam door-slam.
- [Groans]
You've earned $500,000 for charity.
You can walk away right now
or, and remember, this is for charity,
you can risk it all in
our double or nothing round.
[Audience clamoring]
I wanna risk it all!
All right. Now that's $500,000.
If you get this question right,
you double that,
a million dollars for charity.
But if you get it wrong,
the charity gets nothing
and all the money will be set on fire
live here on our studio sound stage.
Bojack, for all the marbles:
"Which famous actor
played the titular role
in the popular Harry Potter
film franchise?"
- [Audience] Oh.
- Huh.
Yeah. I don't know.
When you're as famous as I am,
you meet so many people,
it's impossible to remember them all.
Okay, I get what you're doing. Very funny.
Yeah. Oh, what is that guy's name?
You know, it's on the tip of my tongue?
Are you serious right now?
Dude, this is for charity.
- Bojack, we need an answer.
- Yeah, I don't know.
Gosh, I wanna say...
- Elijah wood?
- What?
Elijah wood?
J“ back in the '903 j”
j“ I was in a very famous TV show j“
j“ I'm bojack the horse
bojack! J“
j“ bojack the horse
don't act like you don't know j“
j“ and I'm trying to hold onto my past j“
j“ it's been so long
I don't think I'm gonna last I“
j“ I guess I was trying
to make you understand j“
j“ that I'm more horse than a man j'
j“ or I'm more man than a horse j“
j“ bojack! J'j'