And he says... he says,
"why the long face?"
And I say, “hey, buddy,
I can't help it."
You get that? Long face.
Horses have long faces.
I am a horse, my face is long.
You get it, right?
Good, good.
What about
the rock Hudson stuff?
Felt like that flew
over your heads.
Did you get that?
Keep this up, and the only
thing we're gonna get
is our money back!
Okay, okay,
it wasn't that funny.
Maybe you didn't get it.
Uh, hey, guys, guys...
Hey, let me buy you a drink.
Get cancer, jerk wad.
You've got some good material,
you really do.
The gorbachev stuff,
it's killer.
But you gotta stop asking people
if they get things.
But then who do I know
if they got it?
They'll laugh.
Why are you giving me advice?
Look, I've been doing stand-up
for a year now,
and it's the responsibility
of big shots like me
to always be looking out
for the little guy.
Let me buy you a drink.
Oh, I don't drink.
Bojack horseman.
H e rb kazazz.
Oh, god!
Goddamn it, Todd,
clean up your shit.
What am I supposed to do, okay?
You don't give me
any closet space.
Not my problem.
A better man than you
once said, and I quote,
"it's the responsibility
of little guys like you
to be looking out
for big shots like me."
Who said that?
I don't know, Jesus, ghandi,
Malcolm-Jamal Warner.
Clean up your shit! Oh!
Gloria steinem,
one of the leading lights
of modern feminism.
You will surely go down
in the annals of history
just as surely
as Lisa lampanelli
will go down in the locker room
of the Houston rockets.
Hey, bojack, settle a bet.
Are you a Zoe or a Zelda?
Don't know what that means.
Well, I was talking to Wayne.
- Who's Wayne?
- I'm Wayne.
Wayne's writing an article
about me for buzzfeed.
Buzzfeed?
What'll they think of next?
Fun fact: Wayne is also
my ex-boyfriend.
Ha! You're funny.
Pretty cool, eh, bojack?
Diane's writing a book
about you,
Wayne's writing
an article about me.
We're the same!
How could you think that
that's the same?
My book will be in libraries
for hundreds of years.
Your buzzfeed article
will be crammed
between an animated gif
of a cat falling asleep
and a list of fun facts
about legally blonde.
Ha! Classic Zoe.
I still don't know
what that means.
Well, are you familiar
with Mr. Peanutbutter's house?
Do you mean his sitcom
that coincidentally
had the exact same premise
as my sitcom?
Not the exact same.
Mr. Peanutbutter's house
featured a pair of twins,
Zoe and Zelda.
Zelda was the sunny,
fun-loving extrovert.
Look at my pumpkin,
Mr. Peanutbutter.
Pretty smile, zelly-belly.
Aww...
Whereas Zoe was the smart,
cynical introvert.
My pumpkin's throwing up
because Halloween
encourages excessive consumption
of refined sugar
at a time when obesity rates
are sky high.
Plus, Halloween costumes are
a gateway to casual racism.
Why don't I keep the knife,
zo-Bo?
J“ who's that dog? J“
j“ Mr. Peanutbutter j“
j“ knick-knack, paddywhack
give a dog a bone j“
now, was the show's acting
ham-fisted
and the writing moronic?
N-N-No?
Yes, but the zoe/zelda
paradigm rang true.
I believe everyone's
either a Zoe or a Zelda.
For example, Nixon was a Zoe
and Kennedy, a Zelda.
Al Gore, Zoe.
George w. Bush, total Zelda.
It's r2-dz and c-3po,
zooey and Emily deschanel.
So zooey's a Zoe?
No, zooey's a Zelda.
Emily's the Zoe.
What a crazy world.
So which one are you, bojack?
I think I'm... above this.
Said the Zoe.
Well, I think I'm a Zelda.
Or maybe you're
the third kind of person,
whose only function is to drain
the energy and life force
from his host organism.
Come on, bojack.
Nah, he's right.
I'm pretty much worthless.
See? You say something
to someone enough times,
and eventually,
he internalizes it.
The system works.
I don't have a job,
I don't have any prospects.
I probably won't ever finish
the rock opera I'm working on.
What?
Since when are you
working on a rock opera?
Oh, no. Why'd I ask that?
Basically, it's Tommy
by way of cirque du soleil
set in space,
with heavy erotic overtones,
and the gripping psychodrama
of a thriller
with plenty of heart
and more than a little humor.
I call it
newtopia rising, book I:
The search for a new utopia.
Bookl?
You've got me
thinking sequel here.
J“ traveling on a spaceship j”
- I'm in.
- I'm out.
J“ so far away from home j“
j” to find a new
and better place j“
j“ a planet rich with loam j“
loam? "Rich with loam?"
Yeah, it's a kind of soil.
These people are simple,
agricultural types.
On a spaceship?
J“ we learned a lot
and had some laughs I
j“ but they couldn't
make us slaves j“
j“ no! No, they couldn't
make us slaves I
J“ no! I
j“ no, they could-n-n-n't j“
J“ make u-u-u-us j“
J“ one, two j“
"slaves." just say "slaves."
J“ sla-a-a-a-a-a-aves j"
That was... and I don't
say this lightly...
Worse than a hundred
September 11ths.
Yeah, you're right.
This was stupid.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
Well, guess I'll give up
forever.
That's the spirit.
Now, you have to understand
that as a port city,
liverpool had unique access to
all aspects of American culture,
especially blues music and its
unruly nephew, rock and roll.
I thought this story was about
running into Paul McCartney
in the bathroom
at the golden globes.
It is. I thought you would
appreciate some context.
Let's skip that one
for a minute.
Tell me about Todd.
Todd? What's to tell?
Five years ago, he found his way
into one of my house parties
and never left.
And you've never asked him
anything about himself?
I've asked him to get a job,
I've asked him to move out.
With a little encouragement,
I'll bet he could
really flourish.
I mean, didn't you have anyone
who helped you
when you were just starting out?
Um, actually, no.
Todd clearly thinks
the world of you.
Todd thinks the world
of pop-tarts.
Look, I get that helping other
people is not your thing, but...
What? I let Todd live
rent-free in my stately manse.
I am his own personal
Mother Teresa.
But do you let him stay here
because you're kind
or just because you're terrified
of being alone?
That is insane!
I would love to be alone.
That is all I want.
Mmm... if that were really true,
I don't think you'd be clipping
Todd's wings all the time.
What? That's unbelievable.
Todd!
What? Clean up my shit?
Yes, but also,
I would like to...
Help you with your
dumb-ass rock opera.
- What?
- I am... supporting you.
I-I don't understand.
Oh, my god, are you dying?
No. I... think you have great
depth of untapped potential
and I wish to mentor you
in your... art.
- Really?
- Yes.
Wait, is this going to be
like that time
you promised to take me
ice skating,
and I got really excited
about the ice skating,
but then instead of ice skating,
you left me at home
so you could go
to the strip club
and then you took the strippers
ice skating?
- No.
- Then hooray!
Let's dig in. Where to start?
Okay, well, the headline is,
I hate it.
I hate everything about it.
The premise is bad
and the execution is also bad.
It's an irredeemable jumble
of shit.
Tough but fair.
Ahem.
That said, I don't see why
we can't make something
really great here.
Okay, thank you.
I'll work on that.
Are you close?
- How 'bout now?
- No!
Now?
You're not even inside of me.
Oh, god!
Did you get there?
Okay, so you know
in the second act closer
when the seekers of newtopia
are in the turbidians' dungeon
and they learn their ship
- has been destroyed?
- No.
Well, what if we move that
to the fourth act?
I have no idea
what you're talking about,
but that idea is terrible.
I hear the note.
Let me see what I can do.
J“ and that's why this planet j“
j“ su-u-u-u-u-cks j“
how can I put this?
Imagine if the holocaust
happened
every four years
like the Olympics.
I would rather that happened
than your rock opera.
That's not really a note.
In fact, none of your notes
have been notes.
I feel like you're
not even listening.
Yeah, well, you know what?
Maybe I would listen
if the turbidians
had some reason
to enter
the cave of swollen dreams
that didn't break the pact
they made in act one
with queen darneesa.
You have been listening.
Just doesn't make sense.
The turbidians
are a loyal people.
They... they wouldn't
betray their queen.
Unless...
They were working
for queen darneesa,
who gave them a potion
that would counteract
the effects of
the elixir of failed remembrance
so they could bring
the secret knowledge
from the cave back to her,
and then establish newtopia
as a vassal state
to the craterman kingdom!
Well, don't just sit there!
Get this down!
Oh, you like that.
You like daddy's good stuff?
Not especially.
Did you get there?
Okay, what if there isn't
a robot army?
I think you just
blew this thing wide open.
J“ we'll make this
our newtopia-a-a j“
- j“ up a fifth j“ - J” ah j”
j“ down a fifth j“
J“ a-a-ah j“
that was great!
This train is moving.
Let's take a break
and get lunch.
Wait, you want
to get lunch with me?
Yeah, that's right.
Is this like the time
you invited me to lunch,
but then, when I got
to the restaurant,
you texted me to tell me
you weren't coming
because you were at a strip club
"eating stripper" for lunch,
and also, it was my birthday?
Then hooray!
And that was a last time
I worked with David 0. Russell.
What's that old expression?
"Fool me once, shame on me,
but fool me twice...
Fiddle-Dee-Dee."
I do believe
that is the expression.
Ooh, hold on.
I gotta take this.
Erica, I don't have time
to be charmed to death
right now.
So how long have you been
dating Mr. Peanutbutter?
Is it serious?
I'm only asking for the article.
Better question:
How long does it take
to write a buzzfeed article?
I want to be thorough.
What? Diane, Diane,
Diane, Diane!
- Do you know what today is?
- Sunday?
It's "burritos as big as your head"
day at El taco loco!
We gotta go right now!
I thought we were going to see
the Diane arbus show
at lacma today.
You know I love Diane arbus.
I see what's happening here.
Her name is Diane,
and your name is Diane.
That's not what's happening.
I can go to the arbus show
with you, Diane.
What?
I've actually been meaning
to go myself.
Oh, man, you guys
are perfect for each other.
Why did you ever break up?
Okay, less yakking,
more snacking.
Let's go ride in the car!
Here's your steak.
- Uh, sorry.
- Mm-hmm.
You mean to tell me
that for a full year
you were on the run
from the Russian mafia?
Well, a Russian mafia.
I can't believe you never
told me any of this stuff.
I just thought you were
a dumb freeloader
who ate all my food
and played video games all day.
You should have seen me
in high school.
There was this one game,
decapathon.
I remember that game.
I was up for Dr. Decapitator
in the movie version.
They said they wanted
someone hipper,
but the part ended up
going to Robert downey.
- Junior?
- If it was junior,
I would have said, "junior."
That game basically
destroyed my life.
I flunked out of school,
my girlfriend left me.
I mean, I didn't stop playing
until my mom
threw me out of the house.
I mean, that's when
I first realized, you know,
I'm a total screw-up.
You're not a screw-up
anymore, Todd.
You're about to have
a hit rock opera on your hands.
I'm really glad you think that.
I got Princess Carolyn to invite
Virgil Van cleef
to our next rehearsal.
Who in the what Van?
Virgil Van cleef is
the biggest name in rock opera.
Okay, think of all
the great rock operas
from the last 20 years.
Okay.
He had a piece of all of them.
Wow, Todd, are you sure
we're ready for that?
Hey, you said yourself
the train is moving,
but if you think
we're not ready,
I mean, I'll listen to you.
Hey, you've done
enough listening, buddy.
Maybe it's about time
I start listening.
Well, I feel like...
Gotta take this. Hello?
Hello? Bojack horseman?
We have some very delicate
pictures you might
have an interest in not getting
into the wrong hands.
I am very happy with my current
long distance provider,
thank you.
What?
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm having lunch with my friend.
But if you just listen...
All right, gang, when Virgil Van
cleef gets here, look alive.
This could be Todd's big break,
so clap really hard
and laugh at all the jokes,
even if they're not funny,
but also, be careful,
because a lot of things
you might think are jokes
are not jokes,
so, you know, look out.
- That was not a joke.
- That was not a real laugh.
I hope you don't mind
I brought Wayne along.
- Who's Wayne?
- I'm Wayne.
I just wanted to make sure
he had everything he needs
for the big buzzfeed
cover story.
Buzzfeed is a website.
There is no cover.
Eh, "tomato," "tomato."
It's "tomato," "to-mah-to."
You say, "tomato," "to-mah-to,"
I say, "tomato," "tomato."
Oh, hey, Diane,
I got you something.
Oh, plane tickets?
Yep, to San Francisco.
That's where the arbus exhibit
is heading next.
Oh, my god.
Thanks, Mr. Peanutbutter.
Gentlemen, dazzle me.
What you're about to see
is rough, very rough.
It's a vomit pass at what
might become a rock opera.
Right now, it's set
mostly in space,
but we're not married to that.
Todd is neither a singer
nor a trained musician.
In fact, he never even
graduated high school,
he told me in confidence.
Keep all that in mind
as you give it up for Todd.
Okay, so we start in 1887
with a young Emma Goldman.
J“ no they couldn-n-n-n't
make u-u-u-us j“
j“ sla-a-a-a-a-aves j“
it needs
a third act showstopper.
I had the same note.
But in all, it's spellbinding.
All right!
Whoo!
You know, I run a small
theater in north Hollywood.
We were supposed to mount
a j.C. Superstar revival
next month, but of course,
Andrew Lloyd Webber has to be
a real hot penis
about everything.
Oh, Andy.
Fool me once, shame on you,
but teach a man to fool me,
and I'll be fooled
for the rest of my life.
Anyway, could this show
be ready to debut in six weeks?
Six weeks? Uh, damn.
Yeah, I guess so.
Marvelous! We'll schedule
an investor showcase posthaste.
In the meantime, libations!
Ah!
- Popping, what?
- This is great.
You know, just when you think
you have a person pegged,
he can still find ways
to surprise you.
Yeah, Todd really Rose
to the occasion, didn't he?
I was talking about you.
Ah, well, it was nothing.
Maybe the Zoe has
a little Zelda in him after all.
I appreciate the sentiment,
but I still think
that game is stupid.
Hey, bojack, do you realize
what this means?
I mean, if this thing's a hit,
I could finally move out.
Oh, uh, you're gonna move out?
You won't have to yell,
"hey, Todd, clean up your shit!"
Or, "Todd, why haven't you
cleaned up your shit yet?"
Or, "Todd, what was the name of
that guy from perfect strangers?
Not Bronson pinchot,
but the other one?"
Good, that's great.
That's great and good.
So good, so great.
- Just great, and also good.
- Mm-hmm.
And as you can see,
progress has been swift.
For tomorrow's
investor showcase,
we'll have choreography
and pyrotechnics for you.
This is all just
happening so fast.
I don't... I don't think
Todd is ready for this.
Todd's not ready
or you're not ready?
Don't make this about me.
I've seen what happens
when baby birds get pushed
out of the nest too soon.
It's not your fault.
I thought he was ready.
He seemed ready.
It's not... your... fault.
You're right.
In these heady times,
what Todd needs is an agent.
Ha! Ha!
- I just need you to deliver...
- Hoo! Ha!
- That third act showstopper...
- Ha!
And then we'll be
fully financed!
Todd can do it!
Todd can do anything!
- Can I get your autograph?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And another autograph,
and initial here, here,
here, and here.
- Right here?
- And the last four digits
- of your social.
- Okay.
So I think the big
third act number Virgil wants
might be a big anthem that...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, buddy, buddy,
I'm not gonna let you start
on this until we stock up
on snacks and red bull.
I do get snacky.
You think of everything.
'Scuse me, young man.
Can you hand me
that Ronnie milsap cassingle
in the 10-cent bin?
Sure thing, lady.
Oh, my god. Decapathon vii?
This just came out.
Todd, put it down.
Is this really only a dime?
If it's in there,
that's the price.
Todd, this is no time
for a relapse.
Look, okay, I'll buy it now,
but I won't play it
till after I've written
the new song.
Todd, this is a bad idea!
- Whoa!
- All sales are final.
Okay, let's see here.
I wonder if it still
smells the same.
I assure you, it still smells
like cheap plastic
and child labor.
Okay, here we go. Song time.
Or should I just play
one game now,
just to get
the creative juices flowing?
We both know that if you
play that game tonight,
you'll never leave this couch!
Ah, no, you're right, of course.
- Thank you.
- Good night.
Come on, decapathon, come on.
Oh, come on, decapathon.
Oh.
Wake up! It's the morning!
Damn it, Todd, the investor
showcase is in half an hour.
- Did you work on the song?
- Huh?
Pull yourself together, man!
Ugh! Why did the water
have to come out of your mouth?
Well, I'm awfully sorry
to have wasted your time.
I don't think our man
is going to show.
Wait!
Good god, what's happened?
He looks like he was
up all night
playing some sort of
videographic game.
He's in no condition
to debut a song.
Give the kid a chance,
Van cleef.
J“ loam, loam, loam j”
j“ and a...
Uh, little room to, uh, roam j“
j“ and on this planet
it's our home j“
j“ in space j“
rock opera?
More like "schlock flop-era."
Ugh!
J“ loam j“
enough!
Clearly, Van cleef has shown
a rare lapse in taste
and judgment.
I apologize for wasting your
time with this talentless imp.
Hey, Van cleef,
Todd may not be ready
for the high-flying world
of rock opera
or the larger world
outside of my living room couch,
but you know what?
He's a good friend.
I don't see how that's relevant.
No, of course you don't.
Maybe Todd's worse off today,
but you're worse off
in the long run,
because you're gonna die
alone and unloved,
you pompous, affected asshole!
Mon dieu! Never have I ever!
Hey, maybe don't
burn the bridge.
I could still beg
for a second chance.
Shut your mouth, Todd.
And you shut yours, Van cleef,
or I will buck it shut.
Suck a dick, dumb shits!
Oh, that damn video game.
No, it's not
the video game's fault.
I blew it.
For a second,
I actually convinced myself
I was more than
just a worthless screw-up.
Fool me once, fool me twice,
fool me chicken soup with rice.
I guess there's a reason
they don't call it
"the rock opera fun."
They call it
"the rock opera business."
Guess I won't be needing
this piece ofjunk anymore.
Hey, no. Hold on to that.
Why don't you just put it
in the living room closet?
- Really?
- In fact, from now on,
you can keep all your stuff
in the living room closet.
Thanks, bojack, for everything.
This, I will get rid of.
- What the...
- Don't look at those!
- Those are private!
- Are these the notes
you've been taking
on Mr. Peanutbutter?
It's gibberish!
Have you just been mashing keys
this whole time?
It's a... it's a work
in progress.
What's really going on here?
Look, I've been following
you two around
for the last couple weeks,
and I think it's pretty obvious
to everyone that you shouldn't
be with Mr. Peanutbutter.
You should be with me.
No, I've dated you.
Sure, you're smart
and sophisticated and cool,
but you're also mean.
What's your article
on Mr. Peanutbutter called?
The working title is,
"nine jokes from the '90s
we haven't stopped laughing at."
- I knew it!
- Come on!
Like you're not gonna
tear bojack apart in your book.
I'm not "tearing him apart."
I'm writing a nuanced portrait
of a complicated man.
Well, then, we might be
doing different things.
Mr. Peanutbutter is nice to me!
He's kind and he's generous
and he's loyal.
You know what your problem is?
You're trying to be a Zelda
but you're so obviously a Zoe.
Ugh! Don't label me.
You don't know who I am.
You can live your happy Zelda
life in this happy Zelda town
and pretend you're
a happy Zelda,
but I know you,
and this isn't you.
People don't change, Diane,
not really.
Mr. Peanutbutter's a Zelda.
He's happy and he's carefree
and he's loving,
but you and me, we 're zoes.
Yeah, I bought this earlier,
and I'd like to return it.
I don't know where
the receipt went.
I remember you.
You came in yesterday.
No problem.
We're zoes, Diane.
We 're cynical and we 're sad
and we 're mean.
Thanks for your help,
character actress
margo martindale.
I don't feel good
about what we did here, bojack.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
This never happened.
There's a darkness inside you,
and you can Bury it deep
in burritos as big as your head,
but someday soon,
that darkness is gonna come out,
and when it does,
I want you to call me.
I like that guy.
Ahh.
J“ back in the '90s j”
j“ I was in a very famous TV show j“
- j“ I'm bojack the horse j“
- I bojack j“
j“ bojack the horse j”
j“ don't act like you don't know I
j“ and I'm trying to hold on to my past j“
j“ it's been so long j“
j“ I don't think I'm gonna last j“
j“ I guess I'll just try j“
j“ and make you understand j“
j“ that I'm more horse than a man j“
j“ or I'm more man than a horse j“
j“ bojack j“
boxer versus raptor.
Jnanananananananaj'