Oh, right.
Well, just tell whoever, then.
Haaah!
Ooh!
Asshole!
Anyway, I'm off to Malibu
to see herb kazaz.
He has cancer, which,
as you know, is a whole thing.
Plus, he hates me,
so I could really use
some good news
at the end of the day.
Oh, my god.
You're going to see herb?
You must be really... nope.
Don't care. Not interested.
Okay, good talk.
Hey.
- You ready for this?
- Listen.
I want to make sure
I don't spend
any time alone with herb.
I'm bringing you
along as my buffer.
And your memoirist.
I should meet
your old best friend
before he dies of cancer.
Fine, I guess.
Just don't abandon me.
No bathroom breaks.
And don't slip out of the room
to text your fiance
a bunch of winky smileys
with hearts next to them...
Gross.
Congratulations on
the whole being engaged thing,
- by the way.
- Thanks.
It's just starting to hit me.
I'm getting married.
Thank god I don't
have to die alone.
- No offense.
- None taken.
Till you said, "no offense."
So what's the deal with you
and this guy?
You never talk about him.
Well, I kind of, maybe
stabbed him in the back.
Yeah, it's a bit of a story.
A story of power, betrayal,
and ambitious hairstyles.
The year? 198...
- Movie's over.
- Watch the next one.
Aw, I'm tired
of watching movies.
- Do you want to play a game?
- Sure.
I spy with my little eye
someone who needs
to shut the hell up.
- Is it me?
- It's always you.
- Now, where was I?
- You were about to tell
a story about you being
a shitty friend,
but then, we got interrupted
by you yelling at Todd.
Oh, yeah. Shut up, Todd.
J“ generic '803 new wave j“
j“ beep, bop, beep, bop,
beep, bop j“
j“ this is a song
from the '803 j“
j“ the decade which
it currently is j“
why do we need
a kitchen and a bathroom?
Pipes are pipes, people.
Do we really need
a toilet and a sink
and a bathtub and...
Wait, hold on...
A whole nother room
with another sink?
They're all just holes
to the ocean, lady.
I mean, come on.
Bojack, you're late.
Here. I got you a beer.
It's on the house.
Don't tell my boss.
Thanks, Charlotte,
but one beer gets me tipsy.
I got to be clear-headed
for my set.
Looks like herb's killing.
Yeah, and the suits
from abc are here.
Look. They're nodding.
That's the executive version
of laughing.
Wow. They must be serious
about herb.
That's Angela Diaz.
She's the woman who made
pantsuits a thing.
Oh, before I forget.
Herb and I are gonna see
back to the future again
this weekend.
- Want to come?
- I'm in.
That movie was amazing,
except for all
the lame time period jokes.
We get it.
The '505 were different.
I'll have a new coke, please.
Listen, you guys don't need
to include me on your dates.
Sometimes, it makes me feel
like a third wheel.
Bojack, stop.
Without the third wheel,
how would you ride a tricycle?
Wouldn't that make it a bicycle?
Herb kazaz,
ladies and gentlemen.
- Hey-hooh!
- Great set, man.
It's like everything
you said was something
that I thought before but never
had the balls to say.
Thanks, bj. I set 'em up.
Now, you knock 'em down.
Let's give it up
for bojack horseman.
Well, thank you, bubbles.
I love L.A. don't you guys?
The prettiest girls in
the world flock to this city,
and they end up
with total knobs.
Take this couple, for example.
Excuse me, miss.
Is that your date?
He's my husband.
That's your husband?
You can do better.
Give me a call after the show.
I'm just kidding around.
I'm not kidding around.
Maker's Manhattan? 2:00 P.M.?
Notjudging.
That guy tipped me a quarter.
That's barely enough money
to buy three gallons of gas.
- You want a slug?
- No, I got to stay sharp.
I got another audition
this afternoon.
God, I can't wait till
I'm finally up
for real jobs instead
of these dumb commercials.
"Here's the thing about
most long-distance plans."
Ugh. I hate
when people say that.
- "Here's the thing."
- It's so stupid.
Just say the thing.
You don't need to introduce
the concept
that there's going
to be a thing.
I don't expect to
be offered secretariat
right away,
but when am I gonna be up
for real roles?
We'll get there, bj.
We both will.
In fact, if I play
my cards right,
I might get there real soon.
Wait.
- Did the guys from abc call?
- Uh-huh.
They invited me
to some hotshot event
at lacma this weekend.
I'm gonna pitch 'em a TV show
while they're drunk.
An off-the-clock,
non-work related social event?
That's the perfect time
to pitch a TV show.
You're brilliant.
These people are so fancy.
Look, look, look.
Hey, hey, look.
That's Joyce DeWitt, isn't it?
That's Joyce DeWitt.
And that's Angela Diaz.
And that's ubu,
the guy who sits.
He is a good dog.
Guys, don't take
your eyes off the prize.
We need to fill Charlotte's bag
with these mini quiches.
This is our breakfast for June.
- Herb kazaz.
- Shit, we're busted.
Pretend you don't speak English.
Buongiorno. Bon jovi.
Salutations.
Crap, that's English.
Hey, you mind if I steal
this superstar for a second?
Okay, yeah.
I'll catch you two later.
Stay out of trouble. Oh, ho.
Well, there he goes.
Herb's about to hit
the big time,
and I'm just gonna be
a small-fry
doing tiny commercials
and eating mini quiches.
You're dead wrong.
You're gonna be a big success.
Herb says that to me
all the time.
- He thinks the world of you.
- He does?
Yeah, I'm not worried about
if you'll become a star.
I'm more worried about how
you'll change when it happens.
Like, you think I'll get fat?
No, that's not
what I'm talking about.
So you're saying I definitely
- won't get fat?
- No.
Well, make up your mind, lady.
Look over there.
See those tar pits?
Hollywood's a real pretty town
that's smack on top
of all that black tar.
By the time you realize
you're sinking,
it's too late.
Wait, is this a science lesson?
No, bojack, it's a metaphor.
- Ugh, that's worse.
- Bojack, I'm moving to Maine.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Really?
- Does herb know?
- Yeah.
I don't think I'm the person
herb's looking for.
I'm going to miss you,
Charlotte.
Hey, do you ever wonder
what would have happened
if you'd met me before herb did?
Would you have made
a move on me?
- Charlotte...
- I don't think you would have.
You know why?
I think you're a coward.
Now go stuff some prosciutto
in your pants
before that Webster kid
takes it all.
I love this town.
Why did you bring me
to Griffith park?
Are we gonna get in
a knife fight
like in rebel without a cause?
- I hate that title.
- He had several causes.
I wanted to give you this.
Look out at that city.
What do you see?
Wow, I didn't realize
there were so many day hookers.
I see a city that you and I
will run someday,
and when we're both famous
and have everything
we've ever wanted,
we'll come back here together
and high-five.
I'm not fully on board
with this new high five thing.
What ever happened
to the low five?
Give me some skin.
Bj, listen.
I got a call from abc today.
They bought my TV pitch.
What? That's amazing.
- What's the show?
- It's called horsin'around.
Well, good luck
on your rocket ship
to the top without me.
No, bojack,
the show's about a horse,
and I told those suits
if they want my show,
then that horse is gonna
be bj goddamn horseman.
- Oh, my god.
- And they said, "no."
- Oh.
- And I said, "please?"
And they said, "okay."
So, what do you say?
- Want to be my star?
- Seriously?
Of course I do. Of course, herb.
Jesus Christ, thank you.
Mm-hmm... whoa, whoa.
I think you got
the wrong idea here.
- Yeah, no, man. Whoa.
- Herb, I'm not...
Me either.
No, I just... you know,
- I caught up in the moment.
- Yeah, no, I gotcha.
Bj, can you believe it?
We're gonna make
an actual TV show!
One that takes
an unflinching look
at the gritty reality
of the American family.
Just kidding. Let's get rich!
Both: Yeah.
J“ generic '903 grunge song j"
j“ everyone in flannel j“
j“ generic '903 grunge song j"
j“ something from Seattle I
why would I say,
"you'll never get me
in that sweater" in this scene
and then,
in the very next scene,
I'm wearing the sweater?
Did my character suddenly forget
that he didn't want to wear
the sweater?
No, see,
that's actually the joke.
Don't explain the joke to me.
I just don't understand
how it's a joke.
So you do want me
to explain it to you?
I want you to add
a scene showing
how I changed my
mind about the sweater
so the goddamn episode
makes sense.
Look at me,
doing your job for you.
Way to go, Shakespeare.
Bj, you're doing
the scene as written.
What happened
to the stories I requested?
Where's my rap?
You said you'd write me a rap.
We're working on it.
We just need a rhyme for
"and I'm here to say."
Well, what about giving me
rollerblades?
How are people gonna know
that my character is hip
if he doesn't roll the blade?
Just get out there
and do your job.
Every one of your ideas
is stupid or racist.
That was one pitch,
and I didn't say
they're all thieves.
But if you're too scared
to start
a national dialogue,
maybe I'll take my ideas home.
Good luck making horsin'around
without the horse.
Bojack, hon.
That audience out there
traveled from all over
the country just
to taste some of your magic.
Do you really want
to disappoint them?
Okay, sharona.
I'll go out and jerk
this limp script
until it gets hard,
but I'm not doing it for herb.
I'm doing it for the fans.
And your 30k an episode.
Let's give it up
for bojack horseman!
And there better be some zimas
in my dressing room
after the show.
Wait a minute.
This isn't the bar.
I got to fire my assistant.
You guys sound like
you're ready for a show.
Oh, gross. Why do I keep
trying to like zima?
- Talk to me, world.
- Bojack it's Princess Carolyn.
How are you doing today?
Well, I'll tell you my problem.
I just keep getting handsomer.
Good problems to have.
Hold for a sec.
I've got your agent on the line.
Bojack goddamn horseface.
I got some news so good,
you'll goddamn kiss me.
Put it here. Put it here.
What's the role
you've been dying
to play your whole life,
besides Kathy Ireland's
bathing suit?
Ha-ha. She is attractive.
Good god, when I die,
Bury me in Kathy Ireland.
Uh, Marv? Marv?
What's the big news?
Secretariat!
It's happening, and it's down
to you and val kilmer
for the title role.
That's amazing.
Thank you. Thank you.
Now, listen.
I don't want to see you
in any more tabloids.
Keep your head down
and your nose clean.
Now, I gotta go.
I got a lunch with mc scat Kat.
Scandal breaking today
surrounding the family sitcom,
horsin ' around.
Oh, god.
What did I do this time?
Herb kazaz, the show's creator,
was caught tonight
in an LAPD sting
- on public indecency.
- Wha...
Police say Mr. Kazaz
was caught in the middle
of lewd acts with another man.
Conservative groups have
been quick to organize.
Horsin'around
is a show for kids.
My family should be able
to watch those nubile preteens
without men
like perv kazaz flaunting
their alternative lifestyles
and ruining america.
Bojack, I gotta tell ya.
- I'm gay.
- No doy.
I know we haven't been close
for the past couple years.
Okay, I'm gonna hold back
my "no doys"
because there might be a lot.
But you know me, right?
You know that I'm a good guy.
They're gunning for me
at the network,
and if I get kicked off this,
I won't recover.
I need to know that
you've got my back.
If you threaten to walk,
they'll listen to you.
Herb, you picked
the worst possible time to...
Hey, you know I wouldn't
ask if I didn't need it.
Come on, bojack.
How'd we get so far apart, huh?
You know what?
You can count on me, herb.
I mean, I wouldn't even be here
if it weren't for you.
I knew it!
I knew you'd come through.
And when this is all over,
we're going
to drive back up
to Griffith park.
I still owe you
that high five, right?
Hey, this is a dumb question,
but do you guys ever,
like, all link up together
and do, like, a party train
or a fun circle?
'Cause I feel like
I'd be doing that all the...
Never mind. Stupid question.
Feel stupid for asking that.
Go right ahead.
And then it goes,
"I like healthy gums
in a major way."
See, that's
what I'm talking about.
That's great.
We just gotta make sure
that we work in the phrase
"toothbrush rap" early,
so they know I'm rapping.
Bojack,
can we chat for a second?
Ugh. Here we go.
It's the big one.
I'm not gonna waste
your time with small talk
because you work for me,
and your time is my time.
We're letting herb go.
- You can't do that.
- "I can't do that."
I'm not asking you.
It's nothing personal.
I like herb.
I think he's a good guy.
But this is a business,
and every day
we don't fire him,
we're flushing money
- down the crapper.
- Well, if he goes, I go.
"Well, if he goes, you go."
I wouldn't do that.
Bojack, I think you're a star,
and sometimes being a star
means making tough choices.
You can storm out,
make a big show out of
what a "good" friend you are,
or you could be
the guy who does his job.
- Angela...
- I'll tell you when
it's your turn to talk again.
Look, you're a star,
but this is really just
the beginning of
the bojack horseman story.
You can choose
whatever path you want,
but I'll tell you right now.
You don't win awards
and you don't
get to be on the covers
of magazines
and you don't get
to play the lead role
in the secretariat movie
by being a good friend.
What's that old expression
about how the show must go on?
Oh, right.
It's "don't be an idiot."
So what do you think, bojack?
That's a courtesy question.
I already know what you think
because I have conversations
like this one five times a day.
I know who you are, and I know
you've already
made your decision.
But if you want to surprise me,
now's the time to do it.
That's what I thought.
You're doing the right thing,
and I know it's hard.
But if herb's really your
friend, he'll understand.
Now, you've got
a show to put on,
so I'll let you get ready.
This was a good conversation.
Productive.
If you're lucky,
I'll never talk to you again.
You folks ready for a show?
'Cause I think a certain someone
might show up any second.
Wait a minute.
This isn't the bar.
I gotta fire my assistant.
So what ended up happening
with secretariat?
Went into turnaround.
I don't totally know
what "turnaround" means,
- but they never made the movie.
- Whoa.
This house is way bigger
than yours.
Herb's done really well
for a guy you clicked over.
- Oh, no. Ah.
- That's enough out of you.
Stay out here
and turn this car around
in case we need to leave
in a hurry.
Hooray. A task.
Bojack! Well.
Jesus, you look shitty.
Have you been eating your guilt
this whole time?
Yeah, you don't look
so hot yourself, herb.
I have cancer.
And hello.
Who's this stunning creature?
And what string of bad decisions
has placed you
in bojack's orbit?
- Uh...
- This is Diane.
She's writing a book about me.
Pleasure to meet you.
Is your book called,
portrait of an asshole?
I kid.
It's funny,
because he ruined my life.
I joke. It's what I do.
Please, come in.
You're letting out
all the cancer.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha...
Almost. Ah...
Almost there.
Come on... ah.
Oh, thanks. Thanks.
Bojack, how are your utensils?
- Uh, they're fine.
- Are you sure?
Because if that knife
ain't sharp enough,
I got another that you left
in my back 20 years ago.
Could have seen that coming.
Who asks about utensils?
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Nope. No, you are not.
Oh. Ow. Almost.
- Drive, drive, drive!
- Oh. Oh, no.
I can't turn the car around.
I've been trying to do this
three-point turn forever.
I mean, it's more
like a 300-point turn.
- Am I right, huh?
- Hee hee hee hee!
Hey, we've got two sacks
of Kardashian swag
and the fuzz on our heels.
You think this is driver's ed,
you hat-wearing pussy?
Drive the goddamn car!
Hey, herb,
is that your vitamix?
Bojack has one, too.
I wonder if you guys have
strong opinions about it
one way or the other.
Well, the stupid thing
was like 600 bucks.
I have used mine
a grand total of zero times.
I got it a month before
I was diagnosed with cancer.
I don't give a shit
about being healthy anymore.
I don't even have cancer,
and I don't use it.
- So who's it for?
- Exactly.
What is so great about liquids?
Every article I read now is
"juice this" and "juice that."
You know why?
Juice controls the media.
Hey-hooh.
Can't this thing go any faster?
Uh, I'm going as fast as I can.
Do you want me to get out?
Try to guide you?
No, I think I'm almost there.
You're doing a great job.
Kenzie, stop talking to him.
Why? He's being nice.
Remember the number one rule
of the celebrity stealing club...
- "No falling in love."
- Ugh.
That's your rule for every club.
It's a good rule.
Whoa. Whoa, guys.
I'm sensing a lot
of hostility here.
Maybe we should take
our masks off and actually talk.
You want me to take
my mask off? Fine.
Happy? I took my mask off.
Did you?
Because I think
you're still wearing a mask.
Oh.
Oh, my god, herb,
you met President Clinton?
Oh, yeah. Many times.
Did you think that
I spent the last 20 years
on my couch just feeling
sorry for myself?
I mean, I did do that,
but I also started...
A charity to bring clean water
to millions of children
in Sub-Saharan Africa.
Oh, wow.
I presented at
the teen choice awards.
Wait, is that Charlotte?
Yeah, yeah. We kept in touch.
You should actually
give her a call.
I'm sure she'd
love to hear from you.
She looks good
for someone so old.
She's three years younger
than you.
Exactly!
Er?
Well, guys, I'm pretty beat.
I think I need to
head off to bed,
and I hope
I actually wake up later.
And it was actually nice
to see you, bojack.
You can see yourselves out.
"Juice controls the media."
I love it.
So I guess in a sense
I'm running away from the cops,
but I feel like in another,
truer sense,
I'm running away from myself.
- Truth. Truth.
- Whoa.
Kenzie, do you have
anything to share?
Just how amazing it feels
to finally
be honest for once.
I could live a million lives,
and I'd never forget
this one afternoon.
Word.
You know, I act all cool
and sophisticated
on the outside,
but on the inside,
I'm just Todd, you know?
But thanks to you guys,
I think I'm finally
- ready to let my guard down.
- Do you hear that?
- He's letting his guard down.
- Let's get him!
Oh!
Celebrity stealing club
strikes again.
This... this just doesn't
feel right.
I should have brought
a bottle of wine.
That's what adults do.
Bojack, damn it.
Is that what's bothering you,
- that you didn't bring wine?
- You're right.
I just would have drunk it
on the way here.
This isn't about wine, bojack.
If you have something
you need to say to someone,
you should do it
while you have the chance
because before you know it,
it'll be too late.
Is this one of those things
where we're talking
about herb but we're actually
talking about something else?
- No, I was talking about herb.
- Okay, good. Yeah, me, too.
Hey, buddy!
You come back
for that vitamix you...
Ooh, you should get that
looked at.
Yeah. I've been meaning
to see a doctor.
Hey, I wanted to talk
to you about... you know.
I feel bad about what happened.
So you're apologizing.
Yes. I'm sorry.
Okay. I don't forgive you.
Herb, I said I'm sorry.
Yeah, and I do not forgive you.
Uh... not sure you get
what's happening here.
This could be
the last time that you...
No. I'm not gonna
give you closure.
You don't get that.
You have to live
with the shitty thing you did
for the rest of your life.
You have to know that
it's never,
ever going to be okay.
I really think that we'd both
- feel better if we just...
- I'm dying.
I'm not gonna feel better,
and I'm not gonna be your prop
so you can feel better.
You have to believe me.
- I did everything I could.
- Yeah?
Then why didn't you call me?
Huh?
20 years... you didn't call me.
Look, I... I wanted to,
but I didn't think...
You know what
it was like for me?
I had nobody. Everybody left.
I knew all those showbiz phonies
would turn on me.
Sure. But you?
It's not my fault you got fired.
I don't care about the job!
I did fine. I had a good life.
But what I needed then
was a friend,
and you abandoned me.
And I will never forgive you
for that.
Now, get the fuck
out of my house.
Hey, this is a dumb question,
but the gay thing
and the rectal cancer thing
aren't related, are they?
- Get out of here!
- Never mind.
Stupid question.
Forget I brought it up.
- Huh.
- Hey, bj.
- Put that back, asshole!
- No, you gave this to me.
No!
Bojack?
What are you doing? Get off him.
The show was never the same
after I left... admit it.
Some people prefer
the later years.
Bojack. Come on.
Thank you for inviting us.
You have a lovely home.
You know what your problem is?
You want to think of yourself
as the good guy.
Well, I know you better
than anyone,
and I can tell you
that you're not.
In fact, you'd probably sleep
a lot better at night
if you just admitted to yourself
that you're a selfish
goddamn coward
who takes whatever he wants
and doesn't give a shit
about who he hurts.
That's you.
That's bojack horseman.
I don't know why I came here.
Yeah. You do.
Princess Carolyn:
You said you wanted a job.
It doesn't matter.
Nothing matters.
Wow. What happened in Malibu?
I gotta go.
Hey, bright side.
At least now you have
a good story to tell
at his funeral.
Ugh, god.
I'm not trying
to kill the vibe here,
but I've had to pee
for, like, three hours.
Look, I won't put
what happened today
in the book
if you don't want me to.
No, it's okay.
Full truth like we agreed.
Warts and all.
It doesn't matter anyway.
I don't even care what anybody
thinks anymore.
Well, for what it's worth,
I think it took a lot of guts
to do what you did back there.
- Mmm...
- Mm!
J“ back in the '903 j”
j“ I was in a very famous TV show j“
- I“ I'm bojack the horse j“
- I bojack j“
j“ bojack the horse I”
j“ don't act like you don't know I
j“ and I'm trying to hold on to my past j“
j“ it's been so long I“
j“ I don't think I'm gonna last j“
j“ I guess I'll just try I”
j“ and make you understand I“
j“ that I'm more horse than a man j'
j“ or I'm more man than a horse j“
j“ bojack j“
It's a kazzaz-trophe.