Come on!
Oh, is it this guy?
Never travel without it.
Stop holding up the line, idiot!
It's not his fault.
He's just doing his job.
It's your fault, dummy.
I'm sorry, sir,
no liquid over three ounces.
This is pappy Van winkle,
friend.
Do you know how old
this bourbon is?
If this was a person,
I would've stopped having sex
with it a year ago.
I'm sorry, sir.
Do you know who I am?
Come on. Ugh!
I'm actually a huge celebrity
on my way to New York
for an important meeting
with a book publisher,
who wants to publish a book
about me because I am famous.
- That's not...
- Fine, you want me to dance?
I'll dance.
Give me ten seconds, Diane.
This guy's being
a total fascist.
Diane?
Over here, bojack.
How'd you get through so fast?
I followed the basic
requirements for air travel
that have been in place
for over a decade.
Ugh, weird.
Sir, whoever you are, please...
Really? You've never heard
of my TV show?
You know very well who I am.
And now if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to New York.
Ah, no.
More? Come on!
Oh, you know what?
Could be this.
Oh, my god, he's got a gun.
Relax, it's a lighter.
How much lighter fluid
can I take on the plane?
And before you answer,
remember, I'm a celebrity.
We're gonna need
a full body cavity search.
Thanks for coming
to New York for this.
Let's just say, it's better
for everyone's kneecaps
if I stay out of California
for a little bit.
Always nice to get a change
of scenery, am I right?
I think the New York air's
been good for my health.
I mean, I did find a lump,
but hey, who needs
health insurance
when you've got bojack horseman
writing a book, huh?
How's it coming along?
It's great.
I'm pumping out
heartfelt anecdotes
and witty observations
left and right,
and this one is spinning it all
into gold.
Your telephone is ringing.
I'm ira glass.
Thank you for being a sustaining
member of public radio.
Everyone has a story,
and your phone's story
is that it's ringing.
Excuse me. Hello?
Hurry back, superstar.
I don't think
Diane's working out.
What? Why? Is Diane no good?
She's too good.
I don't know if Diane is
damaged enough to tell my story.
She's so... functional.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Mr. Horseman,
she's too functional.
Why don't I just
get on the phone
and call a less functional...
What are you talking about?
This is a very bad time, bojack!
All right.
You need to promise me that
your book will be on the shelves
and making money by October!
All right. Jesus.
Uh-huh? Uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
Got it. Sorry I took so long.
Who was that? The library?
Thanking you for never
returning a book late?
That was my brother Tommy.
My dad just died.
Oh, my god.
Did we talk about firming up
the release date?
- I was thinking late September.
- I am so sorry.
It's fine, he was old
and also the worst.
Such a terrible tragedy
really puts everything
in perspective.
Where does that leave us
as far as the book of it all?
Not a problem.
I just got to swing by Boston
and give my condolences
real quick.
Bojack can come with me.
We'll get some work done
while we're there,
and then that way the whole trip
won't be a total waste of time.
Great.
Call me if you need anything,
but hang up after one ring,
and I'll call you
back from the phone booth
where my wife and I are living.
J“ Todd bless
these scrambled eggs j'
j“ eggs from the fridge j“
j“ sunny side them
and guide them j“
Todd, stop singing
your dumb scrambled eggs song.
Who said that?
If you're wondering
who said that,
it's this note
that you're reading.
You're hearing my voice
in your head,
because that's
how reading works.
Oh, yeah.
As you might've noticed, Todd,
I've left you home alone
for the day,
and frankly, ialready
regret that decision.
Here's what you need to do.
Nothing.
Don't touch my stuff,
and don't make a mess.
Pick me up at the airport
tomorrow,
and until then,
don't do anything.
Well, seal's broken.
Might as well enjoy myself.
J“ it's all good j“
whee!
cheers to bath time.
Great story, Todd.
I love our friendship.
Here we go!
The great toddini!
And here we have the home
of a truly dynamic
and unique talent,
TV's own David boreanaz.
All: Ohh!
Sounds like we have some fans
of person of interest on board,
or castle,
or whatever his show is.
Sorry, dudes,
you got the wrong house.
All: Aww.
Crikey, I would've paid $50 U.S.
To see where
David boreanaz lives.
He's the American Hugh Jackman.
Oh, yeah, 50 bucks?
Is he the guy in burn notice?
What? 50 bucks?
In that case, come on in,
friends.
Some guy named David boreanaz
lives here.
All: Hooray!
Hey, so listen,
I really want to be here for you
in your time of need,
but I'm not really good
with funerals or death
or families or feelings
or people.
Don't worry.
You can wait in the car.
It's probably better
you don't meet my brothers.
They're narrow-minded,
mean-spirited dirtbags.
I wish I had
brothers growing up.
Touch football on the weekends,
noogie parades on the reg.
Life as an only child
can get pretty lonely.
Daddy, do you want to meet
my imaginary friend?
Imaginary friends
are free-loaders
invented by communists
to rip-off welfare.
Why don't you do
something productive,
like bang your head
against the wall
until your brain
isn't so stupid?
Okay, daddy.
Yeah, well, I
was pretty lonely too.
My family made
my life miserable,
and then they never
forgave me for leaving.
So, what,
you're like the black sheep?
No, Gary's the black sheep.
He's adopted.
I'm just the member of
the family nobody likes.
And my dad
was the worst of them all.
You told me
that you and your father
used to sit on the roof
and look at the stars together.
Oh, yeah, I was just trying
to get you to open up,
so I used an old writer's trick
called "me lying to you."
Oh, yeah?
Well, I'm using an old me trick
called "that hurts my feelings."
And the truth is,
I used to sit alone
on the hill out by the dump
and dream of waking up
as Chelsea Clinton,
but with my hair.
You do have great hair.
I know.
That's us.
I'll just pop in
for a quick hi and bye.
Then we'll be on our way.
Ten minutes, swear to god.
You can play
with this kaleidoscope
I got you at the airport.
What? A kaleidoscope?
I'm not five...
Shapes and colors the likes
of which I've never seen.
Hello.
Hey, yeah, deedee came home!
Gary, Marty, Artie,
deedee's back!
Come here!
Game. Watching the game.
Can't look up from the game.
How you doing?
Marty, it's a game from '86.
You've seen it a hundred times.
And how many times does
Buckner break your heart?
Both: 100 times.
Aw, thank god
you're here, deedee.
Pops is wicked departed.
Oh, yeah, man.
He departed so hard.
And I do not like
them apples, deedee.
Yo, deedee, get me a beer.
Yeah, make that two, deedee.
Gary, Marty, I just got home.
Ooh, Princess Diane doesn't
want to get her brother a beer.
Hey, ma, come look
what the pats dragged in.
Oh, hello!
Look who decided to come home.
Queen deedee blesses us
with her presence.
To what do I owe the honor?
Look, I'm just here
to offer my condolences.
Oh, sure, in and out,
like a protestant on Christmas.
Why would you want
to stick around,
be with your family
in their time of need?
Come on, ma.
Don't fight while the game's on.
It's bad juju.
It's the '86 world series.
Theylose.
Ah, why'd you have to...
Oh, we're just a bunch
of savages, right?
We're not like your fancy
California friends.
Your George Clooney
and your California raisins.
Oh, come off it, ma.
She don't mean no harm.
For five years
she didn't come home.
Why don't you make like a-rod
and blow.
Well, this was clearly
a huge mistake.
Ah, don't go.
Deedee, please.
Why not?
Ma doesn't want me here.
Ma don't know what she wants.
She wants you here. We all do.
Ain't that right, Marty?
Can't look up from the game.
Besides, we need your help
organizing all
the funeral stuff.
We didn't go to college.
We're not smart like you.
Fine, I'll help.
Is there a number
for me to call?
Yeah, try 1-800-the-Internet,
dummy.
Jeez, do some legwork, Dee.
And do it quick.
The ice is melting.
Oh, my god. Is that dad?
Did someone draw balls
on his forehead?
That was before
we knew he was dead.
We just thought
he was wicked hung over.
In your face, dad!
In your face forever.
Welcome to the home
of David boreanaz,
famous from television shows
such as dramas on networks.
That will be $50 please.
Oy, mate, this picture
of David boreanaz fell apart.
Oh, no, no, no,
I'll handle that.
Why don't you just
go look through
David boreanaz's
underwear drawer, okay?
It's in his bedroom.
Oh, knickers.
Hey, what do you think
you're doing?
Uh-oh, am I reading
something again?
No, this is your conscience.
Bojack trusted you
to take care of his house.
Is this really...
What are you doing?
J“ dun-dun-dun-dun j“
j“ dun-dun-dun j“
it's a great day
on Todd's phone.
How can I help you?
Are you trying to cut me out
of this David boreanaz deal?
I'm your agent, damn it.
How'd you find out
about boreanaz house?
Don't worry,
I'm not just gonna sit here
batting a ball of yarn around
while you do the real work.
I want to take your project
to the next level.
We need to go bigger.
Have you thought about attaching
Mila kunis to this thing?
Attach her? How?
You do your job. I'll do mine.
Who is this?
Ah, out of combinations.
Now I'm bored.
Diane!
- You show me nothing...
- What do you want from me?
You have no right to barge
in here after five years
and judge us, Diane.
I'm just saying Marty
could lend a hand
instead of sitting on the couch
watching the game all day.
Ah, deedee.
You know very well
his leg's still sore
from the accident at the quarry.
Yeah, he's got to rest up
if he's gonna be
a wide receiver for bc.
He didn't get into b.C.
Ah, what's the point of
getting off the couch anyway?
All the jobs are going
to immigrants these days.
What do you... we're immigrants.
- How do you figure?
- We're Vietnamese?
Step off!
We're American as fuck.
And that's the same crap
you always pull...
What do you want from me?
Come on!
Excuse me.
Yes, hello,
I'm looking for Diane.
Does anyone here speak English?
Pull over and park the car.
Is that the frickin' horse
from horsin'around?
Again, does anyone here
speak English?
- Oh, no way...
- What?
A TV star!
Boreanaz house.
75 each.
Children and seniors free.
Please stay behind the ropes
and keep your hands and
belongings on your person
at all times.
Next we'll head to the kitchen
where... is that Mila kunis?
All: Ooh!
Note the letters b.H.
On all hand towels and linens.
That stands for
"boreanaz house."
Yeah, do you pick up bodies?
Is that a service you provide?
Corpse removal?
Hey, bojack, you ever meet
any Boston celebrities?
Well, one time at Bristol farms,
Ben Affleck and I did reach
for the same bunch of grapes.
Oh, he eats grapes just like us?
Hey, ma,
Ben Affleck eats grapes.
He don't eat grapes!
Bojack said
he fed Affleck grapes.
He was graping it up
with the daredevil himself.
This is the greatest day
of my life.
Oh!
Hey, I don't suppose you boys
would have any interest
in maybe playing some
touch football later?
Are you kidding?
Touch football
with a star like you?
That would be mad wicked pisser.
Ooh, you know what else
we got to do?
We got to watch
the cryane video.
Ooh, that sounds good.
What's that?
No, we don't need
to revisit that.
When deedee was 16,
we made up a secret pen pa!
For her named Leo.
Guys, I really would rather
not discuss it.
We all took turns
writing her letters,
pretending to be this sensitive
boy from Cambridge.
It was wicked messed up.
“Oh, Diane, we're
two misunderstood souls.
"Everyone else is a phony.
Yours forever, Leo."
What? That is amazing.
After six months of letters,
we hired a homeless guy
to pretend to be Leo
and take her
to the homecoming dance.
- Look at her.
- Watch, watch this part.
I like your boutonniere.
Why don't we watch this
every day?
- Look at her face.
- Now that's a good prank.
I was humiliated.
Yeah, you wouldn't get it.
It's a brothers thing,
right, brothers?
Whoo! That's cryane for you.
What a pussy.
You know,
it's nice that years later
we can all laugh about this.
Yep, my therapist
thinks the same thing.
I'm gonna go meet
with the funeral director.
Any of you boys want to come?
Nah, I ain't so big
on funeral homes, deedee.
All them dead bodies,
they give me the jeebies.
Yeah, deedee,
why do we got to go?
Fine, none of you have to go.
I'll take care of everything.
Thank you, Diane.
We all really appreciate it.
Come on, bojack.
Why you got to take
bojack with you?
Boo!
Boys, you have stolen my heart
like Dave Roberts
stole second base.
Hey! He knows our things!
I must go now, but I'll see
you all at the funeral, okay?
And when I do,
you're all getting noogies.
- Funeral!
- Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
Funeral!
Funeral! Funeral!
And now, a very special treat
justfor our platinum members.
Let's take a peak
at the slumbering
Mr. Boreanaz himself.
Get out of my room, Todd!
I'm David boreanaz.
Ohh!
And thus concludes our tour.
Have a boreanderful day.
Tell me about your father.
Well, he was a mean,
sadistic alcoholic,
who never supported
anything I did
and actively delighted
in seeing me fail.
Hmm, I see.
Sounds like you're looking for
our piece of shit dad package.
That would be too good
for my father.
Hmm, I see.
Might I then suggest
our piece of shit dad package
would be too good
for him package.
Yeah, that's the one.
Excellent choice.
Hey, can I suggest something?
You might want to loosen up
a little.
I think you could actually
learn a thing or two
from your brothers.
Are you kidding?
If I was like my brothers,
nothing would ever get done.
I'm just saying,
if you can't find a way
to let off some steam
you're going to explode.
God damn it!
Are you god damn kidding me?
I keep getting calls
from this unlisted number.
Ignore. Who are these assholes?
Why don't you just answer,
and then you'll know?
Oh they'd just love that,
wouldn't they?
Ugh, how are we supposed
to blackmail him
if we can't reach him?
Maybe we got to get him
where he lives?
You mean?
That's right, his house.
What the... whose house is this?
Is that David boreanaz?
I could've sworn
bojack horseman lived here.
Hey, let's keep
these lines moving, huh?
You want to stop and chat,
you gotta pay for
the extended stay ticket.
Ah, so much, so much, so much.
Another five gs, t-bag,
and we are in the pink.
I don't know, Princess Carolyn.
I ran out of shoeboxes
for the money,
and the books aren't adding up.
Plus the men's lav
needs to be serviced,
and I had to fire Janine
in the gift shop
for stealing boreabble heads.
I mean, how did I end up
with all this responsibility?
Hey, I'm not screwing around
here, small fry.
You better make
those numbers sing.
I don't think these
offshore banks we've been using
are 100% legal.
Yeah, well, my mother told me
never to slap an idiot.
What? Ow!
Now we're both
breaking the rules.
You listen, and you listen good.
I've gotten used
to a certain lifestyle
since boreanaz house
went public,
and I'm not going back
to the old way.
Mommy likes her shoes, see?
And her pearls.
Oh, I'm in too deep.
I don't know what to do.
I'll tell you
what you should do.
Who said that?
It's me, David boreanaz.
Is that what
David boreanaz sounds like?
Uh, sure.
Let me give you some advice.
As we say on my show...
I want to say, new girl?
Just keep doing what you're
doing, and you'll be fine.
Wow, thanks, davie b.
Never call me that.
Unbelievable.
It's 4:00.
I don't think anyone's coming.
Unbe-goddamn-iievable.
All those jerk wads
had to do was show up,
and they couldn't even do that.
Where's the body even?
Beg your pardon, minor hiccup.
My goons went to pick your
father up, but nobody was home.
For a nominal fee,
we can scrounge up
another body for you.
Would you care to peruse
our loaner closet?
Hey, assholes! Where were you?
I planned the whole funeral,
like you asked me to,
and nobody showed.
Yeah, we realized dad
wouldn't have wanted
some stuffy funeral.
He would've wanted his body
to be chopped up into chum
and thrown
in Derek jeter's fat face.
Yeah, suck it, jeter!
Wait, what? Where is dad?
We got him chummed.
He's in the truck.
You chummed dad?
It's what your father wanted,
honey,
but then you wouldn't know
anything about that, would you?
Let me get this straight.
So instead of coming
to the funeral
that I paid for
and spent all day organizing,
you had dad's body
ground into chum,
so you could throw his mushy
remains on Derek jeter?
No, not just on Derek jeter.
We're gonna throw it
into his fat face.
- Yeah, his fat face.
- In his fat face.
The Yankees are in town
this week.
The planets are aligning,
deedee.
Tommy, you begged me
to stay and help.
Why does everything always
got to be about big-shot Diane?
Too good for her home.
I don't think
I'm too good for my home.
Yeah, guys,
you got it all wrong.
Diane isn't a big-shot.
She's my ghostwriter.
She's writing a book that's not
even gonna have her name on it.
You think this
is how she expected
her life would be going at 34?
She lives with her rich
boyfriend and doesn't pay rent.
She's not too good for anything.
What?
Diane's a freeloader?
Even I pay rent.
Bojack helping?
Whoa.
This is why I told you
to wait in the car!
Oh, she snapped.
Here comes cryane.
Hey, hey, deedee, come on.
Diane, you are making
a public spectacle of yourself.
Deedee, what are you doing
with dad's keys?
Put those back.
Oh, come on, that's dad's truck.
Dad's chum is in the back.
No! No, no, no!
Suck a dick, dumb shits!
Well, that crazy clam did it.
She took pops.
Oh, no, what are we gonna do?
And it's a one-hopper
back to the pitcher.
Easy out at first.
So what we're gonna do
is nothing?
Sox are on,
and I haven't seen this one.
Does anyone know
where she might have gone?
Ah, she used to run off
like this all the time
in high school too.
Who knows where crazy goes.
I think I know where she went.
Wait, you can't leave.
The party's
just getting started.
I don't know,
Diane was pretty upset,
and she's got your dad.
Oh, don't go, bojack.
You're like the fifth brother
I never had.
I... really?
Yeah, don't leave, bro.
After this,
we'll go play touch football
and do a noogie parade.
Ah, um...
Everyone please disperse.
This is an unlawful gathering.
Disperse immediately.
Oh, this isn't looking good,
Princess Carolyn.
What are we gonna do?
What do you mean, we?
Princess Carolyn
always lands on her feet.
Mr. Boreanaz, I presume.
Um, would you
like a boreabble head?
The amazing thing is,
the house looks
just like bojack's house.
They must have
the same architect.
Anyway, how are things with you?
Not good.
I should've known
it was a waste of time
to come back here.
Oh, that's awful.
Well, when you get back,
I'll give you one of
my patented peanutbutter hugs.
Crunchy and creamy.
You know
that patent wasn't approved,
but I'll take it.
I have to go. Bojack's here.
Bojack, well, what's he doing?
Hey, sorry I said
all that stuff about you.
It's all true, isn't it?
I found this letter
back at the bar.
I think it's for you.
Look, just read it.
I think you'll like it.
"Dear Diane, it's me,
your old pen pal Leo.
This definitely isn't
bojack horseman writing this."
Keep reading.
"You're a good person, Diane,
"and that's
the most important thing.
"Even if no one appreciates you,
"it's important that
you don't stop being good.
"I like how you always
bring your own bags
"to the grocery store,
"and how you're always
organized to go places.
"I like how you chew gum on the
airplane so your ears will pop.
"A lot of people might not
appreciate that about you,
"but I do.
Yours forever, Leo."
That's the best letter
he ever wrote me.
Look, take it from someone
with his own shitty parents,
family is a sinkhole,
and you were right to get out
when you had the chance.
The stupid thing is,
even now I still just want them
to be proud of me
and think I did good.
Is that really stupid?
- Yep.
- No, it isn't.
Yeah, it is.
You want those guys
to be proud of you?
I guess I was just hoping to
get some modicum of closure.
Closure is a made up thing
by Steven Spielberg
to sell movie tickets.
It's, like true love
and the Munich Olympics,
doesn't exist in the real world.
The only thing to do now
is just to keep living forward.
Yeah, but every time
I come back here they...
So don't come back here.
What's great about Los Angeles
is nobody cares about where
you're from or who you are.
It's a superficial town
where you can worry
about stupid shit
like keeping your pool clean,
and what artisanal nuts
to put on your salad.
I do like salad.
Oh, it's the best.
Why do you think people keep
moving there?
Thanks, bojack.
The good news is, your dad
can't hurt anyone ever again.
Uh-oh.
J“ gonna spend the day I
j“ over at Fenway j'
thank you so much, Derek jeter.
I thought a big baseball
hotshot like you
would be too busy to help us
old ladies across the street.
I always have time
to look out for my elders,
yankee fan or no.
Is that a barrel of chum?
J“ only at Fenway j'
j“ ba-dum, ba-da-dum j“
um, I'll meet you inside.
I have to make a call.
Okay.
It's herb. You know what to do.
Hey, herb, look,
I think we have some
unfinished business.
It seems like life's too short
to hold grudges
and stuff like that,
you know what I'm saying?
About life being too short?
Well, of course
you know what I'm saying.
You're the one with terminal...
I feel like I'm doing
all the talking here.
So anyway, I thought
maybe we could chat.
Why don't you give me
a call, okay?
Um... so smell you later?
This is bojack. Horseman.
Obviously.
Ugh, who keeps calling me?
Come on, bojack.
Pick up, pick up.
I'm sure he'll pick up.
It's bojack.
You know what to do.
J“ back in the '903 j”
j“ I was in a very famous TV show j“
- j“ I'm bojack the horse j“
- I bojack j“
j“ bojack the horse j”
j“ don't act like you don't know I
j“ and I'm trying to hold on to my past j“
j“ it's been so long j“
j“ I don't think I'm gonna last j“
j“ I guess I'll just try j”
j“ and make you understand I
j“ that I'm more horse than a man j“
j“ or I'm more man than a horse j“
j“ bojack j“
boxer versus raptor.
Jnanananananananaj'