What are you doing here?
You said if I was in town
to give you a call.
- Wanna get a drink?
- It's eight in the morning.
It's 5 P.M. in Los Angeles.
- That's not true.
- I actually don't know what time it is.
When's the last time you slept?
You look like shit.
Really? 'Cause you look like a million...
- Yeah, let's get you back to my place.
- What about the store?
What if somebody has an emergency
and they need more...
Turquoise shit?
It's new Mexico.
They'll find it.
- It's really good to see you.
- It's good to see you, too.
I can't wait for you
to meet Kyle and the kids.
Kyle and the kids? Please tell me
that's the name of your band.
Kyle and the kids
Kyle is the dad
and Charlotte is married to him
and they've got some kids
there's penny
she's going to high school
and she's got a brother
her brother's name is trip
they're the perfect family
Kyle and the kids
he loves his wife
and there's nothing you can do
Kyle and the kids
nothing's gonna be all right
be all right, oh, no
so, who are you again?
You were friends with mom
when she lived in L.A.?
Your mom never mentioned she used
to hang out with the bojack horseman?
Star of screen and... book?
- Wait, mom lived in Los Angeles?
- Never came up?
- All these years?
- It was a long time ago.
Oh, gross. Mom, trip has a boner again.
- Trip.
- Trip, let's dial back the boners.
- Gross.
- What? I can't help it.
- Trip, ew.
- You are at the breakfast table
with your parents, your big sister,
and an old man.
- What could possibly be arousing you?
- Am I the old man?
I don't understand how it works.
I was just excited that I finished
the maze on the back of the cereal box.
So, bojack. What brings you to tesuque?
So, we're just gonna change
the subject
and pretend trip isn't being a huge perv
right now?
Yeah, penny, that's the plan.
Talking about it makes it worse.
It likes attention.
Charlotte told me if I was ever
in new Mexico
- I should call her.
- But why are you in new Mexico?
- Yeah, what are you doing in new Mexico?
- I, uh...
You didn't drive all this way
just to see my mom, did you?
No, of course not.
That would be crazy,
to come all this way just to see a woman
I haven't had a real conversation with
in 30 years.
- I mean, obviously that would be crazy.
- Uh...
- Because she has a family, which is great.
- Yeah.
- You guys are great.
So, I'm just here to, you know, say hello.
- Mm.
- On my way to see...
- On your way to sea?
- Yes.
To the sea. To the shining sea.
Because I'm here to buy... a boat.
- At the... Santa fe boat show.
- I've never heard of a Santa fe boat show.
That's 'cause... it's a secret boat show.
- Invitation-only.
- Huh.
Mostly athletes and visiting dignitaries
and big-time celebrities and... kings.
- Wow.
- Hold up.
If you live in Los Angeles,
which is right on the ocean,
why would you drive all the way here
to go to a boat show
- in the middle of landlocked new Mexico?
- Jeez, so many questions.
What is this,
hollywoo stars and celebrities,
what do they know,
do they know things, let's find out?
0h, gotta take this.
It's my... boat... guy.
- Heho?
- Okay, so I got turtel...
Hey, knute.
- You got any leads for me, boat-wise?
- What?
Sounds perfect, knute.
- Now tell me, do we need a poop deck?
- Huh?
- Well, if Leo has one, then I want one.
- Bojackn
in fact, I want two, two poop decks.
Sorry about that. What's going on?
- Where the hell are you?
- Tesuque.
- Te-who-ka?
- Tesuque, new Mexico.
- Outside Santa fe.
- Are you te-stupid?
If you don't get your ass back te-set,
you're gonna get te-sued.
- Just get me a couple of days.
- For what? What are you doing there?
I don't know, I just...
This isn't what I expected.
Well, I can probably stave them off
till Monday if you get pinkeye.
- Can you get pinkeye?
- I have to go.
Wait, bojack, when are you coming back?
Soon. Yep, I want the starboard
- to be fully starboard.
- What?
- And the port to be... also starboard.
- Huh?
- Thanks a lot. Goodbye.
- Wait, bojack...
- Hey.
- I'm really glad you're here.
Oh, yeah... uh, me, too.
I hope this isn't weird for you.
You know, me having a family and...
Why would it be weird?
At our age,
it's weird if you don't have a family.
- I mean...
- Well, not for you.
- No.
- 'Cause you've been busy.
- Right.
- With your career.
Sure, yeah,
my career has kept me super busy.
Anyway, I know you're just in town
for the boat show,
but seriously... make yourself at home.
I really don't want to impose.
If there's anything I can do
to help around here...
Mom, dad was supposed to take me driving
after school today,
but now he's gotta take trip
to his dumb-ass basketball game.
- It's the quarter-finals.
- You'll get a hard-on during the game.
Now I'll get a hard-on because
you made me think about it. Thanks a lot.
- I'll take you driving this weekend.
- I need to practice every day.
I'm the only senior
who still doesn't have a license.
It's embarrassing.
Well, I got the store,
and I already took the morning off,
so unless you know any other adults...
Can bojack take me?
- Huh?
- What?
- I mean, he is an adult.
- Uh...
Well, I mean, if it's okay with bojack.
You'd really be doing me a huge favor.
Well, I guess I could make some time...
Before the boat show.
Keep your eyes on the road
and hands on the wheel.
- Okay.
- And don't text and drive,
unless it's an emergency,
like you have a really funny thing
that you just have to text someone.
- Got it.
- So, let me ask you something. Tsk.
Do your parents really love each other,
or is it
a stay-together-for-the-kids situation?
What? Why would you ask me that?
I don't know. Just making conversation.
- Why do we keep passing the same house?
- No, I don't. Shut up.
You shut up. What's the story?
Cute guy live there? Girl you hate?
College kid that gives you Adderall?
Okay, fine.
That's Diego mendoza's house.
He's just this stupid guy.
He's in my calculus class,
and sometimes we'll do this thing
where he goes, "hey,"
and then I go, "hey."
Then he goes, "what's the homework?"
And I tell him.
It's not like a big deal or anything,
but it's like this thing we do.
- Cool thing.
- So, anyway...
My best friend, Alison f.
Was talking to Rachel kaplan.
Do ireally need
to know their names?
Rachel heard from ray-ray
and the bean
that Diego said
if prom happened right now
he'd want to go with am sand/er,
and I'm like,
"yeah, pfft, okay, dude."
You know what I mean?
I don't know these people.
You know I don't know these people.
But then he said
since prom's not for another two months,
he could "foresee a situation"
where he would want to go with me,
because he knows I'm a real girl
who's mostly chill.
If you're so mostly chill,
why do you keep driving by his house?
In case he comes out,
to, like, check the mail or something.
I'll get out of the car and be like,
"that's so funny.
I was just going for a drive."
And he'll be like, "oh, hey."
And I'll be like, "hey."
- 'Cause that's our thing, you know? Heh.
- That's the whole plan?
Well, it's better than your plan
for buying a boat in new Mexico.
Dude, what are you really doing here?
I didn't... like the person I was in la.
And I didn't know where else to go.
- Please do not tell your parents.
- Well, I won't,
but I think people are gonna notice
if you go to a boat show
and don't come back with a boat.
Oh, my god, there he is. Get down!
- Oh, my god. Oh!
- What are you doing?
- What happened to your plan?
- Oh! I panicked.
I didn't know
he'd be wearing a tank top.
- Don't tell my parents I crashed your car.
- Yeah, deal.
- They didn't even put me in.
- I'm sorry, sweetheart.
But you did some great
cheering from the bench,
and for someone who never plays,
you sweat a lot.
- Maybe they'll put me in next game.
- Sure, they will.
No way they'll do that.
- What the...?
- Huh?
- Whoa!
What a boat.
- Can I go on your boat?
- I don't see what's stopping you.
Yeah! Woohoo! I'm going on a boat!
I got my way!
Where's your car?
Ijunked it.
Who needs a car when you got a boat?
- Uh... well...
- Whoa, sweet, a waterbed.
On a boat!
Think of the amount of floating!
Please stay out of the bedroom.
- Does she have a name?
- Who?
- The boat? It does not.
- Come on. You gotta give her a name.
You should call her the escape from la.
That actually is a good name for it,
the nongendered object.
Oh, she's a good girl.
I can tell, she's a good girl, isn't she?
- Or are you a bad girl?
- Are you flirting with my boat right now?
No, just kidding around.
I'm kind of the comedian of the family.
- Mind if I get on top of her?
- Knock yourself out.
Dad, don't be gross.
- Wow, you really got a boat.
- Yeah, sure did.
So, does that mean you're leaving?
Oh, I, uh...
Yeah, I guess, uh... I guess I did...
Do what I came here to do.
You don't have to go right away, right?
At least stay till the end of the weekend.
- Yeah? I don't wanna put you out.
- Oh, it's no bother.
And at least now you have your own bed.
Besides... heh, everyone here loves you.
Uh, everyone?
Don't use the bathroom.
It'll end up in the driveway.
- Too late.
- Seriously, stay as long as you want.
- What?
- Bojack, great news.
Do you still want to go to New York?
Because Jill pill...
Jill pill? I don't care about this.
Okay, moving on. Do you remember
when we were at herb's funeral
- and you told me...?
- Whatever it is, I don't care.
Oh, there's a kitchen!
Can we make pizza bagels?
Yeah, family dinner on the boat.
Hey, uh, I'm not gonna be back
on set Monday.
What? How long do I have
to keep putting out fires for you?
I don't know, Princess Carolyn.
Just let them burn.
- What?
- I think I might be here a while.
Listen, I...
Well, who's getting seasick?
Just kidding.
It's such an eyesore.
Well, I'm sure if we ask them nicely,
they'll move the boat.
Bojack?
- Yeah?
- Supper's ready.
So, I had another meeting today
with the drama chair at sfcc.
They're gonna offer me a position.
- What? That's amazing.
- Oh, that's cool. Congratulations.
There's a real stick-in-the-mud Dean there
who doesn't like my in-your-face style.
If I know me, it might lead
to some pretty zany misadventures.
Mm. Brussels sprouts are delicious, mom.
It's funny you brought up the Brussels
sprouts, because I think they're terrible.
I'm just kidding around.
These are great, hon.
Penny, did you hear my bit
about the Brussels sprouts?
A bit is what they call a joke
in show business.
- Right, bojack?
- That's right.
String a bunch of those together
and you got yourself a riff.
You're not funny, dad.
Your jokes are never funny.
Okay... I think someone's in a mood.
Oh, my god. I'm not in a mood.
Whatever. Get bent.
I hate my life. I can't wait to be dead.
I'll talk to her.
Everyone said for months
- that Diego was gonna ask me to prom.
- Yeah?
- But he keeps not doing it.
- That is so typical Diego.
So, I thought, okay,
if he's not going to ask me, I'll ask him.
- Way to take initiative.
- Oh. Rookie mistake.
So, I asked him and he said no.
And then this other girl Lyla k.
Came up to him and was just like, "hey."
And he was like, "hey."
And that's our thing.
Well, I don't want to tell tales
out of school,
but this Lyla k. Character
sounds like a real bust-ass super-skank.
Thank you, that is exactly what she is.
It's weird that nobody talks about it.
Well, you know, sometimes it's nice
to not have a date,
- because you can actually...
- Mom.
I can't go to the prom without a date.
It's not like when you were in high school
- and you'd go to your sock hops.
- Do you think
- I went to high school in the '503?
- Penny, hey, I got an idea.
- You should take me to the prom.
- Huh?
Everybody loves having bojack around.
What? Why?
Think about it. If you went with Diego,
you'd be nervous.
"Does he like me? Am I cool?"
But with me you can just relax
and enjoy yourself.
Diego will see you
have a good time without him,
and that'll make him superjealous.
So, he'll come up to you,
and he'll say, "hey."
And then you say, "hey."
- Oh, that's so cold.
- Right?
- Wait...
- Rachel kaplan's gonna shit herself.
- How is that cold?
- Then he'll say, "wanna dance?"
And you'll say,
"I'm busy right now. Maybe later."
And then... never dance with him.
- That'll show him.
- Wait... I'm sorry.
- Don't you want to dance with Diego?
- Stop poking holes, Charlotte.
- This is a great plan.
- Yeah, mom, don't poke holes.
Hey, dad, bojack's taking me to prom!
Oh, Yeah, well,
that's definitely the better idea.
Okay, everyone smile. Real big.
- Cheese.
- I think we have enough pictures.
Oh, come on, it's your first prom.
Indulge us.
Taking pictures before prom
is so bourgeois.
And who are you again?
- I'm maddy.
- Maddy's my best friend.
- I thought Alison f. Was your best friend.
- That was like three best friends ago.
You were best friends
with Alison f.?
- No.
- Hey, bojack, I'm Pete.
But they call me Pete repeat
because I always say everything twice.
- Everything?
- Yeah, it's kind of my thing.
- Okay.
- Ah, damn.
I forgot to say that twice, didn't I?
Usually I do it.
Cool.
Wow, ray-ray and the bean
are already posting pics on Instagram.
- What?
- Hashtag much?
Let me see.
Whoa, hold on. Responsible adult.
- What are you drinking?
- Nothing.
- Hand it over.
- Fine.
Ugh. Red bull and vodka? What are you, 12?
You'll get sick drinking all that sugar.
Do they teach you anything in school?
Make a left at the light.
- Where are we going?
- I'll get you some bourbon.
And you'll cut it with water.
That way you don't get hungover.
Wait, really?
If you're gonna drink,
you should be smart about it.
Awesome. Wait.
How many times did I just say "awesome"?
Was it twice or was it once?
Ah, it was probably twice.
Yeah, it's twice. Pete repeat.
- Ugh. It burns.
- Yeah, 'cause it's not a juice box.
You want some?
- No, thanks.
- Pussy.
I'm driving.
Well, more for me.
This prom is really bourgeois.
- Lyla k. Is so pretty.
- Shut up. She's got nothing on you.
Why is nobody dancing?
We gotta get this party started.
Beat it, Poindexter.
- Poindexter?
- It's a nerd reference...
- Just beat it.
- Ah!
Huh?
- Hey!
- What's the big idea?
Why is there an adult
at our high-school prom?
All right, folks.
We're taking it back to 1991,
when a new funky-fresh dance craze
took this nation by storm.
- All right.
- I'm listening.
As a teen, I'm open to new experiences.
Ready for the chorus, stay on the beat,
and here... we... go. Wokka wokka.
Now boys and girls,
if you wanna do the bojack,
- take your hands and put them on your...
- Boo!
- This sucks.
- This guy's bad.
Oh, no. God, no! This is not
the immediate praise I expected.
This prom sucks.
You can say that again.
- I know.
- My flask got empty.
Can we be back to the car,
so, for more get for put in it?
Or we could go back to the car
and just leave.
- You can't just leave the prom.
- Of course you can. You're young.
You can do whatever you want.
That's what they never tell you
until it's too late.
You don't have to be here.
Yeah, he's right. Society is everywhere.
- Society.
- Well, what else are we gonna do?
I'd say it's time to get down,
time to hit the town.
Is that a lyric
from that "do the bojack" song?
Just get in the car.
Okay, one... two... three.
Wow. That is so beautiful.
Hey, you wanna climb up
on the water tower?
We could see the whole city.
Yeah, I wanna go.
Oh.
Oh, careful there, maddy.
Actually, I'm gonna stay right here.
This is nice.
Wow, how'd you think to do all this?
I don't know. It just came to me.
I'm really glad we left that stupid prom,
but I'm kind of bummed
we didn't get to dance.
Well, you wanna dance?
Yes, hold on.
Got it, okay.
It's buffering.
Buffering still, buffering.
This night has been... so perfect.
You know, you look just like your mother.
Guys?
I think you should come down here.
She's still breathing,
but she won't wake up.
She just had too much to drink.
Take her back to your place.
- She can spend the night.
- Maddy, come on.
No, look, my cousin had a friend
who passed out like this,
and she died of alcohol poisoning, man.
I really think we should get maddy
to a hospital, to a hospital.
Did you see what I did there?
That's why they call me Pete repeat.
Bojack, what do we do?
- Society.
- Careful.
- I'm being careful.
- Okay.
- Lock the wheels.
- Watch her head.
Maddy's gonna be just fine.
They'll know what to do here.
Pete, you're in charge.
- Penny and I are gonna take off.
- What?
You don't want too many people around
in a hospital setting.
If anyone asks,
tell them we left the dance early,
and you don't know
where maddy got the whiskey.
Why?
It's one thing if a bunch of kids
get drunk on prom night,
but if there's an adult there,
I was supposed to be responsible,
and then the whole thing feels
kind of creepy.
Are you sure she's gonna be okay?
- I don't know, bojack.
- Pete.
I'm the adult here,
and I need you to listen to me.
Penny and I left early.
You don't know who gave maddy whiskey.
Are we clear on this?
I need you to be 100 percent with me here.
Just listen to him.
He knows what he's doing.
It's gonna be okay.
Where did maddy get the alcohol from?
I... I don't know.
And what happened to your friends
bojack and penny?
They left early.
See, that's not so hard.
You're doing the right thing.
Don't forget that.
- Okay.
- Is it okay?
Or "okay" okay?
- Uh... "Okay" okay.
- All right, that's what I thought.
You're the future of america!
Go, penny! Go, go, go!
- She's gonna be okay, right?
- She'll be fine.
It's a part of growing up.
And we did the right thing back there,
you think?
I...
Look, sometimes when you're an adult,
the right thing
isn't always the best thing.
Well...
I had a really good time tonight.
Even with all the craziness.
This was really special.
I'm glad.
You know, everyone always treats me
like a kid.
You're the first grown-up I've ever met
who actually treats me like...
You know, a person.
So, thanks. Mwah.
- Well, you're welcome, penny.
- Mm...
- Whoa, penny, come on.
- If you want to do it, I'm ready.
I have condoms in my room.
I can put one on with my mouth.
- With your mouth?
- I put one on a banana in health class.
With your mouth?
What kind of health class...?
Look, you are an amazing person,
but you're 17.
Which is the legal age of consent
in new Mexico.
Okay, that's not...
And I didn't drink tonight,
so everything's totally legal.
- Penny, no.
- It's okay. I want this.
No, you think you do, but...
You don't know what you want.
Oh, god.
This is so dumb.
- No, penny, don't...
- I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey.
- What'd you do with my daughter?
- She had a big night.
She was falling asleep on the ride home.
Where are the boys?
Trip's at a friend's house
and Kyle's asleep.
- You know you can get your own, right?
- Hey, do you remember that time
you, me and herb let those balloons go
over studio city?
Oh, yeah. Didn't we attach glow sticks
to them or something?
- Yeah.
- Ooh. That was really bad
for the environment.
- True, but...
- A sea gull could've choked
- on one of those balloons.
- But it's a nice memory, right?
It was a fun night.
We had a lot of fun nights.
Before you left town,
you told me L.A. was a tar pit.
- Do you remember?
- Oh, god.
I said so many things when I was young.
I thought I was so deep.
- Well, do you still think it's true?
- Do I think la. Is a tar pit?
No, I think you're the tar pit.
- Me?
- No, not "you" you.
I'm just saying, like...
It doesn't matter where you are,
it's who you are,
and that's not gonna change
whether you're in California
or Maine or new Mexico.
You know, you can't escape... you.
- Ugh. Now you sound like my mother.
- No, what? No, I don't.
- I don't know what to do, Charlotte.
- About what?
I keep... making these bad decisions.
- And hurting people.
- Well...
- Can I tell you a joke?
- Is it a long joke with no punch line?
- No.
- Then go ahead.
Guy goes into the doctor's office.
Says, "doctor, it hurts when I do this."
You know what the doctor says?
- "Don't do that."
- Yeah.
- That's actually... good advice.
- And you know what else?
The doctor in that story was a woman.
What?!
Oh. Bojack, um...
- I think you got the wrong idea.
- Let's go.
- Let's get out of here right now.
- No, bojack.
You and me, this is real.
- You know this is real.
- My husband is right upstairs.
I don't care about your husband.
All that matters is us.
- Don't do this, bojack.
- I know you feel it, too.
So many times in my life
I've done the wrong thing,
but this is the right thing,
and I have never been more sure
of anything.
I've wasted so much time sitting
on my hands
and imagining what could have been.
Tell me you don't feel the same.
Tell me you haven't thought about it.
- I think you should go.
- Okay.
- Tomorrow.
- Charlotte...
I have worked very hard to build this life
for myself.
I am happy here.
And you just roll into my life
like a hurricane.
Why? Because we knew each other
for five minutes 30 years ago?
- I don't know you.
- You do.
I don't. And you don't know me.
No, please.
These last few months have been amazing.
- I love you, your family and this town.
- Stop.
- I never wanted to hurt...
- Bojackn
I'm sorry I kissed you. I shouldn't have.
We can pretend it didn't happen.
- Everything can go back to normal, but...
- No, no, stop. No.
Please, don't make me go back to la.
I don't care where you go, bojack,
but I can't have you around here.
You make me too sad.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I know what I want, bojack.
Go to bed, penny.
Wait, what?
Shh, shh, shh.
Quiet, quiet, quiet.
- No.
- Mom.
- Charlotte.
- Penny, go to your room.
- We didn't even do anything.
- Now, penny.
- Charlotte, I am so sorry...
- Don't. Don't you dare.
If you are not out of my driveway
in 30 minutes, I will call the police.
And if you ever try to contact me
or my family again,
I will fucking kill you.
Hey.
You're still here?
Yup, still here.
Back in the '90s
I was in a very famous TV show
-I'm bojack the horse -bojack!
Bojack the horse
don't act like you don't know
and I'm trying to hold onto my past
it's been so long
I don't think I'm gonna last
I guess I was trying
to make you understand
that I'm more horse than a man
or I'm more man than a horse
bojack!