[Spaghetti western music]
Whoa!
Okay, how about this one?
Bojack swallowed a dozen
pastries in the time it took
the caterer
to unwrap a fruit tray.
When she asked where
the pastries had gone,
bojack claimed he had no idea,
spraying her with
bits of buttery crust?
[Laughs] I did that once.
Oh, but with holiday cookies.
I had sprinkles
all over my sweater.
See? People respond
to the flawed portrait
I painted of you.
They see themselves in it.
Why do you love secretariat?
Uh, because he was awesome?
No, because he was flawed.
Bojack, when people find
out that someone like you,
who seems larger than life,
is actually just as wounded
and vulnerable as they are,
it makes them feel less lonely.
Ugh, no!
Maybe that's what flawed,
sad fatties want
from other celebrities,
but for bojack horseman,
they want a heroic horse-stud
who is awesome
and who can save them from
their flawed, sad, fatty lives.
- You're so wrong.
- Actually, you know what?
Now that I think about it,
I think that you're so wrong!
Listen, we all agree
Diane broke contract
by leaking
the first two chapters,
but the response
has been amazing!
People want to read more,
and we have to
get this to the printers
by the end of the week,
because that's when
the repo men are coming
to take away our printers.
The end of the week? No!
Okay, what if I told you
that I could have
a new book for you by then?
- What?
- Yeah, a better one.
Better stories,
better told, by me...
Straight from the horse's mouth.
You're gonna write
a whole book in five days?
When's the last time
you even read a book?
"The firm," by John Grisham?
0h, do you think
what you do is so hard?
[Whining] "Oh, I'm a writer.
"I go to coffee shops
with my laptop and my notebook
"and my dumb glasses
that I have to wear,
because I'm so important
I need to see clearly."
Well, I wish you
the best of luck.
You know what your problem is?
You think you're so much
smarter than everybody.
Well, guess what.
I spent as much time with you
as you did with me.
Why don't I write a book about
how you married Mr. Peanutbutter
because he's too dumb to see how
much better you think you are?
- Okay, I know you're upset...
- I'm not upset.
I'm just sick of nerd-girls like
you beating up on stars like me.
It's pathetic!
I'm sorry no one wanted
to date you
in high school, Diane,
but I don't see why I have
to suffer just because
you were never especially
pretty or interesting.
You really let me down, bojack.
You really let me down.
[Slam]
I apologize for her outbursts.
So, you really think you could
write a better book by Friday?
Damn right I can, so you
can throw this turd of a book
in the garbage and then
light the garbage on fire.
In fact, you can burn all books,
because my book,
written by me,
is gonna kick your dick off.
[Funky electronic music]
[Thunder rumbles]
Okay, chapter one.
Hmm.
Not quite right.
Huh. [Cell phone vibrating]
What?
Why are you rewriting
the book, bozo?
Diane's version is great.
You're gonna lose
gems like this one...
[Clears throat]
[Hacking, coughing]
Ahem. "The only
longstanding relationship
"in bojack's life is with
his agent, Princess Carolyn.
"Her loyalty must come
from a deep-rooted faith
"that she's talented enough
to sustain the career of a man
society perceives as a joke."
Uh, yeah, I would say that
I'm not such a fan of that one.
Look, all publicity
is good publicity.
That guy who killed all those
teachers and ate their fingers?
He just got married in jail,
and when this book comes out,
you could be that guy.
Oh, don't you get it?
This is my last chance
to make people love me again.
If this goes out, everybody's
gonna see the real me.
Now, I spend a lot of time
with the real me,
and believe me,
nobody's gonna love that guy.
- Okay.
- Now if you'll excuse me,
I need to go take a shower
so I can't tell
if I'm crying or not.
All right, let's get to work.
[Knuckles crack]
I feel like we can
beat this font.
Ah, copperplate, a font
for the truly modern man.
Ha. No.
There you are, verdana.
Thought you could hide at the
end of the alphabet, did ya?
Oh, comic sans,
you drunk, go home.
3:10? I just spent six hours
playing with fonts? Holy shit!
Okay, focus bojack, focus.
Here comes the focus.
Well, this can't be that hard.
[Diane's voice]
Bojack often felt the need
to impress me
with material items.
You can see from the
teeny, tiny brush strokes,
that this is very expensive.
The color is, um... this one they
don't even have a name for,
that's how exclusive it is,
and this...
[Diane's voice] I wondered where
this came from.
There were two obvious suspects:
His mother Beatrice,
heiress to the sugarman
sugar cubes fortune
and used to certain comforts,
and his working-class father,
butterscotch horseman,
who struggled, and often failed,
to provide those comforts.
Or, maybe it was
something even...
[Explosion noise] Puuuhhhh!
- Hey, Todd, Todd!
- What? What?
- Todd! Todd!
Eyeballs here... look at me.
Look at me!
I need to work.
I can't afford to be distracted.
- Don't distract me.
- Fine.
[Paper rustles]
Oh, Jesus, Todd!
- Read louder much?
- Sorry.
Oh, sure, just drop
toaster strudel crumbs
all over the floor,
why don't you?
Guess I'll just clean them up
myself, like always.
Oh, I can't work like this.
Come on, come on, come on,
pick it up, you dumb vacuum.
Oh, I do not have time for this.
I need to write.
What the... come on!
Seriously?
You cannot be seriou...
God, why are you keeping me
from writing?
[Sighs]
[Upbeat music]
J“ doot j“
j“ doot j“
my parents loved me so much,
it was crazy.
I remember one Sunday afternoon,
my mother said,
"your father and I want to spend
quality family time together.
"All the kids in school
envy your intelligence
"and kickball ability.
["Happy" music plays]
Here's an ice cream sundae."
No, wait.
"An ice-cream sandwich."
No. "A dreamsicle."
Ah, no. I don't know.
This is dumb.
[Happy music wind-down]
[Whack]
Nice writing, Shakespeare.
What did I do?
[Sighs]
Just need something
to help me focus.
Coffee.
No, no. Cigarettes.
[Blows smoke] No, Tequila!
Ah, no, I just need
the right music...
[Classical music]
To do drugs to.
J“ work it j'
Sarah Lynn, I know things
got kind of out of hand
last time when I tried to
make you stop doing drugs.
So I just want to thank you
for coming over this time
to give me drugs.
Well, you can't go wrong
with Dr. Hu's drugs.
They're from another dimension.
These are gonna help me
focus and get work done, right?
Oh, yes. These are what
I give college students
so when they come to, their term
papers have written themselves.
That's exactly what he needs.
Also, I should probably
do another one.
[Sniffs]
Oh, it's "hu." Dr. Hu.
That's right, Dr. Hu.
Dr. Allen hu.
No, no, no, but I thought
it was "who," like "doctor who."
Yes, that's exactly
what it's like.
No, not h-u, but, who,
like, "hello, who is it?"
Uh, I don't know. Who is it?
I'm sorry, is this a joke?
Is he telling a joke
- that I just don't...
- Hard to tell.
Sometimes I just laugh after he
talks so he'll leave me alone.
Seriously? Am I the only one
who knows the extremely popular
BBC science fiction show about
the time traveling doctor
- who saves civilizations?
- Oh, yeah.
I know what you're
talking about... "Doctor who."
- Yes, thank you. "Doctor who."
- Yes?
I saw the one where
she goes to the wild west.
The Cheyenne called her
medicine woman.
What? No, that's Dr. Quinn.
- Who's Dr. Quinn?
- I most certainly am not.
Hu's not Dr. Quinn. Hu's Dr. Hu.
I don't know. Both: Third base!
When are these drugs
going to kick in?
Any minute now,
if they haven't already.
I want you to take three
of these every hour
and take two of these
every 1/2 hour.
Whatever you do, don't take
more than four of these
every 90 minutes, and take
the first two of the three
before you take
the second two of the four.
And don't expose yourself
to bright light or get wet.
- So... gremlin rules?
- Exactly!
Well, I'm off to perform
child heart surgery.
[Groans] Wish me luck.
[Sniffs]
All right, team, focus up.
We got a book to write.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, my god, this is so good.
It's good.
So good, so good.
[Upbeat "action" music]
Okay, Todd, how is it going
with the heartwarming anecdotes?
Great! I'm writing
about that time
we officially became
best friends.
Nice! Can you change
best to pretty good?
Sarah Lynn, how's it coming with
the "horsin' around" years?
Almost done with the story
where hulk hogan guest starred
and told us to say no to drugs.
Great. Keep typing, monkeys.
If only hulk hogan
could see us now, right?
What?
Because Sarah Lynn said
the thing about hulk hogan?
That was like four hours ago.
Oh, uh, right.
- How we doing now?
- Sending.
- Just about to send.
- Nice.
Okay, this is great.
That puts us at 216 pages?
Holy shit, that's almost as long
as "the firm" by John Grisham.
And we just needed
to get to 200, right?
I'm just gonna keep writing.
I got a lot of synapses
firing right now.
It's surprisingly literate
and insightful, but still fun.
It's a beach read you can
thumb through in a wing chair.
Can't believe Diane
thought this was so hard.
"Ow, my fingers are cramping
from all this typing.
It's like they're
having their period."
Did Diane really say that?
No, but my fingers are cramping.
It's like they're having
their period, am I right?
[Laughs]
Are you just laughing
so I'll leave you alone?
[Laughs]
Good one.
We just need a way
to end this thing.
What should the ending be?
-Maybe it was earth all along.
Not that,
but something like that.
Keep thinking.
[Whinnies]
I got it!
Did you guys switch clothes?
Sarah's voice: No.
[Talking backwards]
- Uh... what... huh...
- I don't know.
I like your idea better, bojack.
- What?
- Your idea for the ending.
- Oh, what'd I say?
- About Maine.
About how you end up in Maine.
I like the part where you swim
in the lake in the summers.
Yeah, right, and when I get
too old to take care of myself,
I go for one last swim.
I know I can't make it
back to shore.
I'm too weak, too tired.
So I just let the water
take me under.
Eesh! Downer ending.
- You got something better?
- Wait a minute.
Maybe we don't know
the ending yet
because you haven't lived it.
Yeah, I mean,
if you want to, like, finish
finish the book, then you'd
have to, like, die tonight.
Oh, I know! I should murder you.
[Laughter]
I'm serious.
Think about it.
If the little girl
you raised on television
killed you in real life...
People would eat that shit up.
I love it. It's perfect.
We'll sell so many books.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, kill bojack!
- I'm gonna kill you!
- Oh, yes!
There it is!
Oh, yeah, gonna get you!
No, no, no, no...
Ah!
[All yelling]
[Ominous rock music]
Okay, so what did we learn?
We learned that if
we're going to do drugs
we should do them at home where
it's safe to do them together,
right, Todd?
- No!
- Ahh!
Don't worry, guys.
I have this gun to keep
us safe from intruders.
- And each other.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Is that just
your gun-shaped lighter,
or your lighter-shaped gun?
Busted! It's just a lighter.
[Gunshot] All: Aah!
Shit, I guess it's my gun.
Then what'd I do
with my lighter?
And what did I give
to that baby?
Ha, I have a gun, too.
Don't be a silly Billy.
That's a broom.
Wait, am I holding a gun?
Todd, are you holding
a gun or a broom?
I can't tell anymore!
I guess we'll just have
to shoot them at each other
at the same time to find out!
Okay!
Todd, sh... oh... can I just say...
Todd, Todd, I need you...
I need you to shh.
Listen, listen, Todd.
Okay, just to be totally clear,
we're shooting each other
to determine whether we're
holding guns or brooms, right?
Not because you're still mad
about the whole
me sabotaging you
with the rock opera
and your live stream
and suchety-such?
Bojack, shh, shh, okay, Bo?
Quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet.
As you know, I was hurt,
but then I realized
that's just how you are.
You know, and maybe I just
need to stop expecting you
to be a good person,
so that way, I won't
get hurt when you're not.
Oh, o... okay.
Hey, this isn't fair.
I don't have a gun.
Sarah Lynn is right.
You know, if we all had guns,
then no one would need a gun,
and we would all be safe.
Oh, my god.
I think we just solved
the gun crisis in america.
Let them eat guns!
Bang, bang, pow,
pow, yeah, oh, wow!
Let's celebrate...
By taking more drugs.
[Intense electronic music]
Now we just have to solve
the drug crisis in america.
Easy! We'll take them all.
Yes!
J“ madness,
chaos in the brain j“
j“ let my blood flow j“
j“ make my blood flow
through you, man j“
j“ you've got no business
questioning a thing j“
[music fades]
[Echoing whooping sound]
[Birds twittering]
Bojack?
[Groans, sniffs]
Hey, sorry. You okay?
Yeah...
Listen, I've thought about it,
and you're right.
Your memoir should be
a representation of you.
It's only fair you're happy
with how you're portrayed.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And I want to help write
a book we can both be proud of.
Oh, my god. Thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, what? Ooh!
- Are you okay?
- Oh, no!
[Panting] Not this again!
Gaaaaahhhh!
[Yelling] What is happening!
I ate too many pancakes!
Oh, shit, I'm still tripping.
["Diane" groaning, grunting]
- Kiss me.
- Oh, go...
[Whimpering]
[Electrical crackling]
Ah... ah... oh!
Oh, oh, ah, ah...
[Yelling]
[Laughter]
[Sneezes]
[Cries]
You abandoned me, and I will
never forgive you for that.
I'm Mr. Peanut...
I'm Mr. Peanutbutter.
Oh, my god! [Grunting]
[Panting]
What?
[Deep voice]
Hoo hoo hah hah hah...
Ah!
[Thud]
Whoa.
What the...
Whoa! Okay, stay calm.
I don't have outlines anymore.
That's okay.
There's no boundary
between me and space.
This is a thing that happens.
[Groans]
Shouldn't we help him?
No, he loves treading water.
Oh... oh, god.
Uh-oh. [Whimpering]
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
[Shrill laughter]
[Laughter, chatter]
Why is everyone laughing?
What's so funny?
Cut! Get your head
out of your ass, b.J.
Your line is, "this is all I am
and all I'll ever be."
This is all I am
and all I'll ever be.
You can say that again, old man.
[Echoing laughter]
[Soft heavenly choir] J“ oh j“
- horse, horse, horse!
- What is it?
Will you make me a penis
butter and va-jelly sandwich?
What?
I said, make me a penis butter
va-jelly sandwich, bitch.
[Laughter] No, no.
Well, isn't it too late
to say no, bojack?
This is the road you chose.
[Laughter]
I'm sinking, somebody help.
The floor is tar.
Why don't you come with me?
Come to Maine.
I can't, I'm stuck.
Do they have pinkberry in Maine?
I can't!
- Go out there.
- I can't.
Can't lives in a house
on won't street.
You will not embarrass me in
front of the entire supper club.
I told them you were going
to sing the "lollipop" song.
But I don't feel like singing.
Nobody gives a damn
what you feel.
You've got an audience
out there,
and they want to hear you sing.
Now, you want your mommy
to love you?
You go out there and you do
the only thing you're good for,
which is singing
the goddamn "lollipop" song.
And let me tell you somethin':
The secret to living
forever is...
[Bell tolling]
Oh, no.
Hey.
What seems to be the problem?
Good grief. I'm so depressed.
I just want everyone to love me,
but I don't know
how to make them do it.
You can't force love,
you blockhead.
All you can do is be good
to the people in your life,
and keep your heart open.
I screwed it all up.
It's too late for me, isn't it?
I don't know.
I'm just a crazy
drug hallucination.
I'll say whatever
you want me to.
Then tell me it's not too late.
Well, it's not too late.
It's never too late.
- Yeah, that's right.
- It's never too late
to be the person you want to be.
You need to choose
the life you want.
That'll be 5¢ please...
[Grunts]
Bojack.
Yes, dear?
Supper's ready.
Ran into ed
at the hardware store.
He said we're
in for some weather.
What the hell does that mean?
"Some weather."
We're always
in for some weather.
Guess what, ed?
There's never not weather.
[Laughs]
Oh, bojack, don't.
Come on, I can't help it.
It's just so cute
how they do it automatically.
How do they know?
Oh, man, can we just stay
exactly like this
for the rest of our lives,
please?
Yeah, okay, sure, uh, or we
could do the opposite of that,
because I'm pregnant.
What? That's amazing.
Yeah, and I'm 80% sure
it's yours.
Is it weird that I want
to make love to you right now?
Why would that be weird?
I don't know, it's...
I don't want to spook the baby.
Maybe we should just
do mouth and hand stuff
for the next nine months.
[Mellow instrumentals]
Oh, I think someone's awake.
Dada coming? Dada coming?
Yes, gooby girl, dada's coming.
Dada.
I'm gonna eat your finger.
Yum, yum, num, num.
[Baby giggling, cooing]
- Daddy?
- Harper?
Where do the stars go?
Oh, they're still there.
We just can't see them
because the sun is shining.
- Oh. Daddy?
- Harper?
Do you think if you were a
little kid, we would be friends?
Well, that depends.
Do you love cookies,
and the color green, and braids?
Yes, I love all those things.
Well, then, your application
has been submitted
and is pending board approval.
Approved!
Wah! [Laughing]
Whoa!
Oh, no splashing!
Oh, no.
Oh, oh, it's rough, oh, don't.
Oh, oh, you're tickling.
I got you!
She grew up so fast.
I don't like that
he drives a motorcycle.
Honey, a Vespa
is not a motorcycle.
[Laughs]
Okay, okay.
What are you thinking about?
Oh, just how nice
things could've been
if you had chosen this life.
[Distant rhythmic sound]
[Cell phone vibrating]
Oh... what? Where?
[Vibrating, music playing]
Hello?
Bojack, I read the pages
you sent me last night,
and I have to tell you,
your book is absolutely,
without a doubt, the most...
Gibberish.
- It's gibberish.
- What day is it?
Let's see what you got here.
You got 20 pages of
"doctor who" erotic fan fiction,
a recipe for soup,
five different theories
about how 9/11 happened,
and a bunch
of embedded YouTube videos
that can't possibly
be printed in book form.
Okay, I gotta go. [Beep]
Any questions, at all,
for our panel of ghost writers?
Um, yeah, I have a question
for Tori spelling.
Again, Tori spelling is not
here, as I already explained.
Tori spelling's
ghost writer is here.
This is a ghost writer
convention.
How do you not...
[Clears throat]
Okay, next question?
Uh, yeah,
this is for the whole panel.
What's your favorite kind
of ghost to write for?
What?
No, they don't write for ghosts.
That's not what? Why did I think
this would be a good idea?
Does anyone have
an actual question
for someone on this panel?
An actual question, or a gun,
so I can shoot myself?
Yeah, I got a question.
Oh, thank god.
[Microphone feedback]
My question is for Diane.
Look, I'm sorry about all the
stuff I said about you earlier.
We can publish
the book you wrote.
You're obviously a better
writer than I am,
and I don't actually
even really care
what the world thinks
about me anymore.
I just hated reading that book
because I hated feeling like
that's how you saw me.
Because I guess you know me
better than anybody,
and if you think that...
I guess my question is, do you...
Do you think
it's too late for me?
What?
I mean, am I just doomed
to be the person that I am?
The... the person in that book?
It's not too late for me, is it?
It's... it's not too late...
Diane, I need you to tell me
that it's not too late.
- Bojack, I...
- I... I need you to tell me
that I'm a good person.
I know that I can be selfish
and narcissistic
and self-destructive,
but underneath all that,
deep down, I'm a good person,
and I need you to tell me
that I'm good, Diane.
Tell me, please, Diane.
Tell me that I'm good.
[Lonely bird calling]
[Harper giggling distantly]
Hey, aren't you the horse
from "horsin' around"?
J“ back in the '903 j”
j“ I was in a very famous TV show j“
- j“ I'm bojack the horse j“
- I bojack j“
j“ bojack the horse j”
j“ don't act like you don't know I
j“ and I'm trying to hold on to my past j“
j“ it's been so long j“
j“ I don't think I'm gonna last j“
j“ I guess I'll just try j”
j“ and make you understand I
j“ that I'm more horse than a man j'
j“ or I'm more man than a horse j“
j“ bojack j“
boxer versus raptor.
J'nanananananananal'