[Dick on TV] This is from bojack h.
Bojack is nine years old.
"When I grow up, I want to be like you.
I'm on the right track.
Get it? Track? Because horses
run on tracks and you are a horse.
And I am a horse. Do you get it?
Do you get my joke about the track?"
- There's a whole page of this.
- Should I write him, tell him I get it?
[Dick]
He goes on. "My question for you is:
I am a good kid and I like to play,
and I like to go to school,
but sometimes I get sad.
What do you do when you get sad?
How do you not be sad?"
[Mother] Oh, big stud, running off
to gallivant with your fillies.
[Plate smashes]
[Father] Is that to impress me?
I can smash a dinner plate, too.
[Mother] That's a salad plate.
[Father]
I thought these were salad plates.
[Mother] Those are saucers.
[Father] Why do we even have saucers?
We don't drink tea.
[Mother]
Those saucers are for entertaining!
[Father]
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm exit-taining.
Do you get it?
[Door slams]
But, uh, seriously, folks.
[Chuckles] Right?
[Mother groans]
Don't sit so close to the TV,
it'll make you cruel.
You know, I was beautiful
- before I got pregnant.
- I know.
- You ruined me, bojack.
You better grow up to be something great
to make up for all the damage you've done.
[Man on TV]
And I just kept running. Bojack...
Okay, enough me being a great mom.
I'm gonna go hide
your father's heart medication.
Enjoy your dumb little TV show.
[Man on recording] The first thing is,
you gotta believe that change is possible.
You have to tell yourself every day:
"I can change and I will change."
- I can change and I will change.
- [Man on recording] Louder.
I can change and I will change.
- [Man on recording] I still can't hear you.
- You're an audiobook.
[Man on recording]
"I've got a new attitude."
T hat's what your face should be saying
to everyone you pass on the street.
We call that the pants approach.
P-a-n-t—s.
People all need to see.
Yeah, a little to the right.
No, house right.
That's an acting term.
It means left. I'm an actor.
[Phone ringing]
[Groans]
No.
- Bojack, why did I wake up in an alley?
- I had to get rid of the old couch, Todd.
While I was sleeping on it?
The couch was a metaphor
for my old attitude.
My audiobook told me I had to let go
of the burdens of my life sofa.
Oh, you know what?
Maybe it was "my life so far."
I feel like
you could've woken me up first.
Todd, no one can wake anybody else up.
You need to wake yourself up.
I don't know if I trust this new guy.
I'm just gonna go sleep in your car.
- Uh-oh. I think someone needs a fab.
- A fab?
Fab, stands for fresh active bna.
- Bna?
- Brand-new attitude. Try to keep up.
Attitude stands for attention to...
Did you also get rid of my stuff?
Where's my duffel bag?
I value you.
Hashtag "thank you for being a friend."
Hashtag "pants."
[Panting]
[Man on recording]
You got to conquer that hill.
The hill is a metaphor.
Everything is a metaphor.
- You are literally a metaphor.
- Oh, my god.
Oh, my god, this is the worst.
This feels awful.
Why does anybody run?
On your right.
And she had no idea
that her boyfriend was the strangler.
I guess some people just see what
they wanna see, right, Vincent?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Princess Carolyn.
I gotta 90.
One of my dumb-ass clients is here.
Just out for a jog, thought I'd say hello.
I jog now.
You jogged here from Laurel canyon?
I drove, but I moved my arm a bunch,
so the fitbit counted the miles.
Uh, someone named bojark hoseman
is here?
- Thank you, Stuart.
- Also, your coffee is coming late
- just like you ordered.
- I said "latte."
Ah. Well, I wrote down “late,"
so that's what it's gonna be.
- What happened to Laura?
- Assistants are like belushi brothers.
Good ones leave too soon,
bad ones never go away.
It's a beautiful day, though, right?
Every morning is a miracle.
Hashtag “miracle."
Hashtag "every morning."
Hashtag "every morning's a miracle."
Hashtag "bojack thoughts."
I'm glad you found your bliss, but are you
ready for your first day on set tomorrow?
You mean, am I amped?
Because I am so pumped.
This secretariat movie is a big deal.
Please do not blow it.
Why would I blow it?
I have a brand-new attitude.
You know, when I won that golden globe
last month, I went to a very dark place.
I was in a hole.
And I realized, "I can wallow
in this hole or I can change."
While I was tempted to go with the former,
sometimes the only way out of a hole
is a latter.
- No pun intended.
- You clearly intended that pun.
Princess Carolyn,
you gotta believe in the ahp of tpe.
Huh.
- Uh-uh. I'm not asking.
- The awesome healing power...
- I am not asking.
- -Of total positive energy.
You should leave because
I'm about to pretend to get a phone call.
Hello? [Chuckles]
No, he's still here.
- No, he is not taking the hint somehow.
- Mm-hm.
[Mr. Peanutbutter]
Honey, where's my bandana?
You chewed it up,
we had to throw it away, remember?
[Mr. Peanutbutter] No, not that one.
The one with the bones on it.
With the meat juice stains?
The one I wore to the emmys.
I don't know. I gotta go.
Bojack's gonna be here any minute.
Did you check the hall closet?
[Mr. Peanutbutter]
I can't see anything in this stupid thing.
I know, Mr. Peanutbutter.
But you gotta keep it on
for one more week.
[Thudding,
then Mr. Peanutbutter grunting]
I look like an idiot.
You look very responsible.
Is the bandana doing anything?
[Doorbell rings]
Hey, work buddy,
first day on the job, huh?
Hashtag "great day to start fresh
at a new job, sincerely, bojack."
- At Diane.
- Can't believe you wanted to carpool.
- Gotta save the planet, Diane.
- Hey, is that bojack horseman?
I don't know because I have no peripheral
vision. Going off of smell here folks.
Mr. Peanutbutter, how the hell are you?
- Loving it, buddy. Loving life.
- Brother, I am right there with you.
I got a brand-new attitude
and I am also loving life.
Diane, look at us.
A couple life-lovers over here.
- Uh...
- Is that a new cone? Looking sharp, pb.
It is a new cone.
Is it obvious I'm wearing a cone?
Didn't notice.
You've got the smile of a winner.
- What's going on?
- I have to wear the cone
so I don't gnaw on the stitches I had
to get when I punched a mirror last week.
I got drunk and thought my reflection
was another dog. [Chuckles]
I was so mad at that other dog.
He was wearing my clothes.
- We've all been there.
- I don't understand what's happening.
Did someone say something to the left?
Diane, is that you?
Hey, why don't we just us two schedj
a hang for this 'kend?
"'Kend" is how I say weekend now.
Uh, I love that. And I got a pair of tix
to the 'stones show this 'kend.
- Wanna go?
- The rolling stones?
What? Oh, no, no, no.
The mighty mighty bosstones.
I'm not really familiar with that outfit,
but I do love trying new things.
- Who are you?
- Anyway, we gotta get to work.
It was really great talking to you,
Mr. Peanutbutter.
All right, break a leg, good buddy.
Diane, bojack's ready to go.
Where are you, sweetheart?
Are you ready?
[Man on recording]
The house is a metaphor for a home.
Happiness is a metaphor for change.
Happiness is a metaphor...
- Where are we going?
- Oh, my god.
Bojack, this is corduroy
Jackson-Jackson, your costar.
- Hey, man.
- Corduroy Jackson-Jackson.
Oh, right, the underwear guy.
Underwear model[Actor/dancer/dreamer.
[Chuckles]
Also, you know, I'm a huge fan.
I'm so excited/amped/pumped
to be working with you.
[Chuckles] Yeah.
Hey, man, that's
fantastic/great/i-ran-out-of-things.
- Hi. Kelsey jannings?
- That depends.
- Are you my ex-wife's lawyer?
- I'm Diane.
I'm here to be a character consultant.
- What?
- I got a call from the studio.
Okay. Why don't you stand over there and
make sure no one trips over that cable?
- This cable?
- Do you have a thousand dollars?
- What?
- Because each minute
I spend talking to you,
that's how much money I'm wasting.
- Oh. Sorry.
- Hey, who's this guy?
- Who let this guy in?
- I just...
He's got a funny face. I like your face.
- Thank you.
- What a funny face. Cookie?
Can someone get this guy a cookie?
He's got a soothing face
and I like looking at it.
- Like a Matisse painting.
- Whoa.
Guys, could I get
everyone's attention, please?
Oh, watch out for the cable.
Don't trip over the cable.
I just want everyone to know
what an honor it is to be here.
Secretariat has always been
a personal hero of mine.
A complex role that requires
a precise touch and a deft hand
and I just can't wait to tackle it
head-on.
It's truly an honor.
Namaste.
Neat. So, in this scene,
secretariat's at his lowest.
He just lost his first race,
his father was sent to the glue factory.
It's a dark moment.
- You got it.
- Scene 22 Alpha, take one.
[Inhales, then exhales]
- [Kelsey] Action!
- Hey, secretariat.
What are you doing here?
[Chuckles]
[Mumbles, then chuckles]
[Kelsey groans]
[Phone buzzing]
- Hello?
- Diane!
I can't tell you how disappointed I am
you're not here with me
in northern cordovia.
I'm incredibly disappointed. Boo!
I didn't think I could do it,
but I did it.
I'm amazing.
Sebastian,
I know you're doing important work.
I couldn't just drop everything
and fly to the third world.
- I just got married, and...
- [Sebastian] Diane.
People are dying, and I'm witnessing it.
And I need people
to witness me witnessing it.
I know, and I'll be there in three months,
as soon as I'm done on the movie.
This is also important.
In a way.
Well, lucky for you,
there'll still be just as much famine
and war and devastation
in three months.
I'm not dead yet.
- Yep. Lucky me.
- [Man] We're still rolling, people.
So, bojack, in this scene,
secretariat is sad, right?
Afraid he's gonna lose his scholarship.
Oh, sure. Yeah, sad. Of course. Duh.
[Chuckles]
Okay, here we 90. Action.
Hey, secretariat.
What are you doing here?
That was bad. I know that was bad.
Let's keep it rolling.
- I'll say when to keep rolling.
- Okay.
What are you doing here? Did we get it?
I can tell by your face that we didn't.
All right, let me try again.
What are you doing...?
I am having trouble with the words.
Is it okay if I play around with it a bit?
When did you get here?
Sorry, no. Got it. Got it. Got it.
Man, these lights are bright, huh?
Can we kill these lights at all?
Is that a...?
- No.
- Okay, I'm sad.
I'm sad. Acting sad.
Secretariat is sad.
Okay, here we go.
I'm sad!
Sorry, what was the line?
I don't know if this helps or not,
but when secretariat was a kid
- he actually...
- Aah!
- My face!
- [Man 1] Hey, hey.
- Whoa, whoa!
- [Man 2] Oh, my god.
[Man 3] Watch out! [Man 4] Hey.
[Man 5] Oh, no, not me.
[Man 6] Whoa, whoa!
[Pa] Oh, my god. My face.
My beautiful face.
Why didn't someone tell me
not to trip over that cable?
It was such an important job,
but no one was there to do it
and now my face is in ruins.
We're gonna need a couple of days
to rebuild the set.
So, let's all just use this time
to regroup
and really figure out what we're doing
and why we're here.
[Audience laughing]
So, let me get this straight.
Bad means good?
Maybe you should leave the teen-talk
to me. Jeezy kableezy.
[Audience laughing]
Well, it wasn't ibsen.
That's your takeaway?
That your son's TV show wasn't ibsen?
I'm sorry. Did you need a compliment?
Oh, I loved the part where you got
your head caught in the banister.
- Yeah...
- And what's this letter I have?
It's from the government saying,
"I'm proud of you."
- Are you...?
- No, what I'm holding is nothing.
Can you check on our drinks?
I would love some gin.
I wouldn't drink anything out of an open
container. This town is full of aids.
- That's not...
- You're a clown, you know that?
You've always been a pillar of support.
Gin, please? 15 there gin coming?
I'm here, aren't I?
I suffered through that ordeal.
You know, the man sitting next to me
was wearing a t-shirt?
A t-shirt, bojack, in the theater.
Yes, a t-shirt.
Worst thing that's happened to anyone
in a theater.
- The t-shirt told me to "just do it."
- Here we go.
I don't know to what "it"
the t-shirt referred
but I won't be spoken to in that tone
by an article of clothing.
Vodka? Triple sec?
Looking for any alcohol.
You don't know how
lucky you are to have me.
I hope you die before I do so you never
know what it's like to lose a mother.
Well as long as one of us dies,
that's good enough for me.
Can we please get some alcohol
into my mouth?
[Man on recording]
The past is past.
That's why it's called the past.
Tomorrow is an opportunity.
You can be big and proud
and bang on your Tom-Tom drum
or you can get in your boat and row.
Tom or row.
Tomorrow.
- Hey, do you wanna talk?
- Talk? Why? Why would we do that?
So you can put everything
in a book and sell a million copies?
Wow. Uh...
That's what the old me would have said.
The new me doesn't hold a grudge.
[Phone rings]
- No.
- I gotta say
the new you seems a little on edge.
What? Me?
I'm as cool as the fonz in a meat locker.
That's a metaphor, Diane.
- It's a simile.
- Goddamn it.
[Phone rings]
Oh, okay. Hello?
Small talk, small talk, small talk.
Are you blowing it?
- I heard you're blowing it.
- What? Who told you that? Was it Todd?
You gotta turn this ship around, boj.
If you don't...
Hey, can you hold on a second?
I'm getting another call.
Well, if it isn't my friend rutabaga,
the boy prince of the 26th floor.
Carolyn.
How are things all the way up on 27?
Stomp once for good, twice for killing it.
Killing...
Give me some gossip.
My wife is making me go
to the opera tonight.
I need something to distract me
from the thought of d-bags
singing songs in German
about their boners.
Okay, you gotta
keep this close to the vest
but I am inches
from getting Emily vancamp
the lead in goose Van sant's
new movie about Jackie o.
My clients would flip
if I got them parts like that.
You're killing it
in the department of kicking ass
in regards to you being an agent
and being good at it, crushing it.
You're not so bad yourself, rutabaga,
for a 26er. [Chuckles]
You're the only one in this building
who isn't a total snooze-cooze.
Yes, Natasha, I'm talking about you.
I know you're listening.
Ugh. I gotta go. I made Natasha cry.
[Chuckles]
I don't think she's coming back.
Could we keep it down
in the front, please?
- Thank you.
- What am I gonna do?
Well, you were an actor for nine years
on horsin' around. How did you do that?
- Hey, can I talk to you for a minute?
- Of course, buddy.
I always have time for you,
my good friend bojack
in this, the year 1988.
Have a seat.
[Stomping overhead]
Hey, enough with the stomping already!
- Am I...? Am I a clown?
- Oh, brother.
Didn't I tell you not to invite your mom
to the taping?
As Max headroom would say,
"your mom is a bitch." [Chuckles]
But I am a good actor, right?
Bj, I don't know.
You know what you're good at?
Hitting your Mark and saying your lines,
loudly with good diction.
Should I be doing more?
To capture the character
- and make the audience connect?
- This is a situation comedy.
No one watches this show to feel feelings.
Life is depressing enough already.
You bring joy to millions of people.
Maybe someday later,
you'll need to learn how to act for real.
But for now,
[Chuckles] Don't worry about it.
Oh, shit. I'm not an actor.
All this time, I assumed there was more
to me than everyone thought
but maybe there isn't.
The part where you're supposed
to disagree with me.
Oh, right.
Well, you got the part, didn't you?
What did you do in the audition?
Well, how should I know?
That was the old me.
Now I've got a brand-new attitude.
Oh, god. Okay. Okay.
What should I do?
Make a break for it? Drive to Mexico?
Start a new life there?
Meet a local girl? Fall in love?
Talk my way into a job at a textile plant?
Work my way up until I own the place?
What am I talking about?
I can't run a textile plant.
Too much responsibility. What am I
gonna do? The walls are closing in!
Bojack, breathe. You can do this.
You have two days.
Maybe you could hire an acting coach.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Plus, you can watch old
secretariat videos.
I've got a hard drive full of research.
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
You're right. I can do this.
I've got two whole days.
And when the pressure's on,
that's when I shine.
Yeah. Two days.
I can do all those things.
Oh, shit. I didn't do any of those things.
- What are you doing here?
- Ah!
That was it. Say that again.
What are you doing here?
Bojack, before we get started
- I wanted to show you this.
- What?
This is the machine
that's gonna make you a good actor.
- Really?
- We need to make a scan of your face
so that if you die,
we can finish the movie.
Standard procedure. When a star
is assessed to be of a certain liability,
like if there was a whole book written
about what a reckless jackass he is,
you make a digital replica so you're
not screwed if he goes all belushi on you.
- Wait, which belushi?
- Hold still, please.
[Whirring]
- Terrific. We got it.
- One day, that's gonna be the job.
Sit for five seconds
while a machine scans his face.
Six months later,
plugging a movie on kimmel.
I gotta go on kimmel now?
What if he makes me read a mean tweet?
I'm not emotionally prepared.
Don't worry so much.
If you can't do this part
we'll just fire you and get someone else
who can. Either way, I'll be fine.
- [Groans]
- What do you need, bojack?
I don't know. I thought I wanted this,
but now I'm feeling all this pressure.
- Think you made a mistake, hiring me?
- I don't make mistakes, bojack.
I do the crossword in sharpie,
I never learned the shortcut for undo.
- Command-z.
- Don't need it, won't use it.
I'm trying to have this new attitude,
be this better, more positive guy.
I keep thinking about how this movie
is my last shot at happiness.
Well, bojack, I hope this helps:
I don't care if you are happy or not.
You have a job to do.
[Kelsey chuckles]
This guy again? I'm in love with this kid.
I wanna put you in my pocket. [Grunts]
- You're adorable.
- Aw.
[Man sobbing]
- Hey, Diane, you're a writer, aren't you?
- Yes.
Yes. I am a writer. What do you need?
Can you write on a sign
"watch out for cable"?
You were telling people,
but it's a really important job
and a sign is less likely
to get distracted.
Oh. Yeah. Okay.
What are you doing here?
- What are you doing here?
- So, I went a little overboard
and I made you two mixes.
The first cd is all mighty mighty.
The second cd is all of the bosstones'
side projects and solo singles.
Listen to it and imagine the band
never took that hiatus
in the mid-aughts
when america briefly lost interest in ska.
I don't have time.
I don't wanna listen to your music.
I don't wanna hang out.
Get out of here.
[Mr. Peanutbutter chuckles]
All right. You don't wanna listen
to bosstones together.
That's the impression that I get.
- Is it the impression that I get?
- Yes. That's the impression that you get.
[Todd yawns]
I see. Way to go, Mr. Peanutbutter.
What a stupid move. Why did you...?
[Snarling]
[Bojack groans]
Bojack, listen, I know you're scared,
but it's gonna be okay.
- You gotta be strong.
- Yeah, but...
You gotta rise to the occasion, okay?
So what if the new couch is weird?
- Or lumpy?
- Uh, what?
What are you gonna do?
Just sleep in bojack's car forever?
- Are you talking to me, or you...?
- Damn it, time to stop being a coward.
It's time to go home
and sleep on bojack's couch. Hurray!
Happy ending for Todd!
[Sighs]
[Phone rings,
then Charley gasps and grunts]
Charley Witherspoon, 28th floor agent.
Charley. Listen, I wanted to touch base
about Emily's start date on Jackie o.
Oh, yeah. Uh...
Well, we got some new screen tests
and, uh, goose decided to go
in a different direction.
Are you saying the Van sant camp
wants to recant on vancamp?
Because they can't.
Charley, you better get your client
to change his mind
- or I'll walk up to the 28th floor and...
- Just kidding.
- I can't get to the phone right now.
- What?
This is one of those answering machines
that sounds like it's Charley talking
but it's actually
just an answering machine.
- I know you're there, Charley.
- Leave a message.
- I'm not gonna leave a message.
- Beep.
Hey, Charley, Princess Carolyn again.
Listen...
- Mailbox is full.
- What? Mailbox full?
- Error. Message deleted.
- Wait... no...
Gotta go. Bye.
[Grunting]
[Phone rings]
[Rutabaga over phone] Carolyn.
Rutabaga, this is not a good time.
Okay. Can I please just tell you
about the opera, though?
[Groans]
- How did you like the opera?
- I loved it.
Loved Tristan, loved isolde,
cried like a bunny.
Listen, my brain has been a-buzzing
for the past few days
thinking about that Jackie 0 movie.
I know it's your baby,
but I did make a few calls
and got my Rooney a screen test.
I put that movie together for my client.
No, no, no, don't freak out.
It's just a screen test.
But, honestly,
how fantaj would my Rooney be
as a young Jackie bouv?
Stomp once for so fantaj,
twice for stupid-fantaj.
Carolyn? I only heard one stomp.
Oh. Carolyn, I heart you.
You're beautiful.
I wish I met you before I got married.
[Groans]
[Man on recording]
You can do it.
Only you hold the keys
to the house that is you.
The house is at the top of a hill.
The hill is also you.
[Knock on door]
Five minutes, Mr. Horseman.
[Man on recording]
When you get your new attitude
you're gonna wave goodbye
to the old...
[Phone ringing]
[Groans]
What do you want, mom?
Look who finally decided
to pick up the phone.
- Do you need more blood?
- I don't need blood.
- I read your book, bojack.
- 0h.
It takes a real narcissist to think
anyone wants to buy a book about him.
You know how I feel about Anne frank.
- That was a diary.
- [Mother] I read the parts about me.
The things I said to you.
You must think I'm a real monster.
- Mom...
- [Mother] I don't wanna fight you, bojack.
I just wanted to tell you I know.
I know you wanna be happy,
but you won't be, and...
- [Mother] I'm sorry.
- What?
It's not just you, you know.
Your father and I, we...
Well, you come by it honestly,
the ugliness inside you.
[Mother] You were born broken,
that's your birthright.
And now you can fill your life
with projects
your books and your movies
and your little girlfriends
but it won't make you whole.
[Mother] You're bojack horseman.
There's no cure for that.
Anyway, do you remember
who directed the Philadelphia story?
Five letters, second letter u?
- Lubitsch?
- [Sighs] No, bojack. Goodbye.
[Man on recording]
You need to visualize it
flying out the window, over the...
What are you doing here?
[Kelsey]
Great. We got it. Let's move on.
Back in the '905
I was in a very famous TV show
- I'm bojack the horse - bojack
bojack the horse
don't act like you don't know
and I'm trying to hold on to my past
it's been so long
I don't think I'm gonna last
I guess I 'ii just try
and make you understand
that I'm more horse than a man
or I'm more man than a horse
j“ bojack! J“
boxer versus raptor.